{
  "timestamp": "2025-05-11T08:07:46.182999",
  "total_mcqs": 3044,
  "total_source_mcqs": 3044,
  "fixed_mcqs": 2595,
  "no_match_mcqs": 449,
  "status_counts": {
    "fixed": 1733,
    "no_match": 449,
    "answer_fixed": 862
  },
  "changes": [
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022392,
      "question_number": "77",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient with intracerebral hemorrhage (ICH) followed by midline shift had an external ventricular ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Replace EVD and give IV vancomycin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7783094098883573,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3280867436166492,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022393,
      "question_number": "74",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A female patient fell from a height of 3 meters while cleaning her house and presents with severe he...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. CT brain",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7665198237885462,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.37354544115480925,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022394,
      "question_number": "165",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is a therapeutic effect of mannitol?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022395,
      "question_number": "64",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient presented with fluctuating levels of consciousness. Which of the following should...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Metabolic panel screen"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022396,
      "question_number": "73",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient with head trauma arrives at the emergency department conscious and oriented. After one hou...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Epidural hemorrhage",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8109161793372319,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7601179308496382,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022397,
      "question_number": "20",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q20. A female patient post subarachnoid hemorrhage (SVD) presented with headache, visual field defic...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pituitary Apoplexy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7253668763102725,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.772408293460925,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022398,
      "question_number": "164",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is a potential complication of using hypertonic saline in the treatment of increased ICP?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Pulmonary edema",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6241610738255033,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6126406511850611,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022399,
      "question_number": "163",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient was admitted after a cardiac arrest and is now in the ICU. He is intubated, sedat...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Perform an EEG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8053435114503816,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5073823010493081,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022400,
      "question_number": "152",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "EVD associated with infection:",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022401,
      "question_number": "155",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q155. A female patient diagnosed with cerebral venous thrombosis (CVT) was admitted to the ICU and t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Increased intravascular volume",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7211895910780669,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6155471060414026,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022402,
      "question_number": "149",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "When should a patient with Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome be admitted to the ICU?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Evolving respiratory distress"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022403,
      "question_number": "167",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is the most important predictor of outcome in cardiac arrest?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022404,
      "question_number": "4",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A brain CT shows coup contrecoup injury (left frontal and right temporal bleed). What is the mechani...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Trauma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7124183006535948,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7638903152921844,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022405,
      "question_number": "33",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient with no available history is brought to the emergency department with fever and decreased ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Acyclovir"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022406,
      "question_number": "156",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is the difference between mannitol and hypertonic saline?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022407,
      "question_number": "70",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following statements is true regarding the duration of effect between hypertonic saline...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022408,
      "question_number": "10",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient came with high blood pressure and a picture of PRESS syndrome. What is the management?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Control BP"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022409,
      "question_number": "143",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q143. A patient with a 3 mm hemorrhage in the putamen is stable but has increased edema and decrease...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Osmotic treatment",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.80306905370844,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5988788945378699,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022410,
      "question_number": "157",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient with a long ICU stay developed neuropathy/myopathy. What is the recommended management?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Physiotherapy and supportive care",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6643356643356644,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6385731448110156,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022411,
      "question_number": "56",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A 19-year-old female presents with acute encephalopathy. MRI of the brain demonstrates T2/FLAIR hype...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Lumbar puncture (LP)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022412,
      "question_number": "47",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is the most important predictor of outcome in cardiac arrest?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Duration of CPR",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5485232067510548,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.783981517135156,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022413,
      "question_number": "145",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "In a case of subarachnoid hemorrhage (SAH), the patient is found to have hyponatremia, high urine so...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Intravenous fluids (IVF)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7837150127226463,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7731595255903408,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022414,
      "question_number": "5",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "An elderly male presents with decreased oral intake for one week and is inattentive during examinati...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Generalized slowing",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8176470588235294,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3257059939725416,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022415,
      "question_number": "62",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "In a Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome scenario, what is the predicting factor for intubation?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "D. Presence of respiratory failure",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5878136200716846,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.20158899561247481,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022416,
      "question_number": "344",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following statements is true regarding mannitol and hypertonic saline in the management...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022417,
      "question_number": "408",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is a poor prognostic indicator after cardiac arrest at 24 hours?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022418,
      "question_number": "32",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is the best predictor for a patient in a coma (not considering brain death or time)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Etiology"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022419,
      "question_number": "29",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is the threshold of intracranial pressure (ICP) that is considered abnormal?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. 22 mmHg",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7647058823529411,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7561315496098104,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022420,
      "question_number": "121",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Assessment of blood\u2013brain barrier (BBB) in traumatic brain injury (TBI) is best indicated by which o...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. S100B",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7083333333333334,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2985399192295744,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022421,
      "question_number": "162",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient with ventricular hemorrhage is being evaluated for ventriculostomy. Which one of the follo...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. The risk of infection increases after day 7.",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5030927835051546,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.40557512635931997,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022422,
      "question_number": "67",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient is brought unconscious to the emergency department. A CT of the brain shows multiple hemor...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Traumatic",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8207171314741036,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7105962376448082,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022423,
      "question_number": "168",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is assessed to evaluate the blood-brain barrier (BBB) in traumatic brain injury (TBI)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. S100",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6394052044609665,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7459595959595959,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022424,
      "question_number": "160",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is the most appropriate test to order next for an elderly patient admitted with cardiac arrest ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Brain death assessment"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022425,
      "question_number": "10",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient with a history of inability to care for himself presents with decreased level of ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Diffuse slowing",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.702576112412178,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.15161541455819386,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022426,
      "question_number": "3",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q3. A patient presented with visual symptoms, confusion, and is taking immunosuppressants for renal ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Control blood pressure"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022427,
      "question_number": "153",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient had an accident and presents with a Glasgow Coma Scale (GCS) score of 5. What is the role ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. No evidence in traumatic brain injury"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022428,
      "question_number": "80",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is the most important diagnostic factor in hypoxic post-cardiac arrest in comatose patients?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Neurological examination findings",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.631578947368421,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6924046282506587,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022429,
      "question_number": "78",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A 63-year-old male admitted with left hemiparesis underwent CABG. He was successfully extubated off ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. EEG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9170437405731523,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6281031573873223,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022430,
      "question_number": "77",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "An elderly female is brought to the ER with a level of consciousness that is altered. Her labs show ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Vitamin K"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022431,
      "question_number": "22",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Following a road traffic accident (RTA), the patient developed post-concussion syndrome. What is the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Shear injury"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022432,
      "question_number": "158",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "In an elderly patient post-cardiac arrest who underwent therapeutic hypothermia and received sedatio...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Stop muscle blockers"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022433,
      "question_number": "76",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "In a patient with liver failure, what will you see on EEG?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022434,
      "question_number": "1",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with confusion and recurrent seizures two days after hemodialysis, with normal i...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Water influx inside cells causing edema"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022435,
      "question_number": "9",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient with SAH presents with low sodium levels and high urine osmolarity. The patient is hypoten...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. IV fluid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7611940298507462,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7107344632768362,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022436,
      "question_number": "141",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is the most important predictor of outcome in cardiac arrest?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Time to defibrillation"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022437,
      "question_number": "144",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A 29-year-old male is found unconscious on the street. What do you expect as the mechanism of injury...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Trauma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8037383177570093,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6430973669100156,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022438,
      "question_number": "150",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is considered a poor prognosis in burst suppression?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022439,
      "question_number": "159",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario, what is the diagnosis based on the EEG findings?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Nonconvulsive status",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6267281105990783,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.49608114338404796,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022440,
      "question_number": "148",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient with renal failure missed one dialysis session. What would you expect to see on EEG?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Triphasic waves",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6789667896678967,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6418933390447633,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022441,
      "question_number": "511",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is a common side effect of hypertonic saline administration?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Hypernatremia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6597938144329897,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7190906982138715,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022442,
      "question_number": "492",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is a potential risk associated with the use of mannitol in patients?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "D. Volume overload",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6575342465753424,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.34762456546929316,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022443,
      "question_number": "79",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q79. A 67-year-old female experiences recurrent episodes of headache, nausea, and vomiting shortly a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Dialysis disequilibrium syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022444,
      "question_number": "169",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is the most important predictor of outcome in cardiac arrest?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Bilateral SSEP"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022445,
      "question_number": "12",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Cardiac arrest in a smoker patient complicated with hypotension and intubation. After 1 month, the p...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Vasospasm"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022446,
      "question_number": "62",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of post-subarachnoid hemorrhage (SAH) and hyponatremia, what is the recommended t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. 3% hypertonic saline",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7023411371237458,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.25218784666584493,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022447,
      "question_number": "151",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient with a history of sick sinus syndrome had a pacemaker implanted and subsequently ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. EEG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9153605015673981,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6729459498623388,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022448,
      "question_number": "161",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "In a sedated patient, which diagnostic test is least likely to provide useful information?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Brain death assessment",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7719298245614035,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6120417344692256,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022449,
      "question_number": "50",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "An approximately 70-year-old male patient post-CABG 2 days ago is extubated, awake but not following...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. EEG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8208955223880597,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7548454688318491,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022450,
      "question_number": "171",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient was in the ICU for 33 days. On the 3rd day, he has a persistent sleep-wake cycle. What is ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Vegetative"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022451,
      "question_number": "93",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A case of intracerebral hemorrhage (ICH) with a 6 mm midline shift is presented. What is an appropri...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Surgical intervention"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022452,
      "question_number": "170",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Which test is used to assess the blood-brain barrier (BBB) in traumatic brain injury (TBI)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. S100",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6394052044609665,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.010238408658768466,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022453,
      "question_number": "61",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q61. What is assessed to evaluate the blood-brain barrier (BBB) in traumatic brain injury (TBI)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. S100",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6498194945848376,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5704175513092711,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022454,
      "question_number": "75",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "In a case of intracerebral hemorrhage (ICH) in the basal ganglia, what is the target blood pressure?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. 140/90",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8067226890756303,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.04019862851737999,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022455,
      "question_number": "97",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A brain CT picture shows coup and contrecoup injury. What is the most likely cause?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Coup-contrecoup injury"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022456,
      "question_number": "8",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q8. In a patient with dialysis, what is the pathophysiology behind the disequilibrium syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022457,
      "question_number": "6",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A female patient with high blood pressure (180/??) presents with seizures and confusion. MRI shows b...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Posterior reversible encephalopathy syndrome (PRES)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022458,
      "question_number": "30",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old male was found unconscious on the street. What do you expect as the mechanism of injur...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Trauma"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022459,
      "question_number": "2",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with visual symptoms, confusion, and is taking immunosuppressants for renal tran...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Failure of autoregulation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7216035634743875,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7050322580645161,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022460,
      "question_number": "17",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient has an MRI showing tonsillar herniation. What is the next best step in management?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Send to neurosurgery",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6451612903225806,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7768969422423556,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022461,
      "question_number": "42",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q42. A patient with intracerebral hemorrhage (ICH) two days later has a blood pressure of 170/90 and...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Labetalol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7955056179775281,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.25155004428697963,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022462,
      "question_number": "76",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient who was arrested by police presents with encephalopathy and has a halitosis odor. What tre...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thiamine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8311688311688312,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.404862773991527,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022463,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "An elderly man has a 1-month history of right-sided weakness and confusion. A brain CT shows a cresc...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Bridging veins rupture",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7227272727272728,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6935308641975308,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022464,
      "question_number": "345",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient had cerebellar intracerebral hemorrhage (ICH) near the 4th ventricle with dilated lateral ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Insert EVD and release high ICP",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5950413223140496,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3563643256563359,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022465,
      "question_number": "499",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient who suffered a cardiac arrest is not waking up. What is the next best step in man...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. EEG"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022466,
      "question_number": "126",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with subarachnoid hemorrhage and hyponatremia (serum sodium 129), with a blood pr...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Cerebral salt wasting (CSW) causing hypovolemic hyponatremia with hypotension",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5689149560117303,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6861528756177058,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022467,
      "question_number": "85",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Which type of brain herniation is commonly associated with a fixed dilated pupil?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Uncal herniation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6274509803921569,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.565677966101695,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022468,
      "question_number": "69",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q69. In a case scenario about cerebellar hemorrhage, what is the next step in management?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Neurosurgery consultation for evacuation"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022469,
      "question_number": "62",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient with acute ischemic stroke received intravenous tPA and subsequently developed difficulty ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Antihistamine, Steroid"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022470,
      "question_number": "254",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "What EEG finding is associated with poor prognosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Non-reactive continuous alpha.",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5347593582887701,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6606940777065259,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022471,
      "question_number": "95",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient with subarachnoid hemorrhage (SAH) presents with hyponatremia. What should you do?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022472,
      "question_number": "327",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "In a case of trauma, which biomarker is most reliable for detecting disrupted blood-brain barrier (B...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. S100\u03b2",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7722007722007722,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7647124761798004,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022473,
      "question_number": "174",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "An EEG shows a burst suppression pattern. What is the most likely status of the patient?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Brain dead",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6991869918699187,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6230849947534103,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022474,
      "question_number": "19",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient who is status post cardiac arrest and has been discharged from the hospital returns to the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lance Adams Syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8187633262260128,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4778430325680726,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022475,
      "question_number": "491",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "An elderly male with left-sided weakness and dysarthria, who is on dabigatran, underwent thrombectom...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Idarucizumab"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022476,
      "question_number": "195",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with acute confusion and is found to have elevated blood levels of urea. What is ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Uremic encephalopathy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022477,
      "question_number": "179",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Hypertonic saline is contraindicated in which of the following patient populations?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Patients with end-stage kidney disease"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022478,
      "question_number": "460",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a months-long headache, papilledema, and MRI demonstrating hydrocephalus wit...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. HIV antibody test"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022479,
      "question_number": "392",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A 56-year-old male patient is found in his house with decreased level of consciousness. He was last ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Admit to ICU for close monitoring and supportive care"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022480,
      "question_number": "43",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A delirious patient presents. What is your next step?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022481,
      "question_number": "51",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A victim of a road traffic accident was awake for 2 hours, then the right eye pupil became fixed and...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Epidural hematoma (EDH)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7123287671232876,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5968457368161656,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022482,
      "question_number": "42",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "For the same patient, what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Osmotic therapy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5869565217391305,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6139254149601208,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022483,
      "question_number": "356",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A young lady with SLE nephritis on dialysis presents with seizures and confusion. MRI shows findings...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Posterior Reversible Encephalopathy Syndrome (PRES)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022484,
      "question_number": "2",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A brain CT shows a coup contrecoup injury with left frontal and right temporal bleed. What is the mo...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Trauma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7596439169139466,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7567797210224456,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022485,
      "question_number": "178",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is the benefit of using mannitol over hypertonic saline in the management of increased intracra...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Faster onset of action",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6588921282798834,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.553711387736284,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022486,
      "question_number": "146",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A mother receiving antiepileptic drugs has an infant who developed intraventricular hemorrhage (IVH)...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Phenytoin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022487,
      "question_number": "337",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A pregnant patient presents with recurrent vomiting. What should be administered?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thiamine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7022222222222222,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.41288156928563935,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022488,
      "question_number": "71",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Pregnant lady came with confusion and had a history of increased vomiting; she has no ophthalmology ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thiamine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7753846153846153,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6459533951390629,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022489,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q41. An alcoholic patient was admitted after a post-traumatic seizure and delirium; he was started o...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Ammonia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022490,
      "question_number": "196",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient who has recently delivered vaginally and is experiencing eclampsia presents with progressi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Magnesium level",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8070175438596491,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.32976984027166395,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022491,
      "question_number": "120",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient developed cognitive impairment and ataxia. MRI showed high signals in the mammillary bodie...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thiamine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8411214953271028,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7960747663551402,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022492,
      "question_number": "212",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A pregnant lady came with confusion and had a history of increased vomiting; she has no ophthalmolog...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thiamine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7781155015197568,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4436406295825594,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022493,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient was on warfarin and developed intracerebral hemorrhage (ICH). Which of the following has t...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Prothrombin Complex Concentrate (PCC)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7340425531914894,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3257488479262673,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022494,
      "question_number": "75",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "An alcoholic patient came with post-traumatic seizure and delirium. He was on Keppra and Depakin, th...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Ammonia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8336933045356372,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7494297816878462,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022495,
      "question_number": "90",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is the best imaging modality for diffuse axonal injury?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. MRI with diffusion-weighted imaging (DWI)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5462962962962963,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7321286910533275,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022496,
      "question_number": "79",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with acute inattentiveness. Laboratory tests including liver function tests, elec...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Systemic infection"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022497,
      "question_number": "154",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q154. A patient presented to the emergency room with meningitis and no papilledema, what is the appr...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Perform LP without CT"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022498,
      "question_number": "19",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q19. What is the management of hyponatremia due to cerebral salt wasting syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Hypertonic saline",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6504065040650406,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6890335503254882,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022499,
      "question_number": "26",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A 60-year-old male presented to the ER with a 2-day history of unilateral weakness and dysarthria. O...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. IV labetalol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.850909090909091,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6210643633324046,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022500,
      "question_number": "13",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient came after head trauma and was fine initially. After one hour, he started to have a decrea...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Epidural hematoma (EDH)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7405764966740577,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4219440353460972,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022501,
      "question_number": "289",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient is intubated with intact level of consciousness but is only able to move his extr...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. NCS with RNS",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8305084745762712,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.48512258985955725,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022502,
      "question_number": "267",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient on sedation has EEG findings suggestive of bilateral generalized slowing. What is the next...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Stop sedation"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022503,
      "question_number": "257",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A male elderly patient with liver disease and hypertension presents with decreased and fluctuating l...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Hepatic encephalopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.826797385620915,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6821267965787849,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022504,
      "question_number": "72",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient known to have congenital heart disease presents with headache, fever, and hemiparesis. Wha...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. CT without contrast"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022505,
      "question_number": "255",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "In the assessment of brain death, which of the following is a critical step?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Stop sedation"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022506,
      "question_number": "12",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A 6-year-old female has recurrent episodes of headache, nausea, and vomiting that occur shortly afte...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Water influx into brain parenchyma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7357293868921776,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.782307311437531,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022507,
      "question_number": "260",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is a mechanism by which hypertonic saline reduces intracranial pressure?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. It increases the osmotic gradient across the blood-brain barrier."
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022508,
      "question_number": "292",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "In a case of warfarin-related intracerebral hemorrhage (ICH) with an INR of 3, what will you give fo...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "B. Fresh frozen plasma (FFP)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6923076923076923,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4912574850299401,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022509,
      "question_number": "205",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "A 65-year-old man presents with an abrupt severe headache and drowsiness. His Glasgow Coma Scale sco...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. External ventricular drainage",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8490566037735849,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7608872058425751,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022510,
      "question_number": "75",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q75. A pregnant lady had a headache, and her CT showed an intracranial hemorrhage (ICH). What is the...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Supportive care and blood pressure control",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6481481481481481,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.15272727272727274,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022511,
      "question_number": "2",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q2. A brain CT shows a coup-contrecoup injury with left frontal and right temporal bleed. What is th...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Trauma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7529411764705882,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.04038526529232849,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022512,
      "question_number": "58",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "In a patient with ICH on CT brain and an International Normalized Ratio (INR) of 3.2, which treatmen...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. PCC",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8042704626334519,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6582024724356833,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022513,
      "question_number": "192",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q192. What is the primary benefit of administering anticonvulsants during the first week after traum...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Decrease early seizures"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022514,
      "question_number": "186",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following occurs within an hour of IV infusion of mannitol?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022515,
      "question_number": "25",
      "subspecialty": "Critical Care Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q25. In a similar scenario to the previous one, what is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Acute confusional state"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022516,
      "question_number": "32",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "To differentiate between frontotemporal dementia (FTD) and Alzheimer's disease (AD), which imaging m...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. PET scan"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022517,
      "question_number": "56",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with visual hallucinations and fluctuating levels of consciousness, with symptoms...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Lewy body disease"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022518,
      "question_number": "55",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A 70-year-old male presents with cognitive decline, ataxia, and a startle response. What is the like...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.662613981762918,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6151297625621204,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022519,
      "question_number": "45",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A 70-year-old male presented with a shuffling gait, freezing, and urinary incontinence. Upon examina...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Normal Pressure Hydrocephalus"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022520,
      "question_number": "57",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with hyperphagia, personality changes, and memory loss. What is the likely diagno...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Frontotemporal dementia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6493506493506493,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6049966239027684,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022521,
      "question_number": "68",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient with increasing forgetfulness had to change his bank ATM card because he misplaced it. Thi...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Dementia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022522,
      "question_number": "61",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Dementia with Lewy Bodies (DLB)",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022523,
      "question_number": "71",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of Mild Cognitive Impairment (MCI), what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Cognitive training and lifestyle modification"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022524,
      "question_number": "80",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "For the same patient, what treatment would you recommend?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Rivastigmine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6043956043956044,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6532825074121135,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022525,
      "question_number": "52",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "In the context of Dementia with Lewy Bodies (DLB), which medication is used for cognitive symptoms?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Rivastigmine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7480314960629921,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6181153184165232,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022526,
      "question_number": "31",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Korsakoff dementia is characterized by impairment of which type of memory?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Episodic memory",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6403508771929824,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.637203166226913,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022527,
      "question_number": "48",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "In the case of Gerstmann syndrome, what is the associated language deficit?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Anomic aphasia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022528,
      "question_number": "64",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "This is a 70-year-old female with a history of short-term memory impairment, long-term memory not af...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Alzheimer's Disease (AD)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022529,
      "question_number": "67",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Q67. The second most common neurodegenerative dementia is:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "D. Vascular Dementia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.509090909090909,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7782672540381792,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022530,
      "question_number": "83",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient came with behavioral changes; what is the gene defect?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. TDP-43",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7560975609756098,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7375950948109459,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022531,
      "question_number": "42",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Q42. (Source: Part I 2022mcqs.txt) What is the most common memory type affected in Korsakoff's encep...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Episodic memory",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7167235494880546,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4720928396621141,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022532,
      "question_number": "65",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A 56-year-old female presents with behavioral changes and personality alterations. She starts talkin...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Frontotemporal dementia (FTD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.841642228739003,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.795978581575784,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022533,
      "question_number": "89",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "For the same patient, what treatment would you recommend?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Rivastigmine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6043956043956044,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.784973544973545,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022534,
      "question_number": "79",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Q79. What is the best test to check cognitive impairment in a patient with MCI?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. MOCA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7264150943396226,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6246200607902735,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022535,
      "question_number": "66",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A 58-year-old female presents with changes in behavior, memory issues, and visual hallucinations. MR...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Dementia with Lewy bodies (DLB)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022536,
      "question_number": "59",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Q59. A 60-year-old university professor started to forget things and frequently loses his bank cards...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Mild cognitive impairment.",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7765151515151515,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2048481619605754,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022537,
      "question_number": "47",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Q47. Apathy is more commonly seen in which of the following conditions?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Frontotemporal dementia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5542168674698795,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7212705615428248,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022538,
      "question_number": "81",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Typical clinical history is suggestive of Lewy Body Dementia (LBD); PET showed a posterior corpus ca...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lewy Body Dementia (clear from the history)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7368421052631579,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7586814292903875,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022539,
      "question_number": "30",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A 77-year-old man with a 3-year history of personality changes and cognitive impairment reports seei...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Dementia with Lewy bodies (DLB)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8396501457725948,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7399113975030205,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022540,
      "question_number": "44",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Q44. A 62-year-old male exhibits inappropriate behavior, impaired social functioning, and a tendency...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Frontotemporal Dementia (FTD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8043818466353677,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6435678128818293,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022541,
      "question_number": "58",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient with cognitive decline also presents with urinary incontinence and a magnetic gait. What i...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Normal pressure hydrocephalus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7058823529411765,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.650804289544236,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022542,
      "question_number": "72",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with the classic triad of normal pressure hydrocephalus (gait disturbance, cognit...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. None of the above",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8814229249011858,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6282624030096402,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022543,
      "question_number": "38",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A 67-year-old male is brought to the clinic because of cognitive decline and multiple neurological s...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Creutzfeldt-Jakob Disease (CJD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8796680497925311,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.12295180002392059,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022544,
      "question_number": "78",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Pathology showed Lewy bodies. What is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lewy body dementia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5025125628140703,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4982279425480321,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022545,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Apathy is more commonly seen in which condition?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022546,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Q7. The nonfluent/agrammatic variant of primary progressive aphasia (nfvPPA) is primarily associated...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Left inferior frontal gyrus (Broca area)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.704,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6316013176070556,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022547,
      "question_number": "53",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "In a patient with normal semantic and language function, what is the pathology associated with behav...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. TDP-43"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022548,
      "question_number": "63",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient exhibits word-finding difficulties and behavioral changes. What is the most likely diagnos...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Frontotemporal dementia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6847457627118644,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6922487875436059,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022549,
      "question_number": "84",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient with a history of neuropsychiatric symptoms and dementia for more than 5 years had PrPSc. ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Familial CJD"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022550,
      "question_number": "82",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "In an Alzheimer patient, what are the expected cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) results?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Low Amyloid \u03b2, High Tau",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5789473684210527,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6041937816341287,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022551,
      "question_number": "86",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Q86. What helps differentiate Alzheimer's disease from frontotemporal dementia?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anterograde memory loss",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5992217898832685,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6458247634718223,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022552,
      "question_number": "85",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with one year of progressive apathy and memory loss. What is the most likely diag...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Alzheimer\u2019s disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6819672131147541,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.706476897689769,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022553,
      "question_number": "87",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Cholinesterase inhibitors are most useful for which condition?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Apathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7011494252873564,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5544444444444444,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022554,
      "question_number": "88",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "An elderly man has been acting out his dreams, kicking his wife, and experiencing vivid visual hallu...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lewy body dementia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7682119205298014,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4558657274545613,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022555,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient comes with progressive dementia over the last 6 months, exhibiting startle and sensory myo...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Prion disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7900677200902935,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.07136583223539746,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022556,
      "question_number": "91",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Q91. Typical history of Lewy Body Dementia (LBD), PET showed posterior corpus callosum abnormality (...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lewy Body Dementia (clear from the history)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6059322033898306,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7990906953045387,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022557,
      "question_number": "73",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario of MCI, what is the conversion rate of cognitive impairment to dementia?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. 10 - 20%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022558,
      "question_number": "64",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Q64. The same imaging findings as previous but with agrammatic aphasia are present. What is the diag...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Frontotemporal dementia (FTD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6821192052980133,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6731141199226306,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022559,
      "question_number": "55",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient exhibits changes in eating habits towards sweet foods. Imaging shows changes consistent wi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Frontotemporal dementia (FTD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7587939698492462,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7434425505608054,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022560,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Which disorder most commonly presents with apathy?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022561,
      "question_number": "54",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "In the Mini-Mental State Examination (MMSE), which component carries the highest weight?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Orientation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6942148760330579,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7462952646239555,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022562,
      "question_number": "91",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A male patient was brought to the hospital by his wife for forgetfulness issues. He has difficulty w...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Primary progressive aphasia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022563,
      "question_number": "91",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A male patient was brought to the hospital by his wife for forgetfulness issues. He has difficulty w...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Primary progressive aphasia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.862453531598513,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.06323669958585537,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022564,
      "question_number": "113",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A 77-year-old man came with his wife to the clinic with a 3-year history of personality changes and ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lewy body dementia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8921933085501859,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5775422065174716,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022565,
      "question_number": "64",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "In a patient with mild cognitive impairment who is still independent, what is the most appropriate m...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Lifestyle modification"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022566,
      "question_number": "55",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient exhibits changes in eating habits towards sweet foods. Imaging shows changes consistent wi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Frontotemporal dementia (FTD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7587939698492462,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.048091078614191776,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022567,
      "question_number": "64",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "The same imaging findings as previous but with agrammatic aphasia are present. What is the diagnosis...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Frontotemporal dementia (FTD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6644295302013423,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.08022420739183744,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022568,
      "question_number": "113",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A 77-year-old man came with his wife to the clinic with a 3-year history of personality changes and ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lewy body dementia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8921933085501859,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.06396544631838749,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022569,
      "question_number": "45",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Alzheimer\u2019s Dementia, what is the most common symptom observed?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Apathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.728110599078341,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6392137347598905,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022570,
      "question_number": "128",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Q128. What is the pathology associated with ALS-FTD?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. TDP-43"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022571,
      "question_number": "43",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with apathy and cerebral atrophy, along with changes in eating habits. Imaging fr...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Frontotemporal dementia (FTD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8296795952782462,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.664241836404785,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022572,
      "question_number": "243",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "What is the second most common cause of dementia?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022573,
      "question_number": "85",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "In Alzheimer\u2019s dementia, which gene mutation is related to earlier onset?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. APP",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7932960893854749,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5991219963031423,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022574,
      "question_number": "44",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "In the context of primary progressive aphasia, which of the following is true regarding the semantic...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. It is associated with impairments of object naming and word comprehension",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5330188679245284,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7234220659635024,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022575,
      "question_number": "331",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Which of the following suggests Alzheimer Disease (AD) rather than Lewy Body Dementia (LBD)?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Anterograde memory loss",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.58,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6263899184581171,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022576,
      "question_number": "322",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "An Alzheimer\u2019s patient presents with depression symptoms (sadness, insomnia) and agitation. What med...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Cipralex",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.392098238120662,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022577,
      "question_number": "66",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Alzheimer\u2019s dementia is most commonly related to which gene mutation?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. APOE",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7861271676300579,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.46264564770390676,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022578,
      "question_number": "288",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "What clinical features help to distinguish Dementia with Lewy Bodies (DLB) from Alzheimer Disease (A...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Fluctuations in cognitive function with varying levels of alertness and attention"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022579,
      "question_number": "292",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "What is the LBD PET finding associated with?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022580,
      "question_number": "399",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "In the context of Alzheimer's Disease (AD), which medication is considered first-line for hallucinat...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Quetiapine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7931034482758621,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5928817451205511,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022581,
      "question_number": "227",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Rivastigmine is the only cholinesterase inhibitor FDA approved for use in which condition?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Parkinson disease dementia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6402877697841727,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3737846597047173,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022582,
      "question_number": "281",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A 55-year-old man presents with a 3-month history of rapidly progressive behavioral changes, dementi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease (CJD)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022583,
      "question_number": "103",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "An Alzheimer patient presents with CSF results showing low amyloid beta and high tau levels. What do...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Alzheimer disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7210031347962382,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7858950859736406,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022584,
      "question_number": "5",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Q5. A picture of ribboning is presented. What is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Prion disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5925925925925926,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.554673299531235,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022585,
      "question_number": "142",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient with progressive myoclonus and dementia is suspected to have which condition?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Unverricht-Lundborg disease"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022586,
      "question_number": "119",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "What is the best test to check cognitive impairment with Mild Cognitive Impairment (MCI)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. MOCA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7478260869565218,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4495307096986662,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022587,
      "question_number": "109",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson\u2019s disease presents with hallucinations and memory problems. What medication...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Clozapine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7931034482758621,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.59227921734532,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022588,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of a Parkinson's disease patient presenting with hallucinations and memory proble...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Rivastigmine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022589,
      "question_number": "228",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A Parkinson\u2019s patient presents with worsening visual hallucinations and progressive memory loss. Wha...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Rivastigmine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8170731707317073,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5600501724678583,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022590,
      "question_number": "325",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A husband reported that his wife started to have gait instability that worsened over 5 years, becomi...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Familial Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease (CJD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7162426614481409,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.43496946392218955,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022591,
      "question_number": "74",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "An 80-year-old patient presents with concerns about his memory function, as he is forgetting names a...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Mild cognitive impairment (MCI)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022592,
      "question_number": "215",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "An 80-year-old patient presents with concerns about his memory function, as he is forgetting names o...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Normal aging"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022593,
      "question_number": "114",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A 63-year-old male has a 4-year history of Parkinson's Disease with visual hallucinations. What is t...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Dementia with Lewy Bodies",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6776859504132231,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6879426423013028,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022594,
      "question_number": "140",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "What is the second most common type of neurodegenerative dementia?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Lewy Body Dementia (LBD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5462184873949579,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.575273338940286,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022595,
      "question_number": "139",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is a common side effect of cholinesterase inhibitors in individuals with park...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Nausea",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.779783393501805,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.727018664537379,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022596,
      "question_number": "66",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "What is the mechanism of action of Donepezil?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022597,
      "question_number": "184",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient with frontotemporal dementia (FTD) shows frontal and temporal atrophy on MRI. What is the ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Frontotemporal dementia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022598,
      "question_number": "207",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient with dementia presents with insomnia and agitation. What medication would you prescribe?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Trazodone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.768,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5411669038422443,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022599,
      "question_number": "38",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient presented to the neurology clinic with complaints of progressive memory problems....",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Rivastigmine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.897822445561139,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7516194331983805,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022600,
      "question_number": "20",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with young-onset familial Alzheimer\u2019s disease and a family history of the conditi...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. PSEN1",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.896358543417367,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6743284778832019,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022601,
      "question_number": "126",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A young patient presents with Alzheimer\u2019s disease with a family history of autosomal dominant inheri...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Presenilin 1",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8812785388127854,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3609358569926393,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022602,
      "question_number": "119",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "In a scenario about DLB, if a patient developed hallucinations and psychiatric symptoms, which treat...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Quetiapine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7931034482758621,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6309242225142356,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022603,
      "question_number": "40",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Which type of pathology is most commonly associated with the semantic variant of primary progressive...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. FTLD\u2013TDP\u201343 type C pathology",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6649076517150396,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.33005743458838543,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022604,
      "question_number": "43",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A young patient with a history of memory loss has a family history of similar issues. Which gene is ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. APP",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8686131386861314,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6244040977786793,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022605,
      "question_number": "101",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Q101. In the context of Lewy body dementia, which of the following behavioral symptoms is commonly o...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Psychosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7924528301886793,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6470478325859492,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022606,
      "question_number": "225",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "What is the most likely diagnosis for a patient with a PET scan showing low FDG uptake in the pariet...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Alzheimer's Disease (AD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7285067873303167,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.602615122228539,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022607,
      "question_number": "73",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Which gene is related to early onset Alzheimer\u2019s disease (AD)?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Presenilin 1",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6982248520710059,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5711416136591898,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022608,
      "question_number": "111",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "What is the drug that showed evidence to treat visual hallucinations in dementia with Lewy bodies (D...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "C. Donepezil",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7680608365019012,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.730723606168446,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022609,
      "question_number": "127",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Which of the following conditions is characterized by 3-repeat tau and ubiquitin?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. FTD-pick",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7407407407407407,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7680239935402007,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022610,
      "question_number": "80",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Which of the following genes is commonly linked to Alzheimer's disease?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. APOE4",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7909604519774012,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.47190439867785405,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022611,
      "question_number": "92",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Which of the following genes is associated with familial Alzheimer\u2019s disease?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. APP",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7562189054726368,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.0509981546720349,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022612,
      "question_number": "46",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Which of the following most accurately summarizes the current situation with respect to the use of c...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Not proven to be effective in delaying or preventing the development of dementia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.639686684073107,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.666473709599614,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022613,
      "question_number": "39",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A young man with a family history of early onset Alzheimer disease. Which of the following genes inc...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Apolipoprotein E",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8571428571428571,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6168089702705483,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022614,
      "question_number": "49",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient with dementia has insomnia and agitation. What medication would you prescribe?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Trazodone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7445887445887446,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6741113289574632,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022615,
      "question_number": "47",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "An individual with mild cognitive impairment is more likely to progress to dementia or Alzheimer dis...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Has positive amyloid imaging on PET scan."
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022616,
      "question_number": "105",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A patient came with behavioral changes; what is the gene defect?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Progranulin/Ch17 (TDP-43)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022617,
      "question_number": "63",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A male patient presents with recent behavioral changes, and MRI shows frontal and temporal atrophy. ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Frontotemporal dementia (FTD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.721763085399449,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6838223504890172,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022618,
      "question_number": "48",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Cognitive symptoms in Lewy body dementia are treated with which of the following medications?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Cholinesterase inhibitors",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6715328467153284,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6021382206949217,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022619,
      "question_number": "59",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Q59. A patient with a history of memory changes and forgetfulness has cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) anal...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Alzheimer\u2019s disease"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022620,
      "question_number": "69",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "An elderly male was brought in by his family with urinary incontinence for years and cognitive decli...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Refer for elective shunt"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022621,
      "question_number": "88",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Declarative memory with remembering past experiences is referred to as:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Episodic memory",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6306306306306306,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.38002109097881315,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022622,
      "question_number": "164",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A 56-year-old male with a history of memory loss for 24 hours and asking the same question repeatedl...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. MRI",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8526645768025078,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7491525423728813,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022623,
      "question_number": "217",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Q217. Cognitive fluctuation is more common in which of the following conditions?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Dementia with Lewy Bodies (DLB)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5756457564575646,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5510373443983403,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022624,
      "question_number": "256",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "What is the mechanism of action of donepezil?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022625,
      "question_number": "42",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "In a case of transient global amnesia (TGA) lasting 4 hours, with the patient confused, repeating qu...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Brain CT & CTA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022626,
      "question_number": "48",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Fatigue during the daytime and increased sleepiness in a patient with Alzheimer\u2019s disease is due to ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Suprachiasmatic nucleus degeneration",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6321243523316062,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7118046816008055,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022627,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Q41. What is the commonest pathological change in neurodegenerative diseases?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Neurofibrillary tangles",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6276150627615062,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.798233826070263,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022628,
      "question_number": "198",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "A 52-year-old woman presents with behavioral changes over the course of 2 years. Her concentration i...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Frontotemporal dementia (FTD)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022629,
      "question_number": "51",
      "subspecialty": "Dementia",
      "question_text": "Q51. A case scenario of a patient with urinary urgency, gait problems, and memory problems, with MRI...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Normal Pressure Hydrocephalus (NPH)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.759825327510917,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.27630942007938813,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022082,
      "question_number": "45",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Typical juvenile myoclonic epilepsy (JME) patient on topiramate is well controlled; he wants to stop...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lifelong treatment",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6123348017621145,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5766174801362088,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022083,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the 2-year recurrence rate of seizures after the first seizure attack?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. 30%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022084,
      "question_number": "63",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q63. A patient with mesial temporal sclerosis\u2013related seizures is receiving topiramate 200 mg BID an...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Refer to surgery",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7584745762711864,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.46303226458986546,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022085,
      "question_number": "9",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a case of catamenial seizures, what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Perimenstrual progesterone supplementation"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022086,
      "question_number": "225",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q225. An 18-year-old female patient with seizures is found dead in bed after taking only one AED. Wh...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. SUDEP risk is highest in patients with uncontrolled generalized tonic-clonic seizures",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5190082644628099,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7381983313971908,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022087,
      "question_number": "250",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Hypsarrhythmia with tuberous sclerosis (TS), what is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Vigabatrin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022088,
      "question_number": "114",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of dyscognitive auras (Temporal lobe epilepsy), what imaging is typically used for dia...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. MRI",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8340080971659919,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4014534519483774,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022089,
      "question_number": "268",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A medical patient with diabetes mellitus, hypertension, hyperlipidemia, osteoporosis, and on warfari...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lamictal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8194842406876791,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7101760412194075,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022090,
      "question_number": "77",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 28-year-old woman with well-controlled epilepsy on lamotrigine therapy wishes to start combined or...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Double the lamotrigine dose"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022091,
      "question_number": "156",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q156. Which of the following treatments is commonly used for Landau-Kleffner syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Valproic acid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.717948717948718,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7485471419897649,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022092,
      "question_number": "215",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the effect of adding a third antiepileptic drug (AED) on seizure control?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. 5%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022093,
      "question_number": "161",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Patient with MTS seizure; EEG showed left temporal discharges. What symptoms does he have?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Left automatism",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6877470355731226,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5479288934251935,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022094,
      "question_number": "259",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with an aura of fear and seizure localization. Which area of the brain is most li...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Temporal lobe"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022095,
      "question_number": "145",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 3-year-old boy presented with developmental delay and seizures consisting of tonic seizures, drop ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Epileptiform discharges less than 2 Hz",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7382297551789078,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7331730769230769,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022096,
      "question_number": "221",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 2-year-old child with developmental delay presents with tonic-clonic seizures and frequent \u201cdrop\u201d ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "C. Spike-and-wave complexes at 4-6 Hz",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6988505747126437,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.26127406641684975,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022097,
      "question_number": "72",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the most common cause of sudden unexpected death in epilepsy?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Uncontrolled seizures",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6153846153846154,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6706507304116865,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022098,
      "question_number": "91",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient has aphasia and multiple seizure types. What is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Landau Kleffner Syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022099,
      "question_number": "79",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old female patient diagnosed with epilepsy is currently on Lacosamide 200 mg BID and Levet...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Video EEG"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022100,
      "question_number": "189",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with a first-time seizure, normal physical examination, and normal EEG, regarding his risk...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022101,
      "question_number": "165",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Patient with typical symptoms of Juvenile Myoclonic Epilepsy (JME), what is a characteristic feature...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Seizure induced by photic stimulation"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022102,
      "question_number": "252",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q252. A patient exhibits seizure semiology characterized by flexion in one limb with extension of th...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. SMA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8504672897196262,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6544297082228117,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022103,
      "question_number": "148",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In an elderly patient with renal stones, heart failure, atrial fibrillation, and post-stroke seizure...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lamictal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8402366863905325,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7104799034623596,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022104,
      "question_number": "70",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A child has had two seizures, both occurring while he was on a train, each associated with nausea an...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Occipital seizure",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7543859649122807,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6815569771224114,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022105,
      "question_number": "29",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of a 30-year-old female patient with bizarre nocturnal movements, what is the lik...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Dorsomedial (SMA)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022106,
      "question_number": "265",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the least medication to interact with oral contraceptive pills (OCP)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Keppra"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022107,
      "question_number": "199",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which EEG finding has the best prognostic value in a 9-year-old boy who has frequent staring spells,...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Normal background activity",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.712166172106825,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4086423953725757,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022108,
      "question_number": "255",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q255. A scenario about a child who has an attack of stereotypical hyperkinetic behavior occurring du...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Autosomal dominant frontal lobe epilepsy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022109,
      "question_number": "136",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q136. Multiple seizure types refractory to AEDs",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022110,
      "question_number": "179",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A child with recurrent staring episodes, myoclonus, and rare generalized tonic-clonic seizures (GTCs...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Oxcarbazepine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022111,
      "question_number": "181",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A lady with diabetes mellitus on multiple anti-diabetic medications, hypertension, and osteoporosis ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Lamotrigine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8253968253968254,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.794743608055992,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022112,
      "question_number": "151",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of uncontrolled epilepsy on 2 AEDs, what is the next step?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Refer to surgery",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5833333333333334,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6863560732113144,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022113,
      "question_number": "280",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A pregnant lady post tumor resection on oral contraceptive pills (OCP) and known to have seizures. W...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Levetiracetam",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8624229979466119,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7451084786370291,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022114,
      "question_number": "2",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "An elderly woman with diabetes mellitus, hypertension, and atrial fibrillation had an episode of syn...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Rhythmic clonus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9028697571743929,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.40253909273881405,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022115,
      "question_number": "75",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a patient with seizures that include myoclonic jerks, which medication is appropriate to prescrib...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Valproic acid (VPA)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022116,
      "question_number": "27",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q27. A young female epileptic patient on Topamax has decreased concentration. What should she be swi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lamotrigine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7709090909090909,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6973037877960921,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022117,
      "question_number": "289",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q289. What factors favor seizures over syncope?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022118,
      "question_number": "201",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A young female with epilepsy on Topamax has worsened difficulty concentrating. Which choice is the b...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lamotrigine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7773851590106007,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5705604321404456,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022119,
      "question_number": "56",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A pregnant lady with epilepsy on valproic acid wants to change her medication. Which of the followin...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Lamotrigine (LTG)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7636363636363637,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5520953479430988,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022120,
      "question_number": "182",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Characteristic of temporal lobe epilepsy:",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022121,
      "question_number": "46",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the most common type of aura in mesial temporal lobe (MTL) seizures?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Epigastric rising sensation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6320346320346321,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7020555202373384,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022122,
      "question_number": "137",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q137. What\u2019s the EEG finding of Juvenile Myoclonic Epilepsy (JME)?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. 4-6 Hz poly spike and wave",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5367965367965368,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6876285630326183,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022123,
      "question_number": "11",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a case of catamenial seizures, which statement is true?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022124,
      "question_number": "218",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a pregnant patient with seizures, which statement is true?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022125,
      "question_number": "291",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a case of laryngeal spasm, what is the localization of the seizure?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Insula",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6634146341463415,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6799007444168734,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022126,
      "question_number": "200",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A young lady diagnosed with mesial temporal lobe epilepsy (MTLE) is on lamotrigine and carbamazepine...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Start epilepsy surgery workup",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8131868131868132,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.1931193986701359,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022127,
      "question_number": "59",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with drug-resistant seizures has an EEG showing multifocal epileptic spikes. Which surgica...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. VNS (Vagus Nerve Stimulation)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5198265179677819,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022128,
      "question_number": "28",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "The patient, an alcoholic with a known case of epilepsy on antiepileptic medication (ASM), came with...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Send for ammonia level"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022129,
      "question_number": "191",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 53-year-old male who presented with a first-time generalized tonic-clonic seizure, normal physical...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. 30%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022130,
      "question_number": "30",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a case of Mesial Temporal Lobe Epilepsy (MTLE), a patient is on the maximum dose of Keppra. What ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Tegretol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8280254777070064,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7944652055347945,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022131,
      "question_number": "177",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A child with continuous jerky movement of the right arm for a prolonged time developed mild weakness...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Rasmussen encephalitis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7835051546391752,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.39963751699139105,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022132,
      "question_number": "10",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 22-year-old woman with a history of epilepsy on topiramate is now complaining of difficulty in con...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Lamotrigine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.84688995215311,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5424473987229143,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022133,
      "question_number": "16",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient has a history of new-onset generalized tonic-clonic seizures (GTCs) and an EEG picture. Wh...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Valproic acid"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022134,
      "question_number": "222",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the effect of hyperventilation on EEG?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022135,
      "question_number": "256",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A video of a patient with bizarre movements during sleep is presented. What classification does this...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Focal motor with impaired awareness",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7371007371007371,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5969055374592834,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022136,
      "question_number": "196",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 23-year-old female is brought to the clinic by her husband, who states she has hyperactive jerky m...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Levetiracetam"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022137,
      "question_number": "131",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a focal aware seizure, which antiepileptic medication (ASM) is commonly used?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. LCM (Lacosamide)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6413502109704642,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6701220531683665,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022138,
      "question_number": "284",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q284. Patient with MTS seizure; EEG showed left temporal discharges; what symptoms does he have?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Left automatism",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7022900763358778,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3551971678631134,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022139,
      "question_number": "166",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A child is brought with a progressive difficulty in understanding language and partial aphasia. He h...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Landau-Kleffner syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8311688311688312,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7222680072523487,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022140,
      "question_number": "211",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a patient with a history of moderate head trauma from a motor vehicle accident, for how long does...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. 10 years"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022141,
      "question_number": "266",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q266. A young lady who underwent tumor resection presented with a staring spell and loss of awarenes...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Focal non-motor onset with impaired awareness",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6683168316831684,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5565178270160837,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022142,
      "question_number": "134",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Regarding mesial temporal sclerosis, which statement is true?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022143,
      "question_number": "25",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient came to the emergency room with multiple episodes of decreased level of consciousness. Wha...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Generalized tonic-clonic (GTC) seizure"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022144,
      "question_number": "13",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the percentage of juvenile myoclonic epilepsy (JME) patients that will be seizure-free witho...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. 15-30%",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8461538461538461,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4933659217877095,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022145,
      "question_number": "349",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with mesial temporal lobe (MTL) epilepsy on two AEDs came to the clinic. What is the reaso...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Non-compliance with medication"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022146,
      "question_number": "153",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q153. What is the mean age of onset for Landau-Kleffner syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. 5.5 years",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7078651685393258,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5016880486158002,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022147,
      "question_number": "26",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q26. A patient with a seizure scenario is asked about the best EEG predictor for good prognosis. Whi...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Normal background"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022148,
      "question_number": "11",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A young female epileptic patient on Topamax has decreased concentration. What should be switched to?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lamotrigine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.765625,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.33329236819466634,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022149,
      "question_number": "294",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q294. In early myoclonic encephalopathy with migrating myoclonus that then became more generalized, ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Burst suppression"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022150,
      "question_number": "82",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a case involving MRI findings consistent with Mesial Temporal Lobe Epilepsy (MTLE), what type of ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Cephalic"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022151,
      "question_number": "4",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old patient with seizures controlled on antiepileptic drugs (AED) developed facial redness...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "D. Valproic acid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8134556574923547,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.019249797607268148,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022152,
      "question_number": "185",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A female patient known to have complex partial seizures with generalized tonic-clonic (GTC) seizures...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Send for pre-surgical evaluation"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022153,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "An 18-year-old girl with mesial temporal lobe epilepsy (MTLE) is on lacosamide 200 mg twice daily, b...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Refer for surgical evaluation"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022154,
      "question_number": "202",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q202. A seizure described as early non-focal right head turning with right hand automatism. What is ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Right temporal lobe"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022155,
      "question_number": "167",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A young lady with epilepsy on lamotrigine wants to start oral contraceptive pills (OCP). What should...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. No effect by OCP, she can start"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022156,
      "question_number": "278",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q278. Which factors favor seizures over syncope?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Cyanosis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022157,
      "question_number": "271",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q271. Male patient has migraine and seizure; what medications will you give?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Valproic acid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6919431279620853,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7375853141915745,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022158,
      "question_number": "210",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A slow EEG is most commonly associated with which condition?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Lennox-Gastaut syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022159,
      "question_number": "269",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Patient with absence seizure; what is the medication that worsens the seizure?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Oxycarbazepine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022160,
      "question_number": "240",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a case of status epilepticus, when will the compensatory mechanisms fail?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. 30\u201360 min",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7628865979381443,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7599950488921896,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022161,
      "question_number": "142",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with Juvenile Myoclonic Epilepsy (JME) on a single AED has been seizure-free for the last ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. Order EEG to aid in the management",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7083333333333334,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.70632692722954,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022162,
      "question_number": "251",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the effect of phenytoin when taken with valproic acid?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022163,
      "question_number": "56",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient on three antiepileptic medications is not improving. What is the recommended next step?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Refer to surgery",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6462585034013606,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6454521347122779,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022164,
      "question_number": "147",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient who has mesial temporal lobe epilepsy (MTLE) and is on 2 antiepileptic drugs (AEDs) presen...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Send the patient for Video EEG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7020109689213894,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4759029874050172,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022165,
      "question_number": "192",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which antiepileptic drugs (AEDs) exacerbate myoclonus?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Phenobarbital"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022166,
      "question_number": "198",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A young male with nocturnal hyperkinetic movements at night, facial clonic spells, and profuse saliv...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Frontal operculum",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8519195612431444,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5846859238881247,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022167,
      "question_number": "19",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the risk of recurrence for febrile seizures in the future?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "C. Approximately 50%",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6074766355140186,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7618547221857349,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022168,
      "question_number": "226",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with epileptic spasms and EEG showing hypsarrhythmia. What is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Infantile spasms",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6813186813186813,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4889710412815773,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022169,
      "question_number": "107",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which area, if removed by surgery, will result in seizure freedom?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Epileptogenic zone"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022170,
      "question_number": "218",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A known case of epilepsy in a female patient on lamotrigine wants to start on oral contraceptive pil...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Double the lamotrigine dose"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022171,
      "question_number": "149",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Landau-Kleffner syndrome (LKS) is also known as:",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022172,
      "question_number": "8",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following antiepileptic drugs (AEDs) is known to worsen myoclonic seizures?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Carbamazepine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022173,
      "question_number": "184",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient experiences an episode of upraising gastric sensation followed by laryngeal constriction. ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Insular",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7909967845659164,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7216144450345194,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022174,
      "question_number": "20",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the next step in the management of a patient with refractory epilepsy?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Refer for surgical evaluation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5238095238095238,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.28865330114411675,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022175,
      "question_number": "246",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of juvenile myoclonic epilepsy (JME), what is a characteristic feature?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Photosensitivity",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6515151515151515,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7690605854322669,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022176,
      "question_number": "94",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Patient has focal seizure on treatment and he is well controlled. What is the favorable outcome in t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. One type seizure",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6376811594202898,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7825174825174825,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022177,
      "question_number": "100",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the AED that has the highest concentration in breast milk?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Levetiracetam",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6565656565656566,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.1338679827267119,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022178,
      "question_number": "294",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which cranial nerve is primarily responsible for the sense of smell?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Olfactory nerve (CN I)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5800865800865801,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7888714922317235,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022179,
      "question_number": "167",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which cranial nerve is primarily responsible for the sense of smell?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Olfactory nerve (CN I)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022180,
      "question_number": "152",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In the scenario of an elderly patient with comorbidities and polypharmacy who has had frequent seizu...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Levetiracetam",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8652482269503546,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6480470840021402,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022181,
      "question_number": "274",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is the most common cause of ischemic stroke?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Large artery atherosclerosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5454545454545454,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6967700807479813,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022182,
      "question_number": "386",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with brief, abrupt-onset nocturnal seizures lasting less than one minute, charact...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Frontal lobe",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8892307692307693,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7179415855354659,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022183,
      "question_number": "36",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A female patient with epilepsy is on two antiepileptic drugs (AEDs) but is still not controlled. She...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Not to interfere with pregnancy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.718562874251497,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5276296380347214,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022184,
      "question_number": "1",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of these is a characteristic of Lennox-Gastaut syndrome (LGS)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022185,
      "question_number": "248",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient experiences seizures characterized predominantly by a sensation of choking or laryngeal co...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Insula",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8509803921568627,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.795068928950159,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022186,
      "question_number": "264",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario, what should be done next based on the EEG findings indicating nonconvulsive st...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Give Keppra IV",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6896551724137931,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.788354898336414,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022187,
      "question_number": "170",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A three-month-old baby with early myoclonic encephalopathy had migrating myoclonic seizures that the...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Burst suppression"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022188,
      "question_number": "184",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which cranial nerve is primarily responsible for the sense of smell?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Olfactory nerve (CN I)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5800865800865801,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5768240343347639,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022189,
      "question_number": "140",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A pregnant lady on a low dose of levetiracetam is sleeping well and has good compliance, but is stil...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lamictal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8308605341246291,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5387492208601704,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022190,
      "question_number": "144",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient in the clinic has continuous facial jerks and hand jerks (partial continua). How should yo...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. IV phenytoin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022191,
      "question_number": "175",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A young man with a known case of epilepsy describes his seizure as starting with laryngeal constrict...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Insular"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022192,
      "question_number": "74",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a similar scenario, the patient experiences loss of awareness and sometimes tonic-clonic seizures...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Video EEG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7461368653421634,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.567866738312735,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022193,
      "question_number": "263",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A child is experiencing repeated staring episodes (absence seizures) at home and school. What is the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Ethosuximide",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7737704918032787,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7342894393741851,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022194,
      "question_number": "155",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A young patient with a 10-year history of focal seizures on treatment has been seizure-free for 2 ye...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "C. Having one type of seizure",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6696230598669624,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5928888888888889,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022195,
      "question_number": "288",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario typical of childhood absence epilepsy, which antiepileptic medication will worsen...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Trileptal"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022196,
      "question_number": "49",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q49. Patient came with absence seizure with rare GTC; EEG showed 3Hz. What are the other associated ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Eyelid myotonia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022197,
      "question_number": "23",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with a new onset seizure and a normal neurological examination presents. What will carry t...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Family history of epilepsy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022198,
      "question_number": "293",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the most significant predictor of seizure recurrence in a patient known to have epilepsy who...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "B. Generalized type of epilepsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6352357320099256,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4969990766389658,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022199,
      "question_number": "224",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient had recurrent nocturnal seizures with hypermotor features, a history of asymmetric posturi...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Supplementary motor area (SMA)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8035714285714286,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.716686289200471,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022200,
      "question_number": "219",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q219. A 20-year-old male with generalized tonic-clonic seizures on lamotrigine 200 mg bid has had a ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Valproate",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8368421052631579,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5058139534883721,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022201,
      "question_number": "269",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following neurodegenerative disorders is characterized by progressive combined upper an...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7621247113163973,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7029350971475816,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022202,
      "question_number": "285",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 26-year-old female, who is known to have epilepsy, has increased seizure frequency and is pregnant...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lamotrigine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.825974025974026,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.620253164556962,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022203,
      "question_number": "140",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is the most common cause of ischemic stroke?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Large artery atherosclerosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5454545454545454,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5428895326867363,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022204,
      "question_number": "278",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is the most common cause of subarachnoid hemorrhage?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Ruptured berry aneurysm"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022205,
      "question_number": "267",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A young lady who underwent tumor resection presented with a staring spell and loss of awareness. Wha...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Levetiracetam",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7737704918032787,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6156178923426838,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022206,
      "question_number": "6",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is the most common cause of acute ischemic stroke?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Large artery atherosclerosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5669291338582677,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7135003054367746,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022207,
      "question_number": "33",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with mesial temporal lobe epilepsy (MTLE) is on two anti-seizure medications but still exp...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Start workup for epilepsy surgery",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6561085972850679,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7785817655571635,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022208,
      "question_number": "154",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "After moderate traumatic brain injury and an episode of transient global amnesia, for how long does ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Up to 5 years"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022209,
      "question_number": "64",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the most common cause of sudden unexpected death in epilepsy (SUDEP)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Uncontrolled seizure"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022210,
      "question_number": "272",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Patient came with absence seizure with rare GTC; EEG showed 3Hz; what are the other associated sympt...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Eyelid myotonia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7834394904458599,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6517610109922979,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022211,
      "question_number": "49",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following cranial nerves is primarily responsible for controlling the muscles of facial...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Facial nerve (CN VII)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022212,
      "question_number": "292",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a case of palpitation and sweating, what is the localization of the seizure?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Insula"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022213,
      "question_number": "5",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a case of generalized tonic-clonic (GTC) seizures, what is the percentage of recurrence within 2 ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. 25%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022214,
      "question_number": "178",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q178. A patient diagnosed with epilepsy started on antiepileptic medication and was later found to h...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Felbamate",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8469387755102041,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7907027738186603,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022215,
      "question_number": "213",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 25-year-old pregnant lady with epilepsy is currently on Valproic acid 500 mg daily. She has had no...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Stop Valproic acid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7943262411347518,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7061508367746142,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022216,
      "question_number": "290",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q290. A patient known to have epilepsy for more than 10 years, who reports no aura, arrives at the e...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "C. Focal to bilateral tonic-clonic",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7374301675977654,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.30127606598194834,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022217,
      "question_number": "190",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A child with developmental delay has an EEG that shows hypsarrhythmia. What is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. West syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6476868327402135,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.537679226408803,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022218,
      "question_number": "197",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 61-year-old male with diabetes, hypertension, dyslipidemia, osteoporosis, and epilepsy is being ev...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Lamotrigine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8187134502923976,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7580455719990604,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022219,
      "question_number": "207",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old female patient diagnosed with epilepsy is currently on Lacosamide 200 mg BID and Levet...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Trisynaptic glutamergic neuron excitation"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022220,
      "question_number": "226",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 58-year-old man presents with an 18-month history of progressive limb weakness. Examination shows ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8933601609657947,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7509440439409544,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022221,
      "question_number": "104",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A young patient with developmental delay and multiple seizure types is on Clobazam 10 mg BID, Leveti...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Corpus callosotomy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022222,
      "question_number": "206",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A young patient presented to the neurology outpatient clinic for epilepsy evaluation. He has seizure...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Supplementary motor area"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022223,
      "question_number": "205",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 35-year-old male presented to the emergency room with a cluster of seizures a few hours ago. He is...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. IV Levetiracetam",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8652037617554859,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.47968577390450473,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022224,
      "question_number": "14",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A young female presents with a right arm focal clonic seizure lasting for 1 hour, triggered by stres...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Persistent eye opening",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8538587848932676,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7857641311933008,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022225,
      "question_number": "178",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following cranial nerves is primarily responsible for the sense of smell?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Olfactory nerve (CN I)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022226,
      "question_number": "120",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the risk of having a second seizure within 2 years after the first seizure?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. 30%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022227,
      "question_number": "92",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q92. A patient has been on levetiracetam (LEV) for a long time. What is a possible side effect?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Suicidal thoughts"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022228,
      "question_number": "132",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with no aura but has focal aware seizure presentations and is uncontrolled on two...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Video EEG"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022229,
      "question_number": "218",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following cranial nerves is primarily responsible for controlling the muscles of facial...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Facial nerve (CN VII)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6809815950920245,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7247372675828617,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022230,
      "question_number": "220",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with seizures who is on antiepileptic drugs (AEDs) develops aplastic anemia. What is the m...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Felbamate",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8203592814371258,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.019545100752399895,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022231,
      "question_number": "287",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A young female with epilepsy wants to start oral contraceptive pills (OCP). What is the correct resp...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Increase lamotrigine to 2 folds"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022232,
      "question_number": "154",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q154. A 65-year-old man presents with sudden onset of right-sided weakness and aphasia. Imaging reve...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Embolism from atrial fibrillation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7336683417085427,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7265221878224974,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022233,
      "question_number": "6",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient had moderate head trauma in a motor vehicle accident (MVA). For how long does the risk of ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. 20 years"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022234,
      "question_number": "211",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A child who has had 2 episodes of seizure, both occurring while he was on a train, associated with n...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Occipital seizure"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022235,
      "question_number": "94",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 26-year-old woman presents to the emergency room with 4 tonic-clonic seizures. Lorazepam and a loa...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Order continuous EEG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7966101694915254,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6487271103171058,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022236,
      "question_number": "187",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "EEG changes associated with hyperventilation?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022237,
      "question_number": "168",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 35-year-old patient with epilepsy on anti-seizure medication (ASM) has been controlled for the las...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Generalized seizure",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7782426778242678,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6602785515320334,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022238,
      "question_number": "262",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 9-month-old child with a history of developmental delay and atonic spasms for seconds has an attac...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Infantile spasm",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7152941176470589,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7071008863658999,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022239,
      "question_number": "275",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents in adolescence with generalized tonic\u2013clonic seizures upon awakening and prominen...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Ion Channel",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8501628664495114,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5717901518637828,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022240,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the localization of juvenile myoclonic epilepsy (JME) based on the semiology of seizures wit...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Mesial-frontal"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022241,
      "question_number": "169",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 26-year-old female, who is known to have epilepsy and has had increased seizure frequency. She is ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Lamotrigine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022242,
      "question_number": "286",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a child with a typical scenario of benign rolandic epilepsy, what is the finding on EEG?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Centrotemporal spikes"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022243,
      "question_number": "285",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is the most common cause of acute ischemic stroke?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. Large artery atherosclerosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5333333333333333,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6293498452012384,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022244,
      "question_number": "286",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following cranial nerves is primarily responsible for controlling the muscles of facial...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Facial nerve (Cranial Nerve VII)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5986659825551565,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022245,
      "question_number": "208",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is the most common cause of acute ischemic stroke?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Large artery atherosclerosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5669291338582677,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7712447304193477,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022246,
      "question_number": "12",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with features of Rolandic epilepsy presents for an EEG. What is the expected finding?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022247,
      "question_number": "178",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A young male with a first-time generalized tonic-clonic seizure during the daytime has no previous s...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. 30%",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9342723004694836,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.518594249201278,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022248,
      "question_number": "273",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with hallucinations followed by a headache. What is the likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Occipital seizure",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6618181818181819,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7644234965523261,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022249,
      "question_number": "388",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "An 18-month-old baby had one febrile seizure. What is the chance of developing epilepsy in the futur...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. 3%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022250,
      "question_number": "93",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with epilepsy wants to get pregnant. Which of the following statements is correct?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022251,
      "question_number": "278",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the most common type of aura in mesial temporal lobe (MTL) seizures?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Epigastric rising sensation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5593869731800766,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7020246913580247,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022252,
      "question_number": "29",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the pathology responsible for MTL (medial temporal lobe) epilepsy?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Mossy fibers sprouting",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5991561181434599,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.566931982633864,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022253,
      "question_number": "203",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the direction of gaze deviation in a patient experiencing a seizure?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Away from the lesion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6097560975609756,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6852956210598058,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022254,
      "question_number": "283",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q283. What is the most common cause of sudden unexpected death in epilepsy (SUDEP)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Uncontrolled seizure"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022255,
      "question_number": "178",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which cranial nerve is primarily responsible for the sense of smell?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Olfactory nerve (CN I)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5381526104417671,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.05384787973973525,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022256,
      "question_number": "171",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient experiences an aura of palpitations and sweating. Where is the likely localization of the ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Insular"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022257,
      "question_number": "60",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the treatment for focal seizures?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. IV phenytoin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5594405594405595,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.55715745260529,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022258,
      "question_number": "99",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q99. Multiple seizure types with intellectual impairment, what will you see in the EEG?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Slow spike/wave less than 2Hz",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.610909090909091,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2439082656473961,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022259,
      "question_number": "214",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 53-year-old male presents with his first generalized tonic-clonic seizure and a normal EEG. He has...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. 30%",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9230769230769231,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7888888888888889,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022260,
      "question_number": "166",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is the most common cause of acute ischemic stroke?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Large artery atherosclerosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5333333333333333,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.27616616384311904,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022261,
      "question_number": "292",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is the most common cause of acute ischemic stroke?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. Large artery atherosclerosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5669291338582677,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7898335992705722,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022262,
      "question_number": "157",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a scenario involving a child with nocturnal seizures and ictal speech, which EEG finding is most ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Centrotemporal spikes"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022263,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with frontal lobe epilepsy has been on antiepileptic drugs (AED) since the age of 15 and h...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Moderate risk",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8059701492537313,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7241250467056919,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022264,
      "question_number": "164",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "An 18-year-old male with epilepsy on valproic acid and topiramate remains uncontrolled. He was found...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Generalized seizure",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8453237410071942,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4839072698627054,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022265,
      "question_number": "32",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "For a patient experiencing a first-time seizure with normal imaging and EEG, what is the risk of sei...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. 26%",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.900709219858156,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7740533119780345,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022266,
      "question_number": "260",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with MRI showing mesial temporal sclerosis (MTS) has a fear aura. What is the best approac...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Surgery",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7417582417582418,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4538112064613831,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022267,
      "question_number": "131",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a scenario about Rolandic epilepsy, what are the expected EEG findings?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Focal spikes in the centrotemporal region",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.51985559566787,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7791074823845208,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022268,
      "question_number": "373",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which antiepileptic drug (AED) is known to worsen myoclonus?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "D. Levetiracetam",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6229508196721312,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5124956812161695,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022269,
      "question_number": "25",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "An old lady with diabetes mellitus, hypertension, and atrial fibrillation had an episode of syncope ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Rhythmic clonus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9055793991416309,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3647088997178764,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022270,
      "question_number": "121",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a scenario with EEG showing interictal discharges, which term describes the source zone?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Irritative Zone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6716981132075471,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5297862664847658,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022271,
      "question_number": "212",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A child with a history of absence seizures and auditory agnosia is most likely diagnosed with which ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Landau-Kleffner syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6833855799373041,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5306581059390049,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022272,
      "question_number": "259",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with an arched back and repeated similar attacks has tried several medications with no imp...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Psychogenic"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022273,
      "question_number": "180",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which condition shows slow spike and wave?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022274,
      "question_number": "173",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A child was seen during an interview and had continuous jerks of the right arm with few interruption...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. IV Levetiracetam"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022275,
      "question_number": "261",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A female patient had a seizure at the mall, described as a temporal lobe seizure. What is the recomm...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Perform an EEG"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022276,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q18. A male patient with a known history of epilepsy has been on carbamazepine and is free of seizur...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Abruptly stopping carbamazepine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022277,
      "question_number": "253",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q253. What is the definition of ictal speech?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022278,
      "question_number": "234",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with epilepsy is taking carbamazepine and valproic acid. What are the effects of these two...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Increase the epoxide",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6183844011142061,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7637434554973822,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022279,
      "question_number": "217",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents to the ER with a history of 3 unprovoked seizures, and all labs are normal. She h...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Give AED"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022280,
      "question_number": "216",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q216. What are the features of right temporal epilepsy?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022281,
      "question_number": "242",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 7-year-old boy playing PlayStation all night has facial twitching and right arm movements. The pat...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Centrotemporal epilepsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8063943161634103,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7862151530699504,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022282,
      "question_number": "22",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A case of hypsarrhythmia, mental regression, and infantile spasms is presented. What is the diagnosi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. West syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6735395189003437,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6924838642515094,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022283,
      "question_number": "64",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Male patient has migraine and seizure; what medications will you give?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Valproic acid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6766169154228856,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4764679911699779,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022284,
      "question_number": "162",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "MTS seizure with normal MRI; EEG showed right frontotemporal discharge. What is the next step?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Interictal PET"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022285,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A female patient on four AEDs still has abnormal movements for more than one hour, with a normal pro...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Stop all AEDs (consider PNES)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.69377990430622,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.392827868852459,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022286,
      "question_number": "85",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with hallucinations followed by a headache. What is the likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Occipital seizure",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6642335766423357,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2089019712782089,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022287,
      "question_number": "223",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with Landau-Kleffner syndrome presents with auditory agnosia and aphasia. During slow-wave...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Landau-Kleffner syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7827868852459017,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6137481717856668,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022288,
      "question_number": "55",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q55. A patient has a history of no aura with a seizure while on two ASM. An EEG showed left temporal...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Video EEG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7356948228882834,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7841877702285361,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022289,
      "question_number": "78",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with a history of stroke followed by one episode of generalized tonic\u2013clonic sei...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Valproic acid"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022290,
      "question_number": "130",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a case where the seizure was idiopathic and the patient has a sibling with seizures, what is the ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. 30%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022291,
      "question_number": "281",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the treatment for focal seizures?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "C. IV phenytoin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5633802816901409,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5959435461258061,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022292,
      "question_number": "509",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A male patient with early morning seizures and an EEG showing juvenile myoclonic epilepsy (JME) is b...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Depakin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022293,
      "question_number": "227",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with laryngeal discomfort and tonic posturing. What type of seizure is likely occ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Insular seizure",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6840390879478827,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.686020635241756,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022294,
      "question_number": "23",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q23. An EEG shows slow spikes characteristic of which condition?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lennox-Gastaut syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5321888412017167,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7397687649109929,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022295,
      "question_number": "138",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with seizure semiology that suggests Mesial Temporal Lobe Epilepsy (MTLE) with epigastric ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. LGI1 gene",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8551401869158879,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7873694321046945,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022296,
      "question_number": "63",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 6-year-old with a staring episode has an EEG showing 3 Hz spike\u2010and\u2010wave discharges, consistent wi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. ADHD",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8944723618090452,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7549470531607658,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022297,
      "question_number": "183",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of these is a characteristic of LGS?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022298,
      "question_number": "15",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a patient with features of Rolandic epilepsy, what is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022299,
      "question_number": "176",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q176. A child with a typical scenario of benign rolandic epilepsy is being evaluated. What is the fi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Centrotemporal spikes"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022300,
      "question_number": "99",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with generalized tonic\u2013clonic seizures and interictal myoclonus (typical scenario for juve...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Ion Channel"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022301,
      "question_number": "92",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In patients with head trauma, what is the risk of seizure recurrence at 12 months?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. 46%",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.851063829787234,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6615515771526002,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022302,
      "question_number": "135",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with epilepsy denies any aura, and the MRI shows heterotopia. What is the classification o...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Unknown",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8028673835125448,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6529372045914922,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022303,
      "question_number": "17",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Young female with right arm focal clonic seizure lasting for 1 hour and triggered by stress on 4 AED...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Persistent eye opening",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8189300411522634,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6547210969149267,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022304,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q7. A 3-Hz spike EEG is characteristic of which condition?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Absence seizure",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5358851674641149,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6728647967223448,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022305,
      "question_number": "228",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In the context of focal seizures, which factors favor a good prognosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022306,
      "question_number": "139",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is a characteristic feature of Benign Rolandic Epilepsy of Childhood?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Onset usually between 2-13 years"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022307,
      "question_number": "277",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Typical JME on topiramate and well controlled; he wants to stop the medication. What is the recommen...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lifelong treatment",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5531914893617021,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5101699392445188,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022308,
      "question_number": "159",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is NOT a common behavioral problem associated with Landau-Kleffner syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "C. Hyperactivity",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7101449275362319,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7259002169197397,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022309,
      "question_number": "31",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of infantile spasms, if an EEG is provided, what is the EEG description?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Hypsarrhythmia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6887966804979253,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.736133873889416,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022310,
      "question_number": "32",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q32. A young female was brought by her family due to bizarre nocturnal hyperactive abnormal movement...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Carbamazepine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.893760539629005,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6023774866569627,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022311,
      "question_number": "33",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Localization of palpitation in seizure attacks is more commonly associated with which structure?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Insula",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7818930041152263,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.58249832999332,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022312,
      "question_number": "270",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q270. Patient with seizure and mental retardation, EEG showed 2Hz; what is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Valproic acid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7172995780590717,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5709556389318031,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022313,
      "question_number": "372",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient has seizure recurrence while on topiramate 200 mg and carbamazepine 400 mg bid. An EEG sho...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. MTS"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022314,
      "question_number": "143",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the typical EEG finding in a patient with Benign Rolandic Epilepsy of Childhood?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Bilateral independent centrotemporal spikes",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.525679758308157,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7588292472189221,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022315,
      "question_number": "31",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of a patient with seizure associated hypersalivation, which area of the brain is ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Temporal lobe",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7781569965870307,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7541984732824427,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022316,
      "question_number": "209",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the risk of developing epilepsy following a febrile seizure?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. 6%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022317,
      "question_number": "141",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient who is epileptic and on Topamax and Carbamazepine (CBZ CR) presents with breakthrough seiz...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Mesial temporal sclerosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7906976744186046,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.38555030384875083,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022318,
      "question_number": "146",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Slow spike-and-wave activity on EEG (1.5\u20132.5 Hz)",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022319,
      "question_number": "389",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of Lennox-Gastaut syndrome, what is the first-line treatment for drop attacks?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Clobazam"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022320,
      "question_number": "280",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Patient with seizure; EEG showed multifocal spikes; what is the surgery for this patient?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. VNS"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022321,
      "question_number": "276",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Patient with a generalized tonic-clonic seizure; which factor increases the risk of seizure recurren...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Long duration",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6688741721854304,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5485801327385486,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022322,
      "question_number": "49",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with hyperkinetic nocturnal seizures and a positive family history. How would you treat hi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Carbamazepine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022323,
      "question_number": "188",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In focal seizures, where is the localization of the seizure in the semiology of absence?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Mesial temporal lobe",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6852589641434262,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.283170520588599,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022324,
      "question_number": "24",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient came with a history of right early non-forced head turning and right-side automatism. What...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Right temporal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7608695652173914,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7439101885193815,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022325,
      "question_number": "307",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 25-year-old pregnant lady came to the clinic and needs counseling regarding antiepileptic drugs (A...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Increase the dose of lamotrigine in the 1st and 2nd trimester",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5770609318996416,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7440747493163172,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022326,
      "question_number": "447",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What EEG finding suggests a poor prognosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022327,
      "question_number": "308",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 6-month-old infant presents with typical infantile spasms and developmental delay. EEG shows hypsa...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. West syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7471264367816092,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5570483670938404,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022328,
      "question_number": "216",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of mesiotemporal epilepsy, what is the typical semiology used to ask about the diagnos...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Aura characteristics"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022329,
      "question_number": "410",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with features suggestive of absence seizures and EEG showing 3 Hz spike-wave discharges. W...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Oxcarbazepine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022330,
      "question_number": "263",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 23-year-old male patient on lamotrigine 200 mg BID had a tonic-clonic seizure that was not fully c...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Keppra"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022331,
      "question_number": "333",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario, if the patient came to the emergency room, what is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. IV diazepam",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.702928870292887,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7762883008356546,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022332,
      "question_number": "264",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 3-year-old boy presents with auditory agnosia and delay in language development. EEG shows ESES. W...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Landau-Kleffner syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7069486404833837,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7914375490966221,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022333,
      "question_number": "108",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Patient presents after a first unprovoked generalized tonic\u2010clonic seizure. Which of the following f...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Long duration",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7384615384615385,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5405405405405406,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022334,
      "question_number": "290",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient came to the clinic with facial and arm twitches, and pronator drift, occasionally stopping...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Epileptic partial complex (EPC)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7584650112866818,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7253438820462106,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022335,
      "question_number": "350",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the normal response to hyperventilation on EEG?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022336,
      "question_number": "215",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "If the seizures were deemed idiopathic with spike-wave discharges on EEG, what is the risk of seizur...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. 17%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022337,
      "question_number": "332",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient underwent a dental procedure and experienced brief loss of consciousness. What favors a di...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Confusion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8404907975460123,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.778126088470916,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022338,
      "question_number": "102",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In the scenario of Panayiotopoulos Syndrome, which of the following is a characteristic feature of t...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Early onset benign childhood seizures"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022339,
      "question_number": "27",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 20-year-old female known to have seizures presented to the outpatient clinic. She is on Lacosamide...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Add Topiramate"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022340,
      "question_number": "322",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A young lady who underwent aneurysm clipping developed seizures characterized by confusion and stari...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Focal nonmotor with impaired awareness",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.75,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.48781758957654725,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022341,
      "question_number": "83",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 70-year-old man with a history of obesity, hypertension, hypercholesterolemia, nephrolithiasis, an...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Lamotrigine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9112426035502958,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7165813807343567,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022342,
      "question_number": "349",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient has been on carbamazepine (CBZ) for a long time for focal epilepsy and has recently been s...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Increased CBZ epoxide level",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7180616740088106,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7575442247658689,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022343,
      "question_number": "26",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A young patient presented to the neurology outpatient clinic for epilepsy evaluation. He has seizure...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Impaired awareness to bilateral tonic-clonic seizure",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8702127659574468,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4571639586410635,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022344,
      "question_number": "101",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient on lamotrigine wants to start oral contraceptive pills (OCP). What should you tell the pat...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022345,
      "question_number": "25",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q25. A 25-year-old pregnant lady came to the outpatient neurology clinic for follow-up. She is a kno...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Switch to Lamotrigine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.847769028871391,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6937646307725048,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022346,
      "question_number": "277",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A child with perisylvian atrophy and unilateral weakness had initially focal seizures and then focal...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. GluR3",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8823529411764706,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4941826643397324,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022347,
      "question_number": "45",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A female patient with a history of epilepsy experiences seizures more frequently during menstruation...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Estradiol lowers seizure threshold",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6318181818181818,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7338067570475576,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022348,
      "question_number": "212",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the electrodecremental response in EEG associated with hypsarrhythmia?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. 2/sec",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7938144329896907,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3338328530259366,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022349,
      "question_number": "135",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A mother brought her 2-month-old baby with seizures and a history of the same seizures in his older ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. KCNQ2",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8982630272952854,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.717948717948718,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022350,
      "question_number": "142",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 3-month-old infant has a history of clonic and possible tonic or myoclonic seizures. The sibling h...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. KCNQ2 on chromosome 20",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8534704370179949,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3862928348909657,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022351,
      "question_number": "214",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is associated with seizures and asymmetrical atrophy?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. GLUR3",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7653061224489796,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7455080039202875,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022352,
      "question_number": "300",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q300. A 28-year-old man with a one-year history of episodes of posturing of both arms, described by ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Supplementary motor area",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8925170068027211,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.43037974683544306,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022353,
      "question_number": "105",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q105. (Source: Part II 2018mcqs.txt) Which AED is known to cause fingers/toes dysesthesia?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Lamotrigine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7142857142857143,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6683417085427136,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022354,
      "question_number": "84",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 6-year-old with a history of seizures and developmental delay is found to have subependymal nodule...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Tuberous sclerosis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022355,
      "question_number": "191",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a case of temporal lobe epilepsy (TLE) with auditory features, which genetic mutation is typicall...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. LGI-1",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8396946564885496,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.789354105809802,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022356,
      "question_number": "150",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is the channel involved in juvenile myoclonic epilepsy (JME)?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Chloride (Cl)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022357,
      "question_number": "13",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with progressive myoclonus and dementia is being evaluated. How can the diagnosis be confi...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. NCL skin biopsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7463768115942029,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7979144539924689,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022358,
      "question_number": "80",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 12-year-old patient presented with a history of seizures that started 3 years ago. The parents des...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. GABRA-1"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022359,
      "question_number": "149",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with seizures who sometimes had febrile seizures is diagnosed with Dravet syndrome. What i...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Carbamazepine worsens the seizures."
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022360,
      "question_number": "20",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a case involving Landau-Kleffner syndrome (verbal auditory agnosia and progressive aphasia) who w...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Landau-Kleffner syndrome (LKS)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7484407484407485,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3440774373814989,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022361,
      "question_number": "436",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a scenario where an infant with myoclonus started focally and became progressive, what would you ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Burst suppression"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022362,
      "question_number": "186",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a case of epilepsy partialis continua, what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. IV Phenytoin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022363,
      "question_number": "53",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with short stature, a long history of seizures, and multiple skin macular and cut...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Multiple enhanced cortical tubers",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.73828125,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7151162790697675,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022364,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a patient with developmental delay and multiple seizure types (tonic spasms, drop attacks), what ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Spike and slow waves slower than 2 Hz",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6141732283464567,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.29172550127082747,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022365,
      "question_number": "409",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a normal child with a simple febrile seizure, what is the risk of developing epilepsy?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. 3%",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.87,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.21074309250042902,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022366,
      "question_number": "65",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A young lady who underwent tumor resection presents with a staring spell and loss of awareness. EEG ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Focal non-motor onset with impaired awareness"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022367,
      "question_number": "30",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient experiences a visual aura lasting for 10 seconds followed by a headache. What is the most ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Migraine aura",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7569060773480663,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7670485542825969,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022368,
      "question_number": "28",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of a patient with Mesial Temporal Lobe Epilepsy (MTLE) on two sufficient anti-sei...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Start workup for epilepsy surgery",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.643510054844607,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6848502816483842,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022369,
      "question_number": "211",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q211. A history of seizures in a few months old baby, with a similar history in the older brother, i...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. KCNQ2/chr 20"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022370,
      "question_number": "61",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario of the young lady post-aneurysm clipping, what is the recommended antiepileptic...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Keppra",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8593350383631714,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7865743813406656,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022371,
      "question_number": "36",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Patient with absence seizure; what is the medication that worsens the seizure?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Oxycarbazepine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022372,
      "question_number": "2",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient with a history of diabetes mellitus, hypertension, hyperlipidemia, and osteoporos...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Lamotrigine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022373,
      "question_number": "42",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient with partial seizures has a PET scan showing hypometabolism in the perisylvian region. Whi...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. NMDA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022374,
      "question_number": "145",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "An elderly male with a history of diabetes mellitus, hypertension, dyslipidemia, and ischemic heart ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Typical syncope",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8963795255930087,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6935269207501512,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022375,
      "question_number": "200",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following statements is true regarding absence seizures?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022376,
      "question_number": "2",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A boy with uncontrolled seizures is known to have bipolar disorder. What is the most appropriate man...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Valproate"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022377,
      "question_number": "25",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient has an abdominal rising sensation and d\u00e9j\u00e0 vu. Which of the following is involved in the p...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Schaffer collateral from C3 to C1"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022378,
      "question_number": "8",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient experiences an abdominal rising sensation and d\u00e9j\u00e0 vu. Which localization is most likely a...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Mesial Temporal"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022379,
      "question_number": "201",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 33-year-old with a history of generalized tonic-clonic seizure with an aura of a rising abdominal ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Temporal lobe epilepsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8048192771084337,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6964589050045734,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022380,
      "question_number": "10",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q10. A patient presents with a figure of 4, fencing posture, and right side nose rubbing. Which loca...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Left temporal"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022381,
      "question_number": "73",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient with a history of diabetes mellitus (DM), hypertension (HTN), and end-stage renal...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. EEG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9237804878048781,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7004915730337079,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022382,
      "question_number": "213",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is a known side effect of Vigabatrin?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022383,
      "question_number": "62",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 5-year-old child presents with cognitive decline since 7 months of age and has frequent spasms wit...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. West Syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8092243186582809,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6225944760195433,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022384,
      "question_number": "263",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "The drug Keppra is:",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022385,
      "question_number": "262",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 28-year-old female with a hemorrhagic lesion in the brain had a staring episode followed by post-e...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Phenytoin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022386,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "Q35. A patient with features of Rolandic epilepsy presents with what EEG finding?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022387,
      "question_number": "112",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old patient with a known case of diabetes mellitus (DM) and hypertension (HTN) presents wi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Start lamotrigine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8442622950819673,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7775365031823287,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022388,
      "question_number": "11",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "What is true about Juvenile Myoclonic Epilepsy (JME)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022389,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old patient with seizures controlled on antiepileptic drugs (AED) developed facial redness...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Phenytoin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8439897698209718,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.02497687326549491,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022390,
      "question_number": "216",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents to the emergency room with status absence seizures. Which of the following medica...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Phenytoin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8184615384615385,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7650632911392405,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022391,
      "question_number": "67",
      "subspecialty": "Epilepsy",
      "question_text": "In a patient with occipital seizure and migraine with aura, which of the following is in favor of vi...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Scintillating",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6646153846153846,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.673293172690763,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024076,
      "question_number": "43",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A known case of migraine, a female patient in her 1st trimester, came to the ER with a headache. Wha...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Acetaminophen",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7958477508650519,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6699580350530733,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024077,
      "question_number": "105",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q105. Which of the following characteristics is associated with pain in glossopharyngeal neuralgia?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Electric shock-like, shooting, stabbing, or sharp in quality",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5359116022099447,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6563407550822846,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024078,
      "question_number": "57",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A pregnant patient at 12 weeks GA with migraine came with status migrainosus. What is the management...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Subcutaneous sumatriptan",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.717391304347826,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7248548812664908,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024079,
      "question_number": "132",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of SUNA (Short-lasting Unilateral Neuralgiform headache attacks with conjunctival inje...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Lamotrigine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024080,
      "question_number": "54",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a small area of headache associated with hair loss. What is the most appropr...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "C. Topical corticosteroids",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7290322580645161,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7979912829259048,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024081,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "What is the first-line treatment for glossopharyngeal neuralgia?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Carbamazepine (CBZ)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024082,
      "question_number": "237",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with unilateral headache on a daily basis associated with ptosis and lacrimation....",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Hemicrania continua"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024083,
      "question_number": "71",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient recently had a baby delivered by C-section one day ago and came to the ED with a headache ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Blood patch",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8854961832061069,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6955467372134039,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024084,
      "question_number": "54",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q54. A migraine patient with daily persistent headache, who used to take daily triptans and NSAIDs, ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Gradual discontinuation of the medications",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6308068459657702,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4973585630583037,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024085,
      "question_number": "40",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A young female patient, known to have migraine controlled on medications, now presents with unilater...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Short\u2010lasting unilateral neuralgiform headache with conjunctival injection and tearing (SUNCT)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8040089086859689,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7989276139410187,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024086,
      "question_number": "133",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q133. Which of the following features would be most supportive of a diagnosis of medication-overuse ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Worsened severity upon awakening"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024087,
      "question_number": "56",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Patient came with tongue pain and paresthesia, radiating to the neck, increased with neck movement; ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Neck-tongue syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024088,
      "question_number": "6",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A pregnant patient presents with a severe migraine attack, similar to her previous migraine attacks....",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Paracetamol"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024089,
      "question_number": "65",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q65. A 35-year-old woman presents with a headache, describing 10 episodes a day of sharp pain over t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lacrimation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8826151560178306,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7032384690873406,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024090,
      "question_number": "14",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A male patient presents with headache, congestion, tearing, with a duration of 15\u201330 minutes, occurr...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. SUNCT"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024091,
      "question_number": "52",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In the same case scenario as above, what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Carbamazepine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6699507389162561,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7975826307543087,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024092,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A young lady post uneventful delivery by cesarean section came with a history of positional headache...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Intracranial hypotension",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8212703101920237,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.601007556675063,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024093,
      "question_number": "179",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of intracranial hypotension not responding to routine measures, what is the next step?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Blood patch",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6950354609929078,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.789478135836928,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024094,
      "question_number": "78",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In a case of a headache attributed to trigeminal neuralgia, what is the best treatment option?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Carbamazepine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024095,
      "question_number": "205",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 10-week pregnant woman presents with severe acute migraine. Which of the following is the recommen...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Acetaminophen"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024096,
      "question_number": "180",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Question 180. In a scenario of glossopharyngeal neuralgia, what should be done next?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. MRI of the head and neck",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5869565217391305,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5814284518127774,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024097,
      "question_number": "46",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 35-year-old man with well-controlled migraine headaches says he sometimes takes pregabalin on week...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Refer to psychiatry",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7174721189591078,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.45436268596702856,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024098,
      "question_number": "8",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A boy presents with a headache that is more pronounced in the morning and is associated with nausea ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CT brain",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.681592039800995,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3849362119725221,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024099,
      "question_number": "321",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A male patient reports shock-like electric sensations in half of his face multiple times per day, an...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Trigeminal neuralgia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7804878048780488,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7618457726850418,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024100,
      "question_number": "115",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of trigeminal neuralgia, what is needed to reach the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Clinical diagnosis, no need for imaging",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6276150627615062,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7173772907265863,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024101,
      "question_number": "350",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with severe periorbital episodic headache lasting 5 minutes. What is the most com...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lacrimation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7378048780487805,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6911660777385159,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024102,
      "question_number": "106",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient has irritable bowel syndrome, is obese, and has migraine. What would you prescribe as a pr...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Topiramate",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7820069204152249,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5425597060624617,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024103,
      "question_number": "16",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient with migraine underwent a brain MRI as a routine workup for chronic headache, which showed...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Reassurance",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7289719626168224,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.521999760220597,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024104,
      "question_number": "94",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Triptans can be used in patients with which of the following conditions?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "D. Tension-type headache",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5795918367346938,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7944878472222222,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024105,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In the evaluation of a patient suspected of suffering from glossopharyngeal neuralgia, which of the ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Presence of trigger factors"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024106,
      "question_number": "72",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient has a severe headache with typical migraine features and has had previous episodes during ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Menstrual migraine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7487179487179487,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6641198942109903,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024107,
      "question_number": "73",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In a case with continuous headache and episodes of more intense headache, which treatment is indicat...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Indomethacin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7680608365019012,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7339223800469746,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024108,
      "question_number": "1",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A boy presents with headaches that are worse in the morning and associated with nausea and vomiting....",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. CT brain"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024109,
      "question_number": "55",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A male patient presents with lacinating pain lasting for seconds, and MRI shows SCA compression over...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Decompressive surgery",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5689954814042405,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024110,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient experiences a visual aura for 10\u201320 minutes followed by a headache. What is the most likel...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Migraine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7236842105263158,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5543613530942414,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024111,
      "question_number": "51",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Which of the following neurotransmitters has a role in the pathogenesis of migraine headache?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Serotonin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024112,
      "question_number": "15",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient came for a third opinion, diagnosed with Cluster Headache and another trigeminal autonomic...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Duration",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7506426735218509,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.753307850632167,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024113,
      "question_number": "39",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Which medication is considered safe for use in the 1st and 2nd trimester of pregnancy for treating m...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Acetaminophen",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.781021897810219,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7830123456790123,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024114,
      "question_number": "111",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Patient came with tongue pain and paresthesia, radiating to the neck, increased with neck movement. ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Tongue neck syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.686046511627907,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5240551150796705,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024115,
      "question_number": "94",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A young lady post uneventful delivery by cesarean section came with a history of positional headache...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Blood patch",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8395802098950524,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7311348781937017,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024116,
      "question_number": "62",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "According to the International Classification of Headache Disorders 3rd edition (ICHD-3), how many a...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. At least 10 attacks",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7597707139134966,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024117,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In a patient with occipital seizures and migraine with aura, which feature is in favor of a visual a...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Scintillating",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6822742474916388,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5889556639074724,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024118,
      "question_number": "93",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient came with a history of severe unilateral headache lasting less than 5 minutes, stabbing in...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Indomethacin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8641975308641975,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7757731958762887,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024119,
      "question_number": "48",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with recurrent attacks of headache lasting 4 days, accompanied by ptosis and opht...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Ophthalmoplegic migraine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7578947368421053,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5238010021474588,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024120,
      "question_number": "86",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Which of the following statements is true regarding medication overuse headache?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024121,
      "question_number": "116",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q116. In a scenario of nummular headache, what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Gabapentin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6886792452830188,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7844655637686261,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024122,
      "question_number": "102",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient with migraine headache has white matter changes that are not typical for multiple sclerosi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Reassurance",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.772020725388601,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6997073170731707,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024123,
      "question_number": "328",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Which medication is absolutely contraindicated in pregnancy for the treatment of migraine?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Ergotamine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7606837606837606,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7241012927217992,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024124,
      "question_number": "118",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of intracranial hypotension, which of the following is the most common MRI brain findi...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Leptomeningeal enhancement"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024125,
      "question_number": "513",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient experiences unilateral severe periorbital headache with autonomic features lasting 10\u201315 m...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Indomethacin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024126,
      "question_number": "285",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "What is the first-line treatment for migraine in pregnancy?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Acetaminophen",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6823529411764706,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7931146476128613,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024127,
      "question_number": "248",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A young patient presents with trigeminal neuralgia. What is the next best step in management?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. MRI",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7551867219917012,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6127814291707453,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024128,
      "question_number": "219",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Prior to prescribing oral contraceptive pills, evaluating for potential hypercoagulable states is mo...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Women with migraine with aura"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024129,
      "question_number": "72",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "How does pediatric migraine compare to adult migraine?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Bilateral and shorter",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5578947368421052,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7906976744186046,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024130,
      "question_number": "217",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of hemicrania continua, what is the first line treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Indomethacin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6831683168316832,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6943552088113814,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024131,
      "question_number": "78",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A male patient has a history of headaches that consistently awaken him from sleep. What is the most ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Caffeine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7817589576547231,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6527027027027027,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024132,
      "question_number": "236",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Which branch of the trigeminal nerve is most commonly affected in trigeminal neuralgia?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "C. V3 (mandibular)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.688,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7774900742275159,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024133,
      "question_number": "53",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "What is the attack duration for SUNCT?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024134,
      "question_number": "53",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A female with migraine occurring once a month underwent a brain MRI, which showed two small white ma...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Reassurance",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8195121951219512,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.49541732860808996,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024135,
      "question_number": "367",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A female patient presents with a headache and occasional blurring of vision when leaning forward. Sh...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Weight loss"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024136,
      "question_number": "209",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 40-year-old woman is seen in consultation for chronic daily headaches. She takes acetaminophen twi...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Worsened severity upon awakening"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024137,
      "question_number": "22",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A scenario describes a patient with basilar migraine and vertigo. What is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Basilar migraine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.63003663003663,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6794582392776524,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024138,
      "question_number": "76",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old man experiences a very severe, sudden-onset headache immediately after orgasm (\u201cthunde...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Brain CT",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8596491228070176,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.19815105529391244,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024139,
      "question_number": "61",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q61. What is the risk of stroke in patients with migraine?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024140,
      "question_number": "102",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q102. A patient with headache and lancinating pain in the face, what should be done next?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. MRI with contrast"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024141,
      "question_number": "99",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient with migraine on amitriptyline and sumatriptan became pregnant. What should be done?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Discontinue sumatriptan."
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024142,
      "question_number": "112",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q112. A known case of migraine in a female patient who is pregnant in her first trimester came to th...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Acetaminophen"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024143,
      "question_number": "65",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q65. A young female presented with a severe headache that worsens with standing and is relieved by l...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Leptomeningeal enhancement"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024144,
      "question_number": "100",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient with migraine that worsens with her period, what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Start triptan 2 days before her period for 7 days",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6035087719298246,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7607939431143851,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024145,
      "question_number": "67",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 24-year-old female came to the clinic asking for a third opinion for her headache. The first docto...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Duration of attack"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024146,
      "question_number": "61",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is NOT a preventive management option for short-lasting unilateral neuralgifo...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Sumatriptan"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024147,
      "question_number": "82",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "The acute treatment for cluster headache is:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Sumatriptan",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5733333333333334,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.32460732984293195,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024148,
      "question_number": "110",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with papilledema and headache, suggestive of idiopathic intracranial hypertension...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Lumbar puncture",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8092485549132948,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5992101320985973,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024149,
      "question_number": "98",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient with cluster headache, what is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Verapamil",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6503067484662577,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4790027834926782,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024150,
      "question_number": "117",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In a case of typical SUNCT, what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lamictal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6593406593406593,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7908920910790892,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024151,
      "question_number": "13",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A young female patient with a history of migraines and diabetes mellitus is a university student. Wh...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Propranolol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7948051948051948,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7833083029392834,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024152,
      "question_number": "76",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 43-year-old male with a history of around 30 attacks of severe headache per day, each attack lasti...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Lamictal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8729792147806005,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.65674643072592,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024153,
      "question_number": "12",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a headache and tearing that lasts less than 5 minutes and occurs 20\u201330 times...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. SUNCT",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7520891364902507,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5445116681071738,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024154,
      "question_number": "368",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "What is the best anti-emetic medication for migraine?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Metoclopramide"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024155,
      "question_number": "181",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In a pregnant patient with migraines, which prophylactic medication is suitable?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Propranolol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6995515695067265,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7569692637598284,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024156,
      "question_number": "69",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In managing migraines during pregnancy, what should be the initial approach regardless of headache s...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Start with simple analgesia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.664576802507837,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6677077523703291,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024157,
      "question_number": "241",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A female patient experiences migraines once a month, and her brain MRI shows one small white matter ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Reassurance",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7731481481481481,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5355859094176851,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024158,
      "question_number": "85",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A pregnant female in her third trimester presents with status migrainosus. What is the most appropri...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Methylprednisolone"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024159,
      "question_number": "10",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with paroxysmal throat pain triggered by swallowing and recurrent syncope suggest...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. MRI brain"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024160,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a stabbing headache occurring 100 times a day. What is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Indomethacin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7520661157024794,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7806160164271048,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024161,
      "question_number": "113",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a small area of headache associated with hair loss. What is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Gabapentin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6713286713286714,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7349688149688149,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024162,
      "question_number": "116",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In a case of trigeminal neuralgia, what is the most predictive of a structural cause?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Abnormal blink reflex",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6831275720164609,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3093666980889536,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024163,
      "question_number": "97",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A female patient presented with a history of flashing in the right eye, followed by right homonymous...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Hemiplegic migraine.",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7890743550834598,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.15018212384421406,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024164,
      "question_number": "68",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old patient with a history of migraines presents with daily headaches for the past 2 month...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Medication overuse headache",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8673740053050398,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7035659196080211,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024165,
      "question_number": "5",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In the scenario of paroxysmal hemicrania, what is the management?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Indomethacin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6596858638743456,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6835702394672813,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024166,
      "question_number": "59",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient experiences headaches lasting less than 1 minute, occurring 40 times a day, and is associa...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Lamotrigine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8413461538461539,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7325827666926764,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024167,
      "question_number": "40",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with unilateral headaches on a daily basis associated with ptosis and lacrimation...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Cluster headache",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7439024390243902,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7531052167641638,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024168,
      "question_number": "6",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient with migraine presents with nausea and vomiting. Laboratory tests show normal liver functi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Valproate",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8809073724007561,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7202863459311506,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024169,
      "question_number": "8",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "What is the mechanism of action of Botox in the treatment of migraine headaches?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024170,
      "question_number": "67",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In managing migraine during pregnancy, what is the initial approach regardless of headache severity?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Start with simple analgesia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024171,
      "question_number": "83",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A male patient presents with unilateral pain on the forehead lasting for 1 minute, with conjunctival...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lamotrigine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8705882352941177,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6414599906410856,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024172,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "An obese lady with asthma also suffers from migraine. What is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Topamax",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7478260869565218,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5688497523390204,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024173,
      "question_number": "117",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 29-year-old female came to the neurology clinic asking for a third opinion regarding her headache....",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Duration of the attack",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8567164179104477,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7571508693213684,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024174,
      "question_number": "104",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A male patient presents with a shock-like electric sensation in half of his face multiple times per ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Carbamazepine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8434343434343434,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.574124447466848,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024175,
      "question_number": "45",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with unilateral headache for a few months, sharp, lasting less than 1 minute, re...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Lamotrigine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024176,
      "question_number": "23",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q23. A woman who is post-partum (gave birth via cesarean section) presents with headache, and an MRI...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Blood patch"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024177,
      "question_number": "108",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q108. A pregnant woman with a history of migraines requires prophylactic treatment. What is the best...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Propranolol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7692307692307693,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7855541130650301,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024178,
      "question_number": "4",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of trigeminal neuralgia (TN) triggered by touching his face, he also has lacrimat...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Carbamazepine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024179,
      "question_number": "14",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a headache and tearing that lasts 15\u201330 minutes and occurs approximately 7 t...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Cluster headache",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8187633262260128,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7960854803275415,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024180,
      "question_number": "17",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q17. A patient with continuous headache for 4 months experiences episodic increases in pain intensit...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Indomethacin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8170731707317073,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6837590173523104,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024181,
      "question_number": "58",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 35-year-old male presents with a history of headaches lasting 1 to 1.5 hours, accompanied by nasal...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Calcium channel blocker",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8776758409785933,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7769364109114132,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024182,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A male patient experiences a very severe headache after orgasm that then improves. What would you do...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Brain CT",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7557251908396947,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5721040189125296,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024183,
      "question_number": "24",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A scenario describes a patient with ophthalmic migraine (third or sixth nerve palsy). What is the di...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Ophthalmic migraine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6731391585760518,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7687257019438445,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024184,
      "question_number": "43",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A case of migraine presents with nausea and vomiting, liver function tests are normal, but there are...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Valproate",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8776699029126214,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.699953509995351,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024185,
      "question_number": "80",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Based on current FDA classifications, which of the following is NOT recommended for migraine treatme...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Triptans"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024186,
      "question_number": "12",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a positional headache that worsens with standing. A brain MRI shows pachymen...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Intracranial hypotension",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7723785166240409,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6657171922685656,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024187,
      "question_number": "13",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A pregnant woman in her 8th month presents with an acute migraine. What is the recommended treatment...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Sumatriptans",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7415730337078652,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7681977423121837,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024188,
      "question_number": "11",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q11. A patient with migraine presents with a new onset of headache that is unlike their previous mig...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Medication overuse headache"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024189,
      "question_number": "42",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A male presents with occipital headache radiating to the frontal area. On exam, he has tenderness ov...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Nerve block",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7992202729044834,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5939520333680918,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024190,
      "question_number": "81",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "What is the best treatment for migraine-related nausea?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Domperidone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6372964322696036,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024191,
      "question_number": "14",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "What\u2019s the mechanism of action of Botox in migraine headache?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024192,
      "question_number": "11",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A postpartum patient presents with a history of headache, and an attached picture shows pachymeninge...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Blood patch"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024193,
      "question_number": "42",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Patient presented with recurrent migraine headache, disabling, causing loss of many hours per week, ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Topiramate"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024194,
      "question_number": "43",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 40-year-old patient presented with a headache for the past 4 months. It is continuous with periods...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Indomethacin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8830188679245283,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.536289033358201,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024195,
      "question_number": "64",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q64. Which medication is recommended for migraine treatment in the 1st and 2nd trimester of pregnanc...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Acetaminophen"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024196,
      "question_number": "44",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q44. What is the best treatment for hypnic headache?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lithium",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6410256410256411,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.008936170212765958,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024197,
      "question_number": "15",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A female patient presents with severe headache and papilledema, and no imaging has been performed. W...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. MRV",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7806267806267806,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7543670833678284,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024198,
      "question_number": "49",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "What is the first-line treatment for migraine in pediatric patients?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Ibuprofen"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024199,
      "question_number": "207",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "An obese female with a history of bronchial asthma is seeking migraine prophylaxis. Which medication...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Topiramate (TPX)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7603833865814696,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.538867232286173,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024200,
      "question_number": "70",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Which medication is NOT recommended for migraine treatment in the 3rd trimester of pregnancy?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. NSAID",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7540983606557377,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7642752562225475,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024201,
      "question_number": "46",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Patient has migraine headache, tried multiple analgesics and NSAIDs with no benefits. What is the sy...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Triptans",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7048192771084337,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7962256574984943,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024202,
      "question_number": "109",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with headache, photophobia, phonophobia, and nausea. Her mother reports a history...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Menstrual migraine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8241758241758241,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6934439498178875,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024203,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario, what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Indomethacin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6352941176470588,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6976952338330723,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024204,
      "question_number": "55",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 25-year-old female with a history of type 1 diabetes mellitus experiences migraines once a month t...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Topiramate",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8662674650698603,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6791003839824465,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024205,
      "question_number": "79",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old with migraine and peptic ulcer, what is the best medication for prevention?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Propranolol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7467811158798283,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.781208351843625,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024206,
      "question_number": "77",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Which of the following medications is considered a third-line treatment for migraine and is classifi...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Ergotamine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024207,
      "question_number": "174",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A scenario of acute onset daily headache which is constant and not related to any triggering factors...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. New daily persistent headache",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6099439110181576,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024208,
      "question_number": "79",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q79. A migraine patient's MRI brain shows hyperintense small lesions. What is the recommended manage...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Reassurance",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6732673267326733,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7246998284734134,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024209,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient with migraine presents with a new onset of headache that is unlike previous migraine heada...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Medication overuse headache",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7969348659003831,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7851148060174189,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024210,
      "question_number": "115",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A migraine patient with daily persistent headache has been taking daily triptans and NSAIDs. What is...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Gradual discontinuation of the medications",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5933014354066986,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4841841528343251,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024211,
      "question_number": "103",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient with chronic migraine, what is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Botox",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6625,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5567632850241546,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024212,
      "question_number": "87",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A pregnant woman at 10 weeks of gestation presents with severe migraine. What is the most appropriat...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Acetaminophen",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8012820512820513,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.705701604643223,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024213,
      "question_number": "74",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 27-year-old female presents with a severe headache located over the right side of her head, charac...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Acetaminophen",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8906882591093117,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.513663581927055,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024214,
      "question_number": "84",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 23-year-old female with type 1 diabetes mellitus is seeking prophylaxis for her migraines. What me...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Topiramate",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7925696594427245,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7924944812362031,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024215,
      "question_number": "52",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "What is the sign on brain MRI of a patient with intracranial hypotension?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024216,
      "question_number": "62",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 33-year-old female with a history of migraines calls the office because of a severe migraine at 32...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Oral sumatriptan",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8653846153846154,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7126460340233655,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024217,
      "question_number": "75",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q75. Which of the following is NOT a criterion for neuroimaging in children with headaches?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "C. Recent headache of less than 6 months' duration",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5056818181818182,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4984099450708297,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024218,
      "question_number": "180",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario asking about treatment, what is the appropriate medication?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Indomethacin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7090909090909091,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6864762704745905,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024219,
      "question_number": "9",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A male presents with an occipital headache radiating to the frontal area. On examination, he has ten...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Nerve block",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8067542213883677,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4718167793995491,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024220,
      "question_number": "60",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "What is the treatment for an acute attack of short-lasting unilateral neuralgiform headache?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lidocaine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7489711934156379,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7838224767358626,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024221,
      "question_number": "16",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "What percentage of migraine patients report their attack in the emergency room as disabling after 24...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. 50%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024222,
      "question_number": "20",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient has continuous headache for 3 months with some increase in baseline pain. What is the like...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Hemicrania continua",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6873065015479877,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6894364479141254,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024223,
      "question_number": "3",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q3. A case scenario of trigeminal neuralgia (TN) is presented, where the condition is triggered by t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Trigeminal Neuralgia (TN)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7414187643020596,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.17157387580299785,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024224,
      "question_number": "39",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In SUNCT, what are the minimum ipsilateral autonomic symptoms?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024225,
      "question_number": "95",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q95. A 25-year-old man presents with episodic, unilateral, throbbing headaches associated with nause...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. A triptan"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024226,
      "question_number": "19",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A middle-aged female presents with unilateral headache associated with tearing and ptosis. What shou...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Indomethacin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7482993197278912,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7586966498393759,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024227,
      "question_number": "50",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "What is the treatment for hypnic headache?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lithium",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5857142857142857,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7688694018164736,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024228,
      "question_number": "1",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q1. What is the physiology of cluster headache?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024229,
      "question_number": "96",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q96. A young lady experiences severe headaches with orgasm, and similar episodes occur every time. W...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Verapamil"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024230,
      "question_number": "173",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "What is the main neurotransmitter involved in migraine headaches?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Serotonin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024231,
      "question_number": "101",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q101. In a case of paroxysmal hemicrania, what is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Indomethacin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6559139784946236,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6268312172600551,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024232,
      "question_number": "114",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q114. A pregnant patient at 12 weeks gestational age with status migrainosus is asking about managem...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Subcutaneous sumatriptan"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024233,
      "question_number": "66",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q66. What is a contraindication for using NSAIDs in the 3rd trimester of pregnancy?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Premature closure of the ductus arteriosus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5382059800664452,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.680577849117175,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024234,
      "question_number": "57",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A young man has a history of headaches lasting 15\u201320 minutes, located over his orbit, associated wit...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. High flow Oxygen",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8650793650793651,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6966792957432583,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024235,
      "question_number": "72",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old female patient, known to have migraine, presented with a new headache unlike her usual...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. New daily persistent headache"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024236,
      "question_number": "56",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a history of unilateral headache, severe, lasting less than 5 minutes, with ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Topamax",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8708333333333333,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5270543212501329,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024237,
      "question_number": "31",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a headache that came out of the blue and has persisted for 3 months. What is...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. NDPH"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024238,
      "question_number": "54",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q54. A patient presents with a history of unilateral headache, severe, lasting less than 5 minutes, ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Short-lasting unilateral neuralgiform headache with conjunctival injection and tearing (SUNCT)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7016949152542373,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7393911961072762,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024239,
      "question_number": "10",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In a patient with migraine without aura, which of the following is the most relevant clinical pictur...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Throbbing quality",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6349206349206349,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6165927802406587,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024240,
      "question_number": "29",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a headache, normal brain CT, and lumbar puncture (LP) done by an intern that...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Traumatic Tap",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7578947368421053,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6697424067666282,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024241,
      "question_number": "14",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "What is the mechanism of action of Botox in the treatment of migraine headaches?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Glutamate inhibition",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6007604562737643,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.358277162115846,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024242,
      "question_number": "14",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of cluster headache, what additional finding is expected?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024243,
      "question_number": "183",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 50-year-old male with a history of migraine has recently been diagnosed with myocardial infarction...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Triptan"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024244,
      "question_number": "195",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q195. Which of the following is required for a diagnosis of pseudotumor cerebri syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024245,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "What is the second-line management for trigeminal neuralgia after carbamazepine?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Lamotrigine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.728110599078341,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3946594252093234,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024246,
      "question_number": "39",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A 67-year-old patient with a history of severe bilateral temporal headache and a high ESR of 30 pres...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Temporal arteritis causing anterior ischemic optic neuropathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6609808102345416,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6552315608919382,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024247,
      "question_number": "11",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A postpartum patient who underwent a C-section presents with a headache that worsens upon standing a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Blood patch"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024248,
      "question_number": "46",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "A young female presented with a severe headache; CT imaging shows pituitary apoplexy. What is the li...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pituitary apoplexy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7417218543046358,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.621732230852752,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024249,
      "question_number": "66",
      "subspecialty": "Headache",
      "question_text": "Q66. SUNCT and SUNA are characterized by sudden brief attacks of severe unilateral head pain in whic...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Orbital, peri-orbital, or temporal"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023782,
      "question_number": "72",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson's disease presented with peak dose dyskinesia. Which medication is most com...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Amantadine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8195718654434251,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6141931138984763,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023783,
      "question_number": "48",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with frequent falls and vertical gaze palsy shows tectal atrophy on Brain MRI. What condit...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Progressive Supranuclear Palsy (PSP)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6809651474530831,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.40432493953620713,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023784,
      "question_number": "70",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "The disruption within the Guillain-Mollaret triangle is associated with which type of palatal myoclo...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Symptomatic palatal myoclonus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5953757225433526,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7777410286092277,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023785,
      "question_number": "44",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with progressive supranuclear palsy (PSP) presents with impaired vertical gaze and axial r...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Progressive supranuclear palsy (PSP)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6773333333333333,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5905376344086022,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023786,
      "question_number": "82",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A Parkinson\u2019s patient on medication develops wearing-off phenomena. What is the mechanism?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Disease progression",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5986394557823129,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7064485081809432,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023787,
      "question_number": "46",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q46. Essential palatal myoclonus is frequently associated with which of the following characteristic...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Muscle agonist is the tensor veli palatini",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5208333333333334,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5856465282637431,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023788,
      "question_number": "4",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Axial brain CT shows bilateral caudate atrophy. What is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Huntington disease"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023789,
      "question_number": "47",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A young patient presents with dystonia and myoclonus. Which of the following is a characteristic fea...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Diurnal variation"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023790,
      "question_number": "221",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A female patient has a tremor and her father has a tremor; the father reported that his tremor is im...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Essential tremor",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7590027700831025,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7247592716178854,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023791,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Which type of palatal myoclonus is characterized by palatal movements due to contractions of the lev...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Symptomatic palatal myoclonus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7470817120622568,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4700244145040239,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023792,
      "question_number": "411",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a case of multiple system atrophy (MSA), what radiological finding is commonly associated?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Hot cross bun sign",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6617100371747212,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.747270686664626,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023793,
      "question_number": "361",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 62-year-old woman has experienced progressive unsteady gait and recurrent falls over the past 3 ye...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Progressive Supranuclear Palsy (PSP)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7942446043165468,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.24500339904826648,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023794,
      "question_number": "120",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "An elderly male patient with a history suggestive of Parkinson\u2019s disease (tremors, rigidity, and bra...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Levodopa/carbidopa trial",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8117359413202934,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7657038814863858,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023795,
      "question_number": "111",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 60-year-old male presented with a history of falls, dyskinesia, and depression. His sister died at...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Huntington's Disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7957559681697612,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5246472420743998,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023796,
      "question_number": "19",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old male presents with a history of symmetrical action tremor that improves with alcohol. ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Essential tremor",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7232876712328767,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6525817480494434,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023797,
      "question_number": "85",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A young man who is a law student in the last year of college has a long-standing intentional tremor ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Primidone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8818897637795275,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7689351805035899,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023798,
      "question_number": "107",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What medication is commonly used to treat essential tremor in a patient with asthma?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Primidone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7410714285714286,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7907882676443629,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023799,
      "question_number": "112",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is dyskinesia related to essential physiological conditions?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Y- Be",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.64,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.40523264456667163,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023800,
      "question_number": "157",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with parkinsonism, ataxia, falls, and orthostatic hypotension has an MRI showing a \"hot cr...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Multiple System Atrophy (MSA)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023801,
      "question_number": "136",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "If a patient with orthostatic tremor does not respond to clonazepam, what is the next step in manage...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Gabapentin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7803030303030303,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6177028686237304,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023802,
      "question_number": "65",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a patient on risperidone, how can you differentiate tardive dyskinesia from Huntington\u2019s disease?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Family history"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023803,
      "question_number": "161",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with bilateral action and postural tremors of the hands, and her father has a sim...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Propranolol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8252148997134671,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5894895271541453,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023804,
      "question_number": "194",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario, what is the next step in management?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023805,
      "question_number": "222",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q222. In a scenario of progressive supranuclear palsy (PSP), what is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Progressive supranuclear palsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6360424028268551,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.34371913441680885,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023806,
      "question_number": "203",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q203. What is the first-line treatment for Sydenham chorea?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Haloperidol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6298342541436464,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6789804211304027,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023807,
      "question_number": "3",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Case scenario of a patient with a 5-month history of unilateral rigidity, bradykinesia, tremor, and ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Levodopa",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7866323907455013,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3922051282051282,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023808,
      "question_number": "231",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson\u2019s disease has developed dystonia that is not improving with treatment. What...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Trihexyphenidyl",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7837837837837838,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.37683299926152547,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023809,
      "question_number": "5",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A scenario of a patient with parkinsonian features and vertical gaze palsy is most likely indicative...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Progressive Supranuclear Palsy (PSP)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6629526462395543,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7448441690557662,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023810,
      "question_number": "27",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a scenario about a patient with parkinsonism, urinary symptoms, and falls, what would you find on...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Hot cross bun sign",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7318840579710145,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6524902070509233,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023811,
      "question_number": "15",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with frequent falls and vertical gaze palsy. Brain MRI shows tectal atrophy. What...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Progressive supranuclear palsy (PSP)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6684931506849315,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6429667932455361,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023812,
      "question_number": "133",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In patients with progressive supranuclear palsy (PSP), what symptom does L-dopa primarily treat?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Bradykinesia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7104247104247104,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7931470622053581,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023813,
      "question_number": "104",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Regarding essential palatal myoclonus, which of the following statements is true?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023814,
      "question_number": "188",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "An approximately 70-year-old male patient has had recurrent falls and gait imbalance over the last 6...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Progressive Supranuclear Palsy (PSP)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7870967741935484,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3397626112759644,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023815,
      "question_number": "91",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with recurrent unilateral facial twitching, mostly triggered by anxiety, what is...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Botox"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023816,
      "question_number": "53",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson's disease presents with increased dyskinesia and parkinsonism. He is on Lev...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Decrease Levodopa and increase dopamine agonist"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023817,
      "question_number": "39",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient with a history of coronary artery bypass grafting (CABG) two years ago presents w...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Progressive Supranuclear Palsy (PSP)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7648183556405354,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7164827526283778,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023818,
      "question_number": "1",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Which condition is characterized by chorea, cognitive decline, and behavioral changes?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Huntington's disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.640926640926641,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7699060526721084,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023819,
      "question_number": "36",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the most common cause of hereditary chorea?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Huntington disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5235602094240838,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5377827365858606,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023820,
      "question_number": "181",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 61\u2010year\u2010old male with a 2\u2010year history of limb tremors and bradykinesia has postural instability a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Corticobasal degeneration (CBD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7309417040358744,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7728043066493869,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023821,
      "question_number": "38",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with essential tremor and asthma, what is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Primidone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6808510638297872,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7842499774225594,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023822,
      "question_number": "87",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q87. A patient with recurrent unilateral eye twitching and sometimes mouth twitching, with no histor...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Botox injections"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023823,
      "question_number": "96",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a case of corticobasal degeneration, where is the involvement seen on MRI?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023824,
      "question_number": "136",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson's Disease (PD) experiences excessive sleep and motor fluctuations. What med...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Selegiline",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8090614886731392,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6856862584811575,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023825,
      "question_number": "134",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q134. Oculopalatal myoclonus is caused by a lesion involving which pathway?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Dentate-rubro-olivary pathway"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023826,
      "question_number": "334",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A scenario suggests a diagnosis of dyt11. What type of myoclonus is associated with this condition, ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Essential myoclonus"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023827,
      "question_number": "195",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Parkinson's disease experiencing motor function issues and dyskinesia, what is the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Decrease Sinemet and add a dopamine agonist"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023828,
      "question_number": "335",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson\u2019s disease for 7 years presents with severe disabling dyskinesia on medical ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. DBS to GPI",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8221153846153846,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6463718934025352,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023829,
      "question_number": "14",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson's disease presents with peak-dose dyskinesia. What medication is commonly u...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Amantadine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8115015974440895,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3829632326174008,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023830,
      "question_number": "106",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient has a history of frequent falls, limited vertical gaze, and parkinsonian features...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Progressive supranuclear palsy (PSP)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6575342465753424,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7753486618921975,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023831,
      "question_number": "29",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A female patient reports throat discomfort and a \u201cclicking tinnitus\u201d that subsides during her sleep....",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Palatal tremor",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7740667976424361,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7920046834490256,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023832,
      "question_number": "117",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson\u2019s disease is experiencing motor function issues and dyskinesia. What is the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Decrease Sinemet and add a dopamine agonist",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7067307692307693,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6110574134931375,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023833,
      "question_number": "116",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "For a patient with orthostatic tremor who is not tolerating clonazepam, what is the second-line trea...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Pramipexole",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7735191637630662,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7248271997011022,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023834,
      "question_number": "177",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 34-year-old female was brought by her family due to a history of abnormal movements of her hands a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Huntington's repeat",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8318356867779204,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5136132902630365,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023835,
      "question_number": "81",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q81. In Progressive Supranuclear Palsy (PSP), which symptom will improve with treatment?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Bradykinesia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6775510204081633,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6616290168628699,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023836,
      "question_number": "118",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 62-year-old male has two episodes of asymmetric tremors in the left arm. What investigation should...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Dopamine transporter scan"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023837,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with diabetes mellitus presents with tremor at rest, during action, and with kinetic movem...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Rubral Tremor",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7632311977715878,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.740165128703254,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023838,
      "question_number": "123",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A female patient presents with bilateral upper limb dystonia that improves with alcohol. Which of th...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Clonazepam"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023839,
      "question_number": "10",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Regarding enhanced physiological tremor, which statement is correct?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023840,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 14-year-old girl, medically free, has episodes of jerky movements of the right upper limb followed...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Paroxysmal kinesigenic dyskinesia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8547297297297297,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.216340817894647,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023841,
      "question_number": "126",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the best treatment for peak dose dyskinesia in patients with Parkinson\u2019s disease?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Amantadine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023842,
      "question_number": "84",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A Parkinson\u2019s patient takes Levodopa/Carbidopa 250/25 mg QID and is complaining of wearing off in te...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Increase frequency to 5 times per day",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7834645669291339,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.49720189410245375,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023843,
      "question_number": "200",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson\u2019s disease presents with increased dyskinesia and parkinsonism. He is on Lev...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Decrease Levodopa and increase dopamine agonist",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6107784431137725,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5827324108360943,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023844,
      "question_number": "110",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q110. Which of the following statements is true regarding symptomatic palatal myoclonus?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023845,
      "question_number": "155",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the benefit of deep brain stimulation of the subthalamic nucleus?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Reduction of dopaminergic medication",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6428571428571429,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6680937818552497,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023846,
      "question_number": "233",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Deep brain stimulation (DBS) of the globus pallidus interna (GPi) may be more effective than DBS of ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Dyskinesias",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8444444444444444,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6510919248349416,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023847,
      "question_number": "138",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q138. What is the next investigation for a patient with orthostatic tremor?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. NCS/EMG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6320346320346321,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6218271604938271,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023848,
      "question_number": "88",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with idiopathic Parkinson disease, complaining of hallucinations, has mild rigidity, brady...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Pramipexole",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8341708542713567,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6152418512933534,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023849,
      "question_number": "189",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A typical case of orthostatic tremor is presented. What is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Clonazepam",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7345132743362832,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7640407438557144,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023850,
      "question_number": "169",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q169. What is the recommended treatment for a patient with Parkinson's Disease (PD) who has features...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Dopamine agonist"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023851,
      "question_number": "325",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A male patient, 85 years old, presents with gait freezing, cognitive changes, bradykinesia, and urin...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Start levodopa",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.821917808219178,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7726797537460797,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023852,
      "question_number": "107",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q107. A patient who works as a chef has been complaining of a months-long history of upper limb rest...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Carbidopa/levodopa",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7960057061340942,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6394852996184633,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023853,
      "question_number": "112",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q112. Which of the following Parkinsonian disorders commonly presents with asymmetrical features?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. CBD",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7983193277310925,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4521219876306249,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023854,
      "question_number": "456",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q456. A female presents with action and intention tremor, dropping things, and a slightly asymmetric...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Essential tremor",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7604166666666666,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7381910612158441,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023855,
      "question_number": "202",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the treatment for hemifacial spasm?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Botox"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023856,
      "question_number": "28",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of orthostatic tremor not responding to clonazepam, which of the following is a second...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Gabapentin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7972027972027972,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7795443979544397,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023857,
      "question_number": "170",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 70-year-old male presents with a history of left arm dystonia, bradykinesia, and myoclonus. He mov...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Corticobasal degeneration (CBD)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023858,
      "question_number": "151",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 60-year-old male presents with recent onset of progressive difficulty using the right hand. Clinic...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Corticobasal degeneration"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023859,
      "question_number": "351",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q351. A patient with tremor-predominant Parkinson\u2019s disease on levodopa/carbidopa (LD/CD) 250/25 mg ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Decrease individual dose with increasing frequency",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7043090638930164,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.48373946915481475,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023860,
      "question_number": "17",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 50-year-old male came with a history suggestive of Parkinson\u2019s disease (rigidity, tremors, bradyki...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Levodopa/Carbidopa",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.75,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5158600392413342,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023861,
      "question_number": "100",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What type of focal dystonia improves when touching the face?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Torticollis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6178010471204188,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6255264603552463,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023862,
      "question_number": "2",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 14-year-old girl, medically free, has episodes of jerky movements of the right upper limb followed...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Paroxysmal kinesigenic dyskinesia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.805111821086262,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6085657370517928,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023863,
      "question_number": "167",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 70-year-old female with a known case of Parkinson\u2019s disease has had stable symptoms for the last 6...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Deep brain stimulation (DBS)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8412017167381974,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.666533943858252,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023864,
      "question_number": "244",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the treatment for Sydenham chorea?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Haloperidol"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023865,
      "question_number": "210",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Which of the following symptoms is the most common side effect of botulinum toxin injection for cerv...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Dysphagia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7174603174603175,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6122900904225872,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023866,
      "question_number": "10",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old male with a history of action tremor presents with symmetrical tremors that improve wi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Essential tremor",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7527839643652561,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7978781781598683,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023867,
      "question_number": "93",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient presents with imbalance that improves with walking. On examination, you find gait...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. NCS/EMG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5922948073701843,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023868,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Which of the following describes orthostatic tremor?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023869,
      "question_number": "115",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 42-year-old female has gait difficulty and feels very dizzy, but when she wakes, she no longer has...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Clonazepam"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023870,
      "question_number": "108",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with lower limb tremor that starts when she stands up and does not improve when s...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Clonazepam",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8948306595365418,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6522575534683717,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023871,
      "question_number": "227",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q227. Which of the following is most likely to be associated with essential palatal myoclonus?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "C. Essential palatal myoclonus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6072607260726073,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7314751869476547,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023872,
      "question_number": "24",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q24. Thalamotomy in Parkinson\u2019s Disease (PD) is expected to improve which of the following symptoms?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Tremor",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7441860465116279,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7329830973047053,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023873,
      "question_number": "24",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A man who presented with abnormal movement (from a psychiatry hospital) and is unable to sit still. ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Akathisia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023874,
      "question_number": "321",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Progressive Supranuclear Palsy (PSP), which symptom is most likely to improve with...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Bradykinesia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7581699346405228,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5231370845101021,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023875,
      "question_number": "192",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with schizophrenia is unable to sit and is on antipsychotic medication. What is the likely...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Akathisia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023876,
      "question_number": "26",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 16-year-old female patient presented with jerking movements that improved with wine. Her father ha...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Myoclonus dystonia DYT11",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7427055702917772,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6536785439630863,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023877,
      "question_number": "97",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient presents with imbalance that improves with walking. On examination, you find gait...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Clonazepam",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8618266978922716,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6189408314645506,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023878,
      "question_number": "162",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Levodopa",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023879,
      "question_number": "45",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In Huntington's disease, how many gene repeats are typically present?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. More than 48 repeats",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5491803278688525,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7631938408046691,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023880,
      "question_number": "116",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 35-year-old male presented to the clinic with complaints of atonic jerks at age 10. He has a histo...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Neuroacanthocytosis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023881,
      "question_number": "153",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the site of deep brain stimulation (DBS) for tremor?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thalamus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5507246376811594,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7952732644017725,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023882,
      "question_number": "92",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient has dystonia of the lower limbs and a positive family history of similar symptoms. She was...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Levodopa/Carbidopa",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7991452991452992,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5136033043009787,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023883,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In the scenario of orthostatic tremor, what diagnostic tests should be performed?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Nerve Conduction Study (NCS) and Electromyography (EMG)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023884,
      "question_number": "20",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q20. A case scenario of a patient suggestive of Corticobasal Degeneration (CBD) is presented, with a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Asymmetrical parietal atrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7024608501118568,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.37221983067872005,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023885,
      "question_number": "232",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A Parkinson's patient on medication developed wearing off phenomena; what is the mechanism?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Disease progression",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5993265993265994,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5728006985374372,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023886,
      "question_number": "73",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In refractory essential tremor, which structure is the target for deep brain stimulation (DBS)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thalamus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7027027027027027,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6953357591796229,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023887,
      "question_number": "121",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q121. (Source: Part I 2023mcqs.txt) A young lady presented to the outpatient clinic with a history o...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Improvement with ethanol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8692579505300353,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.695045695045695,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023888,
      "question_number": "32",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a scenario about essential myoclonus relieved by alcohol, which of the following is the most like...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Essential myoclonus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6915887850467289,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5860230143137806,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023889,
      "question_number": "8",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Parkinson's Disease (PD) on Sinemet, who has shown improvement in motor control an...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Stop the pramipexole"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023890,
      "question_number": "205",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a patient with progressive supranuclear palsy (PSP) receiving Sinemet, which symptom is likely to...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Bradykinesia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023891,
      "question_number": "16",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the male-to-female ratio in the inheritance of paroxysmal kinesigenic dyskinesia?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. 1:1",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8461538461538461,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7325439858360075,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023892,
      "question_number": "83",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the treatment for Sydenham chorea?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Haloperidol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5503355704697986,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5575456337303968,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023893,
      "question_number": "196",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 16-year-old boy presents with dystonic posturing and myoclonic jerks predominantly affecting his u...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Clonazepam"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023894,
      "question_number": "163",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Multiple System Atrophy (MSA)",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023895,
      "question_number": "88",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q88. A patient with a known case of Parkinson's disease on levodopa/carbidopa describes having recur...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. On and off phenomena",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8025210084033614,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4911332179930796,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023896,
      "question_number": "98",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q98. A young patient with lip biting and face and limb dystonia has a blood smear showing abnormal R...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Neuroacanthocytosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7064439140811456,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7485754985754985,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023897,
      "question_number": "12",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q12. A young patient presents with dystonia and myoclonus. What characteristic is likely associated ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Alcohol-responsive",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7090909090909091,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7273634820804632,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023898,
      "question_number": "54",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q54. A patient with typical orthostatic tremor is being treated. What is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Clonazepam",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7710843373493976,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6886575342465754,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023899,
      "question_number": "101",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the diagnosis for a clear case of Parkinson\u2019s Disease (PD)?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Parkinson\u2019s Disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5818181818181818,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5088232834322991,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023900,
      "question_number": "9",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is a common trigger for paroxysmal kinesigenic dyskinesia?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Stress",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.730593607305936,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.006226446010158938,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023901,
      "question_number": "108",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson's disease on multiple agents has developed hallucinations. What is the firs...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Stop amantadine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.725609756097561,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5928071928071929,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023902,
      "question_number": "193",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with essential tremor and asthma, what is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Primidone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6632124352331606,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.681733360978644,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023903,
      "question_number": "448",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 32-year-old female with a history of Parkinson\u2019s disease presents with worsening symptoms, includi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Dopamine agonist",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.804040404040404,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7750322051762502,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023904,
      "question_number": "2",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A female patient presents with a hand tremor that improves with alcohol, and there is a family histo...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Essential tremor",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.754257907542579,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.758197410459055,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023905,
      "question_number": "80",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A female patient has a tremor, and her father also has a tremor. The father reports that his tremor ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Essential tremor",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7520435967302452,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7500639986346957,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023906,
      "question_number": "171",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson's disease on Sinemet every 4 hours and Selegiline complains of wearing off ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Increase the frequency of Sinemet",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7465618860510805,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4052643028061779,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023907,
      "question_number": "23",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old child with dopa-responsive dystonia started with foot dystonia and progressed to gener...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. DYT5",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8938547486033519,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6953802703247932,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023908,
      "question_number": "33",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A young female patient presents to the clinic with head tremor and neck pain. On exam, she has torti...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. She has a good response to sensory trick"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023909,
      "question_number": "87",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old female presents with parkinsonism and worsening dystonia. She had a similar presentati...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Levodopa",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7757009345794392,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7167908811924595,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023910,
      "question_number": "89",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 68-year-old male presented to the clinic due to a history of recurrent falls. He has a history of ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Progressive supranuclear palsy (PSP)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8268733850129198,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3917104495037945,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023911,
      "question_number": "286",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Palatal Myoclonus with continuous ear sound in a young male. What is the most likely explanation?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. It is palatal myoclonus and it may continue in sleep",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5413105413105413,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5931848467542357,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023912,
      "question_number": "156",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A case presents with axial rigidity and parkinsonism, and the patient has upgaze palsy. What is the ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Progressive supranuclear palsy (PSP).",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6532951289398281,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.45231444533120513,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023913,
      "question_number": "145",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q145. A Parkinson's patient on levodopa/carbidopa 25/250 Q4 and selegiline for 7 years has started t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Amantadine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7893805309734513,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3055555555555556,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023914,
      "question_number": "505",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A Parkinson's disease patient on Sinemet every 4 hours and selegiline complains of wearing off 2.5 h...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Increase the frequency of Sinemet",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7229862475442044,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4972839035547508,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023915,
      "question_number": "158",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q158. Corticobasal Degeneration (CBD)",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023916,
      "question_number": "90",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A young female has recurrent muscle (or neck) spasms triggered by sudden neck movement. What is the ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Carbamazepine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023917,
      "question_number": "97",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson's disease and dystonia is not improving with treatment. What is the most ap...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. DBS of the globus pallidus internus (GPi)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6629213483146067,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6312209500056682,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023918,
      "question_number": "160",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 70-year-old male patient with a history of Parkinson\u2019s disease for 10 years, who has been respondi...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Multiple System Atrophy (MSA)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023919,
      "question_number": "164",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A male patient presents with parkinsonism and swallowing difficulty, and MRI shows atrophy of the mi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Progressive Supranuclear Palsy (PSP)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6898263027295285,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5409727947238252,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023920,
      "question_number": "182",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson\u2019s Disease for 6 years on Sinemet and experiencing depressed mood, changes i...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "B. Add Amantadine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7907949790794979,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5107036771484175,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023921,
      "question_number": "51",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with orthostatic tremor not tolerating clonazepam, what is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Pramipexole",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7136563876651982,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6447460800374444,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023922,
      "question_number": "36",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 17-year-old boy has developed multiple verbal and motor tics since the age of 11. What is the diag...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Tourette syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6775244299674267,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.42500966370313104,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023923,
      "question_number": "112",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Progressive Supranuclear Palsy (PSP) receiving Sinemet, which symptom is likely to...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Rigidity",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7608695652173914,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.711913518332776,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023924,
      "question_number": "135",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a patient with hemifacial spasm, what is the most common treatment option?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Botox",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7211538461538461,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7244457241577886,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023925,
      "question_number": "119",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient presented with abnormal limb movement. He described that his left upper limb seem...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Corticobasal degeneration"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023926,
      "question_number": "39",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 16-year-old had dystonia that improved with wine, and her father has the same symptoms. What is th...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Clonazepam"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023927,
      "question_number": "197",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with orthostatic tremor not tolerating clonazepam, what is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "C. Pramipexole",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7136563876651982,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7758064516129032,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023928,
      "question_number": "132",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with dystonia, tremor, and Parkinsonism. MRI shows bilateral basal ganglia and br...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. D-penicillamine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8130841121495327,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5844927182491254,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023929,
      "question_number": "22",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q22. What is the appropriate management for a Parkinson\u2019s disease patient on Sinemet 5 times daily w...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Add COMT inhibitors"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023930,
      "question_number": "225",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with orthostatic tremor is not tolerating clonazepam. What is the second-line treatment?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Pramipexol"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023931,
      "question_number": "223",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a patient with essential tremor and asthma, which medication is commonly used?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Primidone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7247706422018348,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7863677950594693,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023932,
      "question_number": "47",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A Parkinson's disease patient on levodopa/Carbidopa every 4 hours experiences reoccurrence of rigidi...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. On & off phenomena",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7816593886462883,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7925460722742715,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023933,
      "question_number": "13",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Which treatment is commonly used for paroxysmal exertion-induced dyskinesia?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Acetazolamide",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7009345794392523,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5991178323881537,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023934,
      "question_number": "166",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 70-year-old male patient has a history of urinary retention, syncope, and memory impairment. He la...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Multiple System Atrophy (MSA)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7391304347826086,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6461489140017632,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023935,
      "question_number": "165",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 70-year-old male patient presents with recurrent falls and gait imbalance over the last 6 months. ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Progressive Supranuclear Palsy (PSP)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7857142857142857,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4931672720982529,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023936,
      "question_number": "134",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the first-line treatment for Sydenham chorea?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Haloperidol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5875706214689266,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5972168534982605,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023937,
      "question_number": "118",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 67-year-old man with a 3-year history of Parkinson disease has had increasingly distressing proble...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Pimavanserin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9127324749642346,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6906379765949415,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023938,
      "question_number": "8",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q8. A patient exhibits palatal abnormal movements that are fast, rhythmic, and persist during sleep....",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Symptomatic palatal myoclonus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.702247191011236,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3760506022008491,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023939,
      "question_number": "11",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the typical age of onset for paroxysmal nonkinesigenic dyskinesia?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. 1-40 years",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6636363636363637,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.720100045475216,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023940,
      "question_number": "39",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Pathology showed Lewy bodies. What is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lewy body dementia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5025125628140703,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6470009832841691,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023941,
      "question_number": "60",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with schizophrenia on antipsychotics presents with orolingual dystonia. What is the diagno...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Tardive Dyskinesia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6644951140065146,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.43826026078585806,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023942,
      "question_number": "224",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old female patient presents with parkinsonism and worsening dystonia. She had a similar pr...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Levodopa",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8042553191489362,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6885216291881152,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023943,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the PET finding in CBDG?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023944,
      "question_number": "118",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a girl with Sydenham chorea, what laboratory test is indicated?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. ASO titer"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023945,
      "question_number": "189",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q189. A girl presents in childhood with progressive, isolated limb dystonia and no parkinsonian feat...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. DYT 1"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023946,
      "question_number": "26",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the recommended treatment for cervical dystonia?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Botox",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6285714285714286,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7958599798047795,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023947,
      "question_number": "9",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the pathology associated with Multiple System Atrophy (MSA)?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Glial cytoplasmic inclusions"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023948,
      "question_number": "4",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient diagnosed with Parkinson\u2019s disease 6 years ago presents with troublesome dyskinesia and is...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Amantadine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7942583732057417,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6474775611265862,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023949,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a scenario involving essential tremor and asthma treatment, which medication is commonly used?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Primidone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.76,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6168915977361776,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023950,
      "question_number": "66",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the treatment for hemifacial spasm?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Botox"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023951,
      "question_number": "79",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Best to explain orthostatic tremor:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023952,
      "question_number": "116",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 70-year-old man with Parkinson\u2019s disease has become progressively more demented over the past year...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Quetiapine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023953,
      "question_number": "99",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q99. A young female has a Kayser\u2013Fleischer ring on slit lamp exam and presents with parkinsonism and...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. D-Penicillamine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7878787878787878,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6835676423138972,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023954,
      "question_number": "245",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A young girl with PKAN presents with dystonia and an MRI showing central hyperintensity. What is the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. PKAN",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7622377622377622,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5677976871266998,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023955,
      "question_number": "6",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario of paroxysmal kinesigenic dyskinesia, what is the most appropriate management o...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Phenytoin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023956,
      "question_number": "99",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson\u2019s Disease for 7 years on Sinemet has started to wean off the medication. Wh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Disease progression",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7064935064935065,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5249009133206962,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023957,
      "question_number": "191",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q191. A 46-year-old female patient presented with jerky movements that improved with wine. Her fathe...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Myoclonus dystonia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023958,
      "question_number": "226",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson\u2019s disease on pramipexole develops visual hallucinations. What is the next b...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Stop pramipexole",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6855524079320113,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5139993463340233,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023959,
      "question_number": "374",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a typical scenario of left hemifacial spasm, what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Botox",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6666666666666666,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5740291262135923,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023960,
      "question_number": "46",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a patient with parkinsonism symptoms not responding to Sinemet, which condition is characterized ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Corticobasal degeneration (CBD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6683417085427136,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.36293436293436293,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023961,
      "question_number": "222",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In Progressive Supranuclear Palsy (PSP), which symptom will improve with treatment?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Bradykinesia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023962,
      "question_number": "507",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A female with abnormal movements in the form of arching back had an EEG that was normal during the e...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Psychogenic movement disorder",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.696969696969697,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6196552059998052,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023963,
      "question_number": "25",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a case of an elderly patient with symptoms suggestive of Multiple System Atrophy (MSA), which of ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Autonomic insufficiency",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.714975845410628,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7311388264158659,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023964,
      "question_number": "201",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with typical orthostatic tremor. What is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Clonazepam"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023965,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 72-year-old woman is brought to the clinic by her family due to trouble walking. She reports feeli...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Orthostatic Tremor",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8342440801457195,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6799533799533799,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023966,
      "question_number": "131",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q131. Who is more likely to benefit from dopamine agonists compared to levodopa?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023967,
      "question_number": "89",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with hand stiffness, usually during writing. Her father had the same symptoms. Wh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Myoclonus dystonia syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7318435754189944,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.39950086388942213,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023968,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient presented with peak dose dyskinesia that is bothering him and affecting his daily...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Add Amantadine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.847682119205298,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5990187332738626,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023969,
      "question_number": "127",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient exhibits on-off palatal movements accompanied by click sounds, which resolve with sleep. W...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Essential palatal myoclonus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7183908045977011,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7423740630991807,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023970,
      "question_number": "135",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a clear scenario of essential palatal myoclonus, what is the recommended investigation?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. MRI of the brain",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6068965517241379,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.762684124386252,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023971,
      "question_number": "248",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A case of essential tremor in a young law student with bronchial asthma is presented. What is the mo...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Primidone"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023972,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with no significant medical history experiences episodes of jerky movements of the right u...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Paroxysmal kinesigenic dyskinesia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023973,
      "question_number": "229",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of hemifacial spasm, what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Botox",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6090909090909091,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7390246276647523,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023974,
      "question_number": "185",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a case of spontaneous generalized chorea, which of the following options describes the phenomenol...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Chorea"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023975,
      "question_number": "30",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A question describes symptomatic palatal myoclonus and asks what to do (not improved with sleep). Wh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. MRI of the brain"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023976,
      "question_number": "154",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q154. A patient on metoclopramide developed dystonia, what is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Trihexyphenidyl"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023977,
      "question_number": "125",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A case of essential tremor is noted with a frequency of 6 Hz that improves with alcohol and has a fa...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Essential tremor",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7642276422764228,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6912724306688418,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023978,
      "question_number": "412",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a scenario suggestive of Wilson's disease with Parkinsonism and dystonia, what is the recommended...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Penicillamine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7465753424657534,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7737789203084833,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023979,
      "question_number": "150",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 67-year-old patient known to have Parkinson's disease presents with sleep disorders. Which sleep d...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Restless legs syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7592592592592593,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4023634804155151,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023980,
      "question_number": "114",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Tourette's syndrome and ADHD, which medication is appropriate for treatment (Cloni...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Atomoxetine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7938461538461539,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.42318840579710143,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023981,
      "question_number": "459",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q459. What imaging finding is associated with corticobasal degeneration (CBD)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023982,
      "question_number": "398",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a patient with corticobasal degeneration (CBD), what would a PET scan most likely reveal?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023983,
      "question_number": "223",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Inclusion with alpha synucleinopathy contains:",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Lewy body",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.569620253164557,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5869541304586954,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023984,
      "question_number": "168",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the treatment for a patient with Parkinson's Disease (PD) who has features of Restless Legs ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Dopamine agonist",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.738255033557047,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.49738953266267666,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023985,
      "question_number": "515",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with mild parkinsonism over a few months, a history of urinary incontinence for s...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Lumbar puncture"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023986,
      "question_number": "39",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the best way to confirm the diagnosis of synucleinopathy?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Neuropathologically",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6274509803921569,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5119945939858093,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023987,
      "question_number": "42",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A Parkinson's patient came with increased hallucinations and memory loss; what is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Rivastigmine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7580645161290323,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6769850718930305,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023988,
      "question_number": "227",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson\u2019s disease and excessive sleep with motor fluctuations is experiencing diffi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Amantadine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8181818181818182,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7304834715193281,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023989,
      "question_number": "109",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "For a patient with rubral tremor associated with multiple sclerosis, what is the recommended treatme...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Surgical treatment"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023990,
      "question_number": "85",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q85. In a case scenario of hemiballismus, what is the localization?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Subthalamic nucleus (STN)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6153846153846154,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7135083662086791,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023991,
      "question_number": "490",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q490. Which of the following disorders is associated with Parkinson's disease treated with dopamine ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Restless Legs Syndrome (RLS)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023992,
      "question_number": "287",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Which is a Tauopathy?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. PSP",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5555555555555556,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6304621188305565,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023993,
      "question_number": "59",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a case of familial Parkinson disease, which gene is associated with autosomal dominant inheritanc...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. LRRK2 (PARK8)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8407960199004975,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6272561346582843,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023994,
      "question_number": "136",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a scenario suggestive of Wilson\u2019s disease with Kayser-Fleischer ring and MRI features, what is th...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Ceruloplasmin level",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7803468208092486,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.022610483042137718,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023995,
      "question_number": "139",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "For a patient with dyt11, what is the first-line treatment if the condition improves with alcohol?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Clonazepam"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023996,
      "question_number": "175",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A pediatric patient had mental retardation, tremor, and ataxia; his sister had ovarian insufficiency...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Bilateral cerebellar hyperintensity",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.680306905370844,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6581647902759789,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023997,
      "question_number": "40",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A middle-aged lady presents with problems with attention, tremor, and progressive ataxia. What is th...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Wilson's disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6997084548104956,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6006668376506796,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023998,
      "question_number": "163",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 34-year-old female is brought in by her family due to a history of abnormal movements of her hands...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Genetic testing",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8619791666666666,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7478330178340141,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023999,
      "question_number": "160",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q160. A 50-year-old male patient has a history of cognitive impairment for 6 months, accompanied by ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. CAG repeat"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024000,
      "question_number": "153",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q153. A young man with orolingual dystonia, associated with cognitive deficit, has no family history...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Peripheral blood film for acanthocytes",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.702247191011236,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6475621890547264,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024001,
      "question_number": "46",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q46. What will confirm the diagnosis of Wilson\u2019s disease?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Liver biopsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5116279069767442,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5990824661519526,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024002,
      "question_number": "190",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A case of Huntington\u2019s disease shows CT brain imaging with head of caudate atrophy. What is the expe...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. 48 CAG repeats",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7877094972067039,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7882301273605622,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024003,
      "question_number": "125",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A case presents with ataxia, slow saccades, and optic atrophy. Which type of spinocerebellar ataxia ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. SCA 7",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8581560283687943,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.49736673089274247,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024004,
      "question_number": "156",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q156. Hallervorden-Spatz syndrome is associated with which gene?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. PKAN-1"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024005,
      "question_number": "51",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with progressive cerebellar ataxia, optic atrophy, sensorineural hearing loss, an...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Spinocerebellar Ataxia 7 (SCA7)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7547169811320755,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6393055948674403,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024006,
      "question_number": "61",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A child presented with dystonia and Parkinsonism. Brain MRI reported bilateral hyperintensity in the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pantothenate kinase-associated neurodegeneration",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7205882352941176,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6691430087556381,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024007,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with features of Friedreich Ataxia is asked about the associated gene. What is the gene in...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. FXN gene with GAA trinucleotide repeat expansion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6885245901639344,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7737556561085973,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024008,
      "question_number": "72",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with muscle weakness, optic atrophy, hearing loss, and a family history of a simi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Spinocerebellar Ataxia Type 7 (SCA7)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7012987012987013,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.784985563041386,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024009,
      "question_number": "96",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a girl with Sydenham chorea, which test is most relevant to confirm the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. ASO titer"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024010,
      "question_number": "164",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "The most common familial gene mutation associated with Parkinson's disease is:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. LRRK2",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7938144329896907,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6321698804002929,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024011,
      "question_number": "114",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with a known case of diabetes mellitus presents with axial and appendicular ataxia and has...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. GAA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9215686274509803,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5025548542230237,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024012,
      "question_number": "167",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q167. A 16-year-old female presented with oculomotor apraxia and ataxia; she had normal immunoglobul...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Oculomotor apraxia type 2"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024013,
      "question_number": "277",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 50-year-old female presents with complaints of imbalance and tremor. MRI shows bilateral hyperinte...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Fragile X syndrome [FXTAS]",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7104072398190046,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7212433360440951,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024014,
      "question_number": "146",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 75-year-old patient with progressive cognitive decline, chorea, and ataxia has no children, and hi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Huntington's disease"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024015,
      "question_number": "285",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the most common familial gene associated with Parkinson's disease?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. LRRK2",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7934782608695652,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.13067484662576687,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024016,
      "question_number": "198",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Dystonia with myoclonus is most commonly associated with which genetic mutation?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. SGCE (DYT11)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024017,
      "question_number": "22",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q22. A 50-year-old female presents with recent intention tremor and memory problems, with MRI findin...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Fragile X syndrome [FXTAS]"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024018,
      "question_number": "252",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a case of Wilson's disease with Kayser-Fleischer ring and pyramidal signs, which test confirms th...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Biopsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7665505226480837,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6665865962046601,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024019,
      "question_number": "110",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of a girl with dystonia and no Parkinsonism features, which genetic mutation is most l...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. DYT 1",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8013937282229965,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7273729670127722,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024020,
      "question_number": "221",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Which genetic mutation is associated with dystonia accompanied by myoclonus?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. SGCE (DYT11)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7352941176470589,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7472343590220322,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024021,
      "question_number": "90",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with a history of abnormal movements and falls, which interfere with his daily routine, is...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CAG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9259259259259259,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6513020833333333,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024022,
      "question_number": "128",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What is the recommended treatment for Wilson's disease during pregnancy?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Trientine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6729857819905213,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6639476429858674,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024023,
      "question_number": "4",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In the case of Sydenham's chorea, what is the recommended action?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. ASO titer",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5675675675675675,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.788544624120479,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024024,
      "question_number": "291",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 78-year-old female presents with ataxia for one year and mild cognitive impairment. MRI showed cer...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Premutation fragile X syndrome [FXTAS]"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024025,
      "question_number": "73",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "An 11-year-old boy comes to the office with his parents because of a 14-month history of motor and v...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Tourette syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8125,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.26409064497385243,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024026,
      "question_number": "199",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient was in a psychiatric hospital and developed abnormal movements. What is the likely diagnos...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Tardive dyskinesia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024027,
      "question_number": "247",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A young female has Kayser-Fleischer rings on slit lamp exam and presents with parkinsonism and dysto...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Penicillamine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7911392405063291,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6000516395558998,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024028,
      "question_number": "14",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "Q14. Sydenham chorea",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024029,
      "question_number": "173",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 9-year-old boy, previously healthy, develops abnormal movements of the upper and lower limbs with ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Sydenham chorea",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8181818181818182,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6595992791264709,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024030,
      "question_number": "102",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient known to have psychiatric symptoms on antipsychotic medication for a long time presented w...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Tardive dyskinesia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7643020594965675,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6274811772758385,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024031,
      "question_number": "13",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 9-year-old boy has a history of 14 months of vocal and motor tics, along with a history of OCD. Wh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Tourette syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6935483870967742,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.16985203452527745,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024032,
      "question_number": "15",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A 12-year-old male patient had a runny nose two weeks ago. He presents with abnormal movements, and ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Sydenham chorea",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7920792079207921,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7207960199004975,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024033,
      "question_number": "178",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In a clear scenario of vascular Parkinson's disease, what should be done?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Control hypertension",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6068376068376068,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.64029094115054,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024034,
      "question_number": "42",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "In the management of Tic disorders and ADHD, which medication is commonly prescribed?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Methylphenidate"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024035,
      "question_number": "183",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "What test is associated with Sydenham chorea in a girl?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024036,
      "question_number": "181",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient who was in a psychiatric hospital developed abnormal movements. What is the most likely di...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Tardive dyskinesia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024037,
      "question_number": "241",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "An elderly female patient wakes up with abnormal left arm and leg involuntary movements. Before she ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Sub-thalamic",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9237668161434978,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7646733111849391,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024038,
      "question_number": "29",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with schizophrenia is unable to sit and is on antipsychotic medication. What is the likely...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Akathisia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8226415094339623,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7771804717498628,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024039,
      "question_number": "36",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with schizophrenia on antipsychotics presents with involuntary, sustained contractions of ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Tardive Dyskinesia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7553444180522565,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6553001080080234,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024040,
      "question_number": "20",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson's disease presents with hallucinations and forgetfulness. What is the most ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Clozapine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8126984126984127,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6254366915305448,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024041,
      "question_number": "117",
      "subspecialty": "Movement Disorders",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with blunted affect and rigidity after carbon monoxide exposure. What is the most...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Neuroleptic malignant syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024250,
      "question_number": "16",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Pseudorossettes are characteristic of which of the following tumors?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024251,
      "question_number": "136",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q136. What is the characteristic of diffuse astrocytoma grade 2?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024252,
      "question_number": "141",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Patient with intracranial mass crossing the corpus callosum; what is the histology you will see?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024253,
      "question_number": "127",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Dexamethasone is best indicated for which type of edema?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024254,
      "question_number": "128",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q128. Histopathology for the attached MRI shows which of the following features indicative of Gliobl...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024255,
      "question_number": "341",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old female smoker presents with sensory neuropathy and motor symptoms. A chest X-ray shows...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Lung cancer"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024256,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Dexamethasone is helpful in which of the following clinical scenarios?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024257,
      "question_number": "40",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with headache and bilateral 6th nerve palsy with papilledema, and a red mass is s...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Chordoma"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024258,
      "question_number": "179",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Which brain tumor is characterized by histopathological pseudorosettes?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024259,
      "question_number": "98",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A case scenario involves a patient with a brain tumor. The MRI brain report shows a focal lesion wit...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Glioblastoma multiforme",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8810572687224669,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7998099085184746,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024260,
      "question_number": "52",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q52. A butterfly mass with necrosis in the center is observed. What is the most likely grade of this...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Grade 4 glioma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7342657342657343,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5551488772381047,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024261,
      "question_number": "4",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A brain lesion with a pathologic description of central necrosis is most likely which type of tumor?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024262,
      "question_number": "14",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A brain tumor with histology of pseudorosette is most likely:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024263,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A child has a 3-week history of lower limb weakness. MRI of the spine shows T4 and T8 intramedullary...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Astrocytoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7920792079207921,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6359202714164546,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024264,
      "question_number": "60",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q60. A brain MRI shows a mass originating from the fourth ventricle with histology showing pseudoros...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Ependymoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7590361445783133,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7925250683682771,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024265,
      "question_number": "126",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient with a tumor in the lateral ventricle is most likely to have which type of tumor?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024266,
      "question_number": "23",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Neurofibromatosis type 1 who presented with syncopal attacks and a lateral ventric...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Central Neurocytoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.710997442455243,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3901058331282304,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024267,
      "question_number": "130",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A lady presents with a cerebellopontine angle mass; pathology shows psammoma bodies. What is the lik...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Meningioma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7735191637630662,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6823738608579685,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024268,
      "question_number": "27",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q27. Anaplastic astrocytoma is characterized by which of the following features?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024269,
      "question_number": "22",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following tumors is characterized by the presence of Rosenthal fibers?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024270,
      "question_number": "2",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "In which case would steroids have an effect?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024271,
      "question_number": "19",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q19. Homer Wright rosettes are associated with which type of tumor?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024272,
      "question_number": "133",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A right brain lesion with pathology showing a fried egg appearance is noted. What is the next step? ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Debulking surgery"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024273,
      "question_number": "142",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient with CNS tumor pathology shows a Fried egg appearance. What is the appropriate treatment?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Debulking surgery",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.708029197080292,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6719332894448102,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024274,
      "question_number": "13",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A 57-year-old male patient with renal cell carcinoma is brought to the emergency department with con...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Surgical removal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8278388278388278,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5991085474567384,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024275,
      "question_number": "144",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with headache and bilateral 6th nerve palsy with papilledema. A red mass is seen ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Chordoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8358862144420132,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.763011983544983,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024276,
      "question_number": "138",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "What are the most common posterior fossa tumors in children?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024277,
      "question_number": "222",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A 40-year-old female presents with chronic headache. An MRI shows a frontal parasagittal enhancing l...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Psammoma bodies",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7823834196891192,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.729011132940406,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024278,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient with only skull and dural metastases, what is the next step?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024279,
      "question_number": "283",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "What is the treatment plan for a patient with a schwannoma?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024280,
      "question_number": "8",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "In which of the following scenarios does dexamethasone help?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024281,
      "question_number": "72",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A 5-year-old male with renal cell carcinoma was brought to the ED with confusion and seizures. Brain...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Surgical removal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8341463414634146,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.546102707389922,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024282,
      "question_number": "46",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A female patient has papilledema, signs of increased intracranial pressure, and MRI showed a frontal...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Stereotactic biopsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7002801120448179,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.041068668580260544,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024283,
      "question_number": "11",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "What is the pathology of Ependymoma?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024284,
      "question_number": "10",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of a patient with findings suggestive of Neurofibromatosis type 1 (NF1), what ass...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Bilateral Optic Glioma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7555555555555555,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.39599433982801785,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024285,
      "question_number": "139",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "What is the most common benign intracranial tumor?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024286,
      "question_number": "3",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following cancers can cause metastasis only to the dura and skull?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024287,
      "question_number": "71",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A clival mass is visible from the nostril. What is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024288,
      "question_number": "12",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A pathology report indicates atypia and necrosis. What is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024289,
      "question_number": "15",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A boy who presented with early morning headache and a suprasellar mass found on imaging with hormona...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Germinoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8104956268221575,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7538694481830417,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024290,
      "question_number": "149",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q149. A patient presented with tinnitus, hearing loss, and was found to have a tumor in the pons nea...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Schwannoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8316326530612245,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6603278094720637,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024291,
      "question_number": "137",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "In the case of a 59-year-old male patient with a history of prostate cancer, what is the most likely...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Ischemic stroke",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7707808564231738,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6892860226193559,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024292,
      "question_number": "134",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q134. What is the most common posterior fossa tumor in children?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024293,
      "question_number": "36",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with bitemporal hemianopia and headache, along with a drop in hemoglobin. What is...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024294,
      "question_number": "147",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A tumor of the clivus is most likely to be which type of tumor?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024295,
      "question_number": "9",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient with non-Hodgkin lymphoma presents with headache and urinary symptoms, and imaging shows l...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Vein",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8427672955974843,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4797986154814349,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024296,
      "question_number": "23",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q23. A patient with neurofibromatosis type 2 presents with progressive unilateral hearing loss and a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Vestibular schwannoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8191268191268192,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.74175287917236,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024297,
      "question_number": "240",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q240. A patient with glioblastoma multiforme (GBM) has an MRI showing increased edema and mass effec...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Steroid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8246153846153846,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7638085218306154,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024298,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q21. In patients with suspected brain metastases, which diagnostic test is most sensitive for detect...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024299,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A child with neurofibromatosis presents with headache and syncope and is found to have a tumor in th...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Central neurocytoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7806122448979592,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.24755893086103167,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024300,
      "question_number": "38",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Which condition is associated with Subependymal Giant Cell Astrocytoma (SEGA)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024301,
      "question_number": "13",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q13. Which of the following histopathological features is associated with oligodendroglioma?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024302,
      "question_number": "26",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Blue cells can be found in which of the following tumors?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024303,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A brain MRI shows a mass originating from the fourth ventricle with histology showing pseudorosettes...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Ependymoma"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024304,
      "question_number": "140",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Which tumor is associated with opsoclonus myoclonus syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024305,
      "question_number": "11",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient with hypopituitarism, a pituitary mass, and meningeal enhancement is being evaluated. What...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. CT chest"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024306,
      "question_number": "33",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Patient with an intracranial mass crossing the corpus callosum; what is the histology you will see?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Pseudopalisading necrosis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024307,
      "question_number": "143",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A female patient has papilledema, signs of increased intracranial pressure, and MRI showed a frontal...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Stereotactic biopsy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024308,
      "question_number": "60",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q60. Combines location and histology to diagnose Ependymoma.",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024309,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient with active but untreated renal cell carcinoma presents with a headache. Brain imaging rev...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Surgical removal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7782608695652173,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7396483267158253,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024310,
      "question_number": "46",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q46. Addresses initial management decision for a symptomatic brain tumor.",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024311,
      "question_number": "1",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q1. Metastases only to the dura and skull will happen with what of the following?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Prostate cancer",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7022222222222222,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7865887283555751,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024312,
      "question_number": "28",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q28. Addresses immediate management of symptomatic edema in GBM.",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024313,
      "question_number": "72",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q72. Addresses management of solitary brain metastasis.",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024314,
      "question_number": "403",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient came with a history of confusion and difficulty to arouse. MRI shows a glioblastoma multif...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Steroid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8564593301435407,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6987904799063598,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024315,
      "question_number": "122",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A 57-year-old male patient with renal cell carcinoma is brought to the emergency department with con...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Surgical removal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8203266787658802,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.02607264903176813,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024316,
      "question_number": "138",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following statements about the epidemiology of pediatric brain tumors is correct?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024317,
      "question_number": "141",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q141. Links \"butterfly glioma\" imaging to GBM histology.",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024318,
      "question_number": "135",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "What is the most common pediatric posterior fossa tumor?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024319,
      "question_number": "71",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A 4-year-old boy diagnosed with an intramedullary spinal cord tumor, non-enhancing on MRI, presents ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Astrocytoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8337874659400545,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7057041898031298,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024320,
      "question_number": "72",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q72. Addresses management of solitary brain metastasis.",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024321,
      "question_number": "3",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q3. Tests knowledge of primary cancers metastasizing to dura/skull.",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024322,
      "question_number": "24",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Psammoma bodies are typically found in which of the following tumors?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024323,
      "question_number": "32",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient diagnosed with glioblastoma multiforme (GBM) and treated 5 years ago presented wi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Steroid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8630705394190872,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5660913705583757,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024324,
      "question_number": "147",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Regarding diffuse astrocytoma grade 2, which statement is true?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024325,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A pediatric patient presents with progressive gait disturbance and sensory changes. MRI of the spine...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Low-grade astrocytoma"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024326,
      "question_number": "403",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q403. Addresses management of symptomatic edema in GBM.",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024327,
      "question_number": "28",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient with glioblastoma multiforme (GBM) has an MRI showing increased edema and mass effect. Wha...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Steroid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.819047619047619,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6246458923512748,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024328,
      "question_number": "136",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q136. Asks about characteristics/prognosis of low-grade glioma.",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024329,
      "question_number": "69",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "In which of the following conditions does dexamethasone provide benefit?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024330,
      "question_number": "16",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a left-sided chronic headache and develops upper extremity weakness. Imaging...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. Parasagittal meningioma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7564102564102564,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7629733520336606,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024331,
      "question_number": "132",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient has a left temporal lobe glioblastoma multiforme (GBM) with clear mass effect on imaging. ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Steroid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7290836653386454,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7334758596116159,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024332,
      "question_number": "12",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "An MRI showed an intramedullary, ill-defined, non-enhancing lesion. What is the most likely diagnosi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Astrocytoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7452471482889734,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4265716024693505,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024333,
      "question_number": "189",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A child presents with a cerebellopontine angle tumor and hearing loss for more than 5 months. What s...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024334,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q18. Tests knowledge of steroid effectiveness for tumor edema.*",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024335,
      "question_number": "139",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q139. Asks about epidemiology of benign brain tumors.",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024336,
      "question_number": "283",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Most common benign intracranial neoplasm:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024337,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Tumor pathology showing pseudorosette is indicative of which diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024338,
      "question_number": "146",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient with renal cell carcinoma presents with retinal hemangioblastoma and cerebellar hemangiobl...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024339,
      "question_number": "179",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q179. Links histology (pseudorosette) to tumor type (Ependymoma).",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024340,
      "question_number": "149",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q149. A patient presents with unilateral sensorineural hearing loss, tinnitus, and balance disturban...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Schwannoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8870151770657673,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7752711913218777,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024341,
      "question_number": "71",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A 35-year-old patient presents with progressive lower extremity weakness and sensory disturbances. M...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Astrocytoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8698752228163993,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5416978589609223,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024342,
      "question_number": "142",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q142. Links histology (Oligodendroglioma) to treatment.",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024343,
      "question_number": "42",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient with CNS tumor pathology showed a Fried egg appearance on imaging. What is the appropriate...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Debulking surgery",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7315436241610739,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7533177205308352,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024344,
      "question_number": "25",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q25. What histopathological feature is associated with glioblastoma?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024345,
      "question_number": "139",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A 6-year-old girl has a headache and diplopia. On examination, she has impaired upward gaze, lid ret...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pinealoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7990196078431373,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6184046899982235,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024346,
      "question_number": "126",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q126. Which of the following tumors most commonly arises within the ventricular system?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Ependymoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7359307359307359,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.40938806130103955,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024347,
      "question_number": "33",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q33. In a patient with newly diagnosed brain metastases, which of the following is the most appropri...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Chest CT scan",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7960199004975125,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.418727139722019,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024348,
      "question_number": "6",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q6. Links typical Meningioma imaging to its histology.",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024349,
      "question_number": "5",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "In a case of cranial metastases, what is the most appropriate initial imaging study to perform?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Brain MRI with contrast",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7265625,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7964601769911505,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024350,
      "question_number": "417",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Pathology features of meningioma include psammoma bodies. What is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024351,
      "question_number": "148",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A tumor located in the lateral ventricle is most likely a:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024352,
      "question_number": "54",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A male patient over the age of 50 presents with subcortical/cortical metastases. What is the most li...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Lung cancer",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8091168091168092,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.37729026036644164,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024353,
      "question_number": "129",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Histopathology for the attached MRI shows which of the following features indicative of Ependymoma g...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Pseudorosette",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7254901960784313,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5896451425247237,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024354,
      "question_number": "51",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A coronal brain MRI shows a frontal extra-axial homogeneous mass. What is the likely histopathology ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Psammoma bodies"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024355,
      "question_number": "17",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A brain tumor with characteristic cells encircling each other called psammoma bodies is:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Meningioma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.71900826446281,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6349708411584462,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024356,
      "question_number": "20",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A pediatric patient presented with expansile spinal cord signal changes with partial enhancement. Wh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Astrocytoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7975460122699386,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7162194633560273,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024357,
      "question_number": "145",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A brain MRI shows a butterfly mass. What is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024358,
      "question_number": "131",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q131. A pseudorosette is observed. What is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024359,
      "question_number": "517",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A gynecological ultrasound shows an ovarian tumor. What is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024360,
      "question_number": "89",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "In HIV/AIDS patients, what are the most common subtypes of AIDS-associated lymphoma?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024361,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q35. Links histology (pseudorosette) to tumor type (Ependymoma).",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024362,
      "question_number": "71",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with progressive sensorimotor deficits of the lower extremities. MRI of the spina...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Astrocytoma"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024363,
      "question_number": "477",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient who is a smoker has an X-ray showing a lung tumor and presents with peripheral neuropathy....",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024364,
      "question_number": "39",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A smoker presenting with polyneuropathy may have antibodies against which of the following?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024365,
      "question_number": "489",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A 31-year-old female smoker with subacute sensory neuropathy and motor symptoms has a chest X-ray sh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-Hu",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8467153284671532,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.694916795489679,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024366,
      "question_number": "486",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Upon workup of the same patient, you find an ovarian teratoma. What is the best management option?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Removal of the tumor"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024367,
      "question_number": "217",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q217. Suggestive of paraneoplastic syndrome workup.",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024368,
      "question_number": "498",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient with a history of breast cancer presents post-resection and chemoradiation therapy with pr...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Radiation"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024369,
      "question_number": "25",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q25. A spine MRI shows an intermediary non-enhancing mass. What is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Ependymoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7468879668049793,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6093844296922148,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024370,
      "question_number": "76",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient came with sensory motor neuropathy with distal weakness (he has dorsiflexion weak...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CT chest",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8075880758807588,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6333585190782017,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024371,
      "question_number": "217",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient presents with a sensorimotor neuropathy characterized by distal weakness (notably...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CT chest",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8367816091954023,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6719473920191302,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024372,
      "question_number": "101",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient with breast cancer post-treatment presented with horizontal nystagmus without fast compone...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024373,
      "question_number": "114",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A 44-year-old woman is evaluated for severe and progressive left shoulder pain radiating down to the...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Neoplastic plexopathy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024374,
      "question_number": "55",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient with renal cell carcinoma presents with retinal hemangioblastoma and cerebellar hemangiobl...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024375,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A female patient with a history of breast cancer underwent radical mastectomy followed by radiation ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Radiation induced plexopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8535031847133758,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4368692531957838,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024376,
      "question_number": "44",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q44. Which of the following tumors is most commonly associated with opsoclonus-myoclonus?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024377,
      "question_number": "11",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A young boy presents with 4th nerve palsy. Where is the tumor likely located?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Midbrain",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7537688442211056,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5712791913558731,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024378,
      "question_number": "308",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q308. A young lady with progressive insomnia developed psychiatric symptoms, was admitted to the psy...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Ovarian teratoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8600337268128162,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.27663036675428715,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024379,
      "question_number": "14",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q14. A 25-year-old patient complains of inability to walk down the stairs. Upon examination, he has ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Pineal tumor compressing the midbrain",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.796844181459566,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6967120181405896,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024380,
      "question_number": "183",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A male patient exhibits behavior changes and has an MRI showing a frontal lesion with heterogeneous ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024381,
      "question_number": "299",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A 4-year-old child presents with nausea, vomiting, diplopia, and ataxia. What is the most likely dia...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Medulloblastoma"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024382,
      "question_number": "261",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient with a history of breast cancer presents with opsoclonus-myoclonus syndrome. Which antibod...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Anti-Ri"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024383,
      "question_number": "117",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "An elderly male patient came with pancerebellar degeneration. What is the paraneoplastic antibody?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-Hu",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.810126582278481,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7581185715936669,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024384,
      "question_number": "14",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of small cell lung cancer (SCLC) with peripheral neuropathy, which antibody is co...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-Hu",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8231046931407943,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6632867801798354,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024385,
      "question_number": "368",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "An elderly male patient presents with pancerebellar degeneration. What is the paraneoplastic antibod...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-Hu"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024386,
      "question_number": "25",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q25. A patient with breast cancer presents with spontaneous nystagmus suggestive of opsoclonus-myocl...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti Ri"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024387,
      "question_number": "307",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q307. A patient presents with opsoclonus myoclonus. What is the associated malignancy?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "D. Ovary",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7942583732057417,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7924294903513113,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024388,
      "question_number": "112",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A child with proptosis has a mother who also has proptosis and light brown dots in the neck. What is...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Neurofibromatosis Type 1"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024389,
      "question_number": "15",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of opsoclonus myoclonus associated with breast cancer, which antibody is typicall...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-RI",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8122605363984674,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.799132618123716,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024390,
      "question_number": "176",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "An elderly male presents with painful sensory symptoms, progressive loss of coordination, and sensor...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Anti-Hu"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024391,
      "question_number": "182",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "In a patient presenting with multiple caf\u00e9-au-lait macules, cutaneous neurofibromas, and Lisch nodul...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Neurofibromatosis type 1"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024392,
      "question_number": "102",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient with ADHD presents with light brown lesions. What is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024393,
      "question_number": "162",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "In a case with spinal cord and posterior fossa tumors, the most likely diagnosis is:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024394,
      "question_number": "120",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient has 7 flat brown lesions on the skin. What is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024395,
      "question_number": "172",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient with ADHD has a mother with brown pigmentations in her neck. What is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024396,
      "question_number": "180",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A child with proptosis has a mother with similar symptoms and light brown dots on the neck. What is ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Neurofibromatosis type 1"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024397,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A child who presented with ADHD and multiple light brown macula on skin, what is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024398,
      "question_number": "3",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a cyst, and his brother has a hemangioblastoma. There is a family history of...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. von Hippel-Lindau syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024399,
      "question_number": "1",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "SEGA is associated with which disease?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024400,
      "question_number": "43",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A male known case of testicular cancer presented with encephalitis. Which antibodies might be involv...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-Ma2",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7651515151515151,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7641578222474277,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024401,
      "question_number": "158",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A child is suspected to have ADHD and presents with caf\u00e9 au lait spots and flickering movements. Wha...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024402,
      "question_number": "141",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q141. What are the criteria for Tuberous Sclerosis (TS)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024403,
      "question_number": "30",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient with a history of breast cancer presents with weight loss and loss of sensation in the med...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Lower trunk"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024404,
      "question_number": "6",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient known to have breast cancer presents with ataxia and nystagmus. Which antibodies might be ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Anti-Yo",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8333333333333334,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3828956706884315,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024405,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with proptosis and decreased eye movements, and he has brown pigmentations. What ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Benign optic glioma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7619047619047619,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7857015192135836,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024406,
      "question_number": "380",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q380. In Foster Kennedy syndrome with right optic atrophy, where is the lesion located?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024407,
      "question_number": "32",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with retinal lesions and a family history of cerebellar hemangioblastoma. What is...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024408,
      "question_number": "208",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient came with a brain tumor, and his first-degree relative had a history of spine tumor and pe...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Von-Hippel Lindau"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024409,
      "question_number": "50",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A patient with multiple caf\u00e9-au-lait spots presents with unilateral proptosis and restricted extraoc...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Benign optic glioma"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024410,
      "question_number": "46",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "A young female presented with a severe headache; CT imaging shows pituitary apoplexy. What is the li...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pituitary apoplexy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7417218543046358,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.05379912663755459,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024411,
      "question_number": "32",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Brun\u2019s nystagmus localizes to the cerebellopontine angle (CPA) and is most commonly indicative of wh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Schwannoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7633587786259542,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.743537838679539,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024412,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "Q41. The clinical picture suggests an optic pathway glioma related to neurofibromatosis, asking for ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Pilocytic astrocytoma"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024413,
      "question_number": "40",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro oncology",
      "question_text": "An 8-year-old girl with a pineal gland tumor and obstructive hydrocephalus is being examined. What i...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Convergence-retraction nystagmus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7375886524822695,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.29119550807143413,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023267,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro otology",
      "question_text": "A patient presented to the ER with vertigo and vomiting. What is the feature that can differentiate ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023268,
      "question_number": "246",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro otology",
      "question_text": "Q246. A patient with benign paroxysmal positional vertigo (BPPV), what is the management?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023269,
      "question_number": "180",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro otology",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old female presented with visual blurring and is diagnosed with Brun\u2019s nystagmus. The larg...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Cerebellum",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8220551378446115,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3106863196683556,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023270,
      "question_number": "99",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro otology",
      "question_text": "Q99. A patient has vertical and torsional nystagmus. What is the localization?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023271,
      "question_number": "148",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro otology",
      "question_text": "A young patient is complaining of hearing impairment. She has ataxia, dizziness, and nystagmus. Her ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Episodic ataxia type 2"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023272,
      "question_number": "38",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro otology",
      "question_text": "In a case of central vertigo, which of the following is true?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023273,
      "question_number": "400",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro otology",
      "question_text": "What supports central nystagmus rather than peripheral nystagmus?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023274,
      "question_number": "294",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro otology",
      "question_text": "Central nystagmus vs peripheral nystagmus will exhibit which of the following characteristics?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023275,
      "question_number": "364",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro otology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following structures is most likely to be abnormal on VRE in a patient with oscillopsia...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024414,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) showing lymphocytosis and eosinophilia, and is dia...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Praziquantel",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8162162162162162,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5443277672577036,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024415,
      "question_number": "36",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with features of Whipple\u2019s disease and oculomasticatory myorhythmia is being evaluated. Wh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "D. Start antibiotics",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7696629213483146,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6440156268497691,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024416,
      "question_number": "125",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with meningitis from Alhaj is found to have meningococcal meningitis. What prophylaxis sho...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Ciprofloxacin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8176795580110497,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5796938316073841,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024417,
      "question_number": "70",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with cerebrospinal fluid showing lymphocytosis and marked eosinophilia and is dia...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Praziquantel",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8213333333333334,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6210619469026548,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024418,
      "question_number": "84",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient who is returning from Sudan had fever, confusion, and headache. What test should you perfo...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thick blood film",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7443609022556391,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5188636363636364,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024419,
      "question_number": "166",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Young lady with SLE, seizures, and vitals: temperature 39\u00b0C with image of temporal lobe involvement....",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. HSV encephalitis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.74375,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7865290602933188,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024420,
      "question_number": "56",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q56. A case scenario presents a patient with a history of oculomasticatory myorhythmia. What is the ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Biopsy from the jejunum",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.75,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.796447344571325,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024421,
      "question_number": "89",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the most common organism responsible for bacterial meningitis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pneumococcus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5847457627118644,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7973195649785785,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024422,
      "question_number": "92",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of cavernous sinus thrombosis, what is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Cavernous sinus thrombosis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024423,
      "question_number": "133",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Which of the following infections is more common to cause internuclear ophthalmoplegia (INO)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "D. Syphilis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7627118644067796,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.54618312963334,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024424,
      "question_number": "36",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An HIV\u2010positive patient presents with subacute confusion and blurred vision. Brain MRI reveals multi...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Highly active antiretroviral therapy (HAART)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7549909255898367,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5391746031746032,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024425,
      "question_number": "110",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q110. Lady presented with fever, headache and neck stiffness, she had occipital decompression for Ch...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Staphylococci",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8169642857142857,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.48793718772305494,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024426,
      "question_number": "182",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q182. Patient came with neurosyphilis, VDRL positive; what are the symptoms associated with the dise...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Constricted pupils",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7142857142857143,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4598117931451265,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024427,
      "question_number": "61",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q61. A patient with HIV has a brain MRI showing a single ring-enhancing lesion. What is the manageme...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Sulfadiazine and pyrimethamine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024428,
      "question_number": "97",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Patient came with neurosyphilis; VDRL positive. What are the symptoms associated with the disease?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Constricted pupils"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024429,
      "question_number": "80",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with HIV presents with a non-enhancing white matter mass on MRI and has not been compliant...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. HAART",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7967032967032966,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7899882675009777,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024430,
      "question_number": "68",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In an HIV\u2010positive patient presenting with new focal neurological deficits and brain MRI showing two...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Progressive multifocal leukoencephalopathy (PML)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6912065439672802,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7782043079547878,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024431,
      "question_number": "130",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q130. An HIV patient on HAART is not compliant and presents with confusion. A brain MRI shows patchy...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Pyrimethamine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024432,
      "question_number": "149",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q149. A patient who underwent decompression for Chiari malformation two weeks ago presents with meni...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Staphylococcus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8284313725490197,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6034203836376242,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024433,
      "question_number": "155",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A scenario suggests subacute sclerosing panencephalitis (SSPE), and an EEG shows periodic burst comp...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Measles antibody test",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7673716012084593,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7011395662296287,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024434,
      "question_number": "58",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of an HIV patient presented with new neurological focality and brain MRI showing two n...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Progressive Multifocal Leukoencephalopathy (PML)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.702819956616052,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.0977096416697451,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024435,
      "question_number": "81",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In a case of meningitis, what prophylactic treatment should be given to family members?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Rifampin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6938775510204082,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6913534185243914,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024436,
      "question_number": "98",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the most common bacterial meningitis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024437,
      "question_number": "87",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with fever and confusion, was anemic, and had hypoglycemia, which was treated. C...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Artemisinin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8537170263788969,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4722502522704339,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024438,
      "question_number": "67",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A male from Africa presents to Saudi Arabia with fever and vague neurological symptoms, including en...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Cerebral malaria"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024439,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the best management for neuro-brucellosis?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Ceftriaxone"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024440,
      "question_number": "138",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In HIV-AIDS patients who are refractory to initial empiric treatment for CNS toxoplasmosis, what sho...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. An early brain biopsy.",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6589861751152074,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6499080318822809,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024441,
      "question_number": "136",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient diagnosed with HIV one month ago presents now with paraparesis. What is the most likely di...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. CMV",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7598566308243727,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3550259067357513,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024442,
      "question_number": "57",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An HIV patient on highly active antiretroviral therapy (HAART) who is non-compliant developed PML. W...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. HAART"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024443,
      "question_number": "117",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Scenario of a diabetic patient with a history of sinusitis and focal neurological deficit. What is t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Mucormycosis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024444,
      "question_number": "143",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In case of contact with a patient who has meningitis, what is the recommended prophylaxis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Ciprofloxacin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7302904564315352,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5545845832789879,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024445,
      "question_number": "146",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with HIV presents with deteriorated level of consciousness and a CT scan shows an enhancin...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Start pyrimethamine + sulfadiazine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6842105263157895,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.12461443553362123,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024446,
      "question_number": "119",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "When should metronidazole be added to meningitis treatment?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024447,
      "question_number": "63",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q63. A sickle cell patient presents with back pain and lower limb weakness. On examination, he has b...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Salmonella spp."
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024448,
      "question_number": "108",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the primary mechanism of infection by Ameba bacteria?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024449,
      "question_number": "123",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In a diabetic male older than 50 years, what kind of organisms do you expect to see if he develops m...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Listeria monocytogenes",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6625766871165644,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7479708209185246,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024450,
      "question_number": "148",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with a long history presented with seizures and flaccid paralysis. What is the most likely...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. West Nile virus (WNV)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3831315411450852,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024451,
      "question_number": "75",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Corticosteroids with an antibiotic regimen for meningitis help with which of the following?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Decrease deafness",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6428571428571429,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.48795586058403984,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024452,
      "question_number": "137",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with schistosomiasis presents with lower limb weakness and high eosinophils in the CBC. Wh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Praziquantel",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7926829268292683,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5083471724499606,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024453,
      "question_number": "86",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the recommended prophylactic treatment for meningitis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Rifampin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6559139784946236,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7267992917404437,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024454,
      "question_number": "171",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q171. A patient with encephalopathy, EEG showed slow bilateral synchronous high amplitude spikes. Wh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Measles"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024455,
      "question_number": "74",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with meningitis from Alhaj is found to have meningococcal meningitis. What prophylaxis sho...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Ciprofloxacin (adult)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7701492537313432,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7448175536428658,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024456,
      "question_number": "142",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q142. When suspicion for CNS toxoplasmosis is low based on brain imaging, CD4 count, and negative se...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Proceeding directly for a brain biopsy.",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5806451612903226,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.32846521508231546,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024457,
      "question_number": "72",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In neuro-brucellosis, what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Ceftriaxone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.627906976744186,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7542737831136631,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024458,
      "question_number": "156",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In the case of tuberculosis (TB), which artery is most commonly involved?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Middle cerebral artery (MCA)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024459,
      "question_number": "176",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A diabetic patient came to the ER with a black lesion in her nostril. What is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Amphotericin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024460,
      "question_number": "129",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A young girl presents with a complaint of back pain, fever, and night sweats. She shows signs of str...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Blood Culture"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024461,
      "question_number": "150",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the most common organism associated with polyradiculopathy in HIV patients?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Cytomegalovirus (CMV)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5795053003533569,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.22595611285266456,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024462,
      "question_number": "65",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In a diabetic patient presenting with a black necrotic lesion on the nasal turbinate and rapid progr...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Mucormycosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7887323943661971,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.722325836533187,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024463,
      "question_number": "8",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An HIV\u2010positive patient with a CD4 count of 50 cells/\u03bcL presents with headache and focal neurologic ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Toxoplasmosis management",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8429752066115702,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4791352438411262,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024464,
      "question_number": "174",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An HIV patient\u2019s MRI showed multiple brain abscesses. What is the causing organism?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Parasite",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7714285714285715,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.01888111888111888,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024465,
      "question_number": "78",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with sickle cell anemia presents with low back pain and fever. What is the most likely org...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Staphylococcus aureus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7356948228882834,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6065055056321984,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024466,
      "question_number": "19",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q19. A healthy individual returns from hiking in the USA and presents with radiculopathy. CSF analys...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lyme disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8404040404040404,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6948345908299478,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024467,
      "question_number": "64",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Which of the following neuro manifestations is associated with Whipple disease?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Oculomasticatory myorhythmia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.582089552238806,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7997346223106815,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024468,
      "question_number": "9",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the confirmation method for Whipple disease?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Jejunal biopsy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024469,
      "question_number": "144",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q144. Which infection causes bilateral internuclear ophthalmoplegia (INO)?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. HIV",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7734806629834254,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6268023748939779,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024470,
      "question_number": "158",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Tropical spastic paraparesis due to human T-lymphotropic virus type 1 (HTLV-1) typically occurs in w...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Endemic regions (equatorial and South Africa, the Caribbean, parts of Asia, Central and South America)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6365914786967418,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.34301130524152107,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024471,
      "question_number": "62",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A diabetic patient comes to the ER with a black lesion in her nostril. What is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Amphotericin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024472,
      "question_number": "151",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A male nurse was exposed to a patient with meningococcal meningitis. What should be done?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Give rifampin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024473,
      "question_number": "90",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In an HIV-positive patient with a low CD4 count and an MRI showing multiple ring-enhancing lesions, ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Parasite",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8588588588588588,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.16276646139270487,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024474,
      "question_number": "115",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q115. A patient presented with focal numbness on a skin lesion. Investigation revealed nerve enlarge...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Leprosy (Hansen's disease)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8291666666666667,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4031232571109872,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024475,
      "question_number": "59",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An HIV patient has a brain CT showing multiple ring-enhancing lesions. What is the next step in mana...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Empirical anti-toxoplasma therapy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7394366197183099,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.21907302434144715,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024476,
      "question_number": "53",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A case scenario of a young male IV drug user presented with fever and hemiparesis. What will you do?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Start antibiotics",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7396226415094339,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7971625766871165,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024477,
      "question_number": "104",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "When should Metronidazole be added to a patient started on empirical anti-meningitis coverage?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. History of Mastoiditis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.577639751552795,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6670416197975253,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024478,
      "question_number": "66",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In a patient with poorly controlled diabetes mellitus presenting with facial pain, nasal congestion,...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Mucormycosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8026315789473685,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7662372278987117,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024479,
      "question_number": "163",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old male patient with a history of lupus who is on steroids and has undergone a kidney tra...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Infection",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8913043478260869,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3652730546109222,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024480,
      "question_number": "101",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with fever and visual loss. Fundoscopic examination reported retinal whitening, ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Malaria",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8269662921348314,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5351478363031134,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024481,
      "question_number": "173",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q173. A stroke patient has a fever, and cardiac consultation showed a pansystolic murmur. What is th...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Antibiotics",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7346938775510204,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7842227378190255,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024482,
      "question_number": "145",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In the case of cavernous mucormycosis, which statement is true?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024483,
      "question_number": "159",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In an HIV patient with a non-enhancing lesion in the parietal lobe, which statement is true?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024484,
      "question_number": "69",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario (diabetic patient with a black eschar on the nasal mucosa suggestive of rhinoce...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Amphotericin B"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024485,
      "question_number": "135",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the most effective prevention method for post-herpetic neuralgia?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Anti-viral therapy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024486,
      "question_number": "120",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a one-month history of increased thirst, headache, fever, and personality ch...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. NeuroTB",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9221967963386728,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7044105854049719,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024487,
      "question_number": "109",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A 79-year-old female has a 4-week history of malaise, low-grade fever, and altered mental status. Sh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. West Nile Virus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7947019867549668,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.07364739765480353,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024488,
      "question_number": "147",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In a case of Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease (CJD) regarding organ donation, which statement is correct?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Do not take any organ"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024489,
      "question_number": "140",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the benefit of using steroids at the initiation of meningitis treatment?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Decrease the risk of deafness"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024490,
      "question_number": "139",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient is comatose, with retinal findings typical for neuro-retinitis. What is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Syphilis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024491,
      "question_number": "153",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A 16-year-old boy has behavior issues, and his teacher reports a decrease in performance in school. ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Subacute sclerosing panencephalitis (SSPE)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024492,
      "question_number": "154",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is a common complication of cerebral malaria?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. All of the above"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024493,
      "question_number": "131",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q131. A male patient from Africa, an illegal resident in Saudi Arabia, was brought to the hospital a...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Mycobacterium tuberculosis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024494,
      "question_number": "116",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the most common cause of bacterial meningitis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024495,
      "question_number": "62",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An HIV\u2010positive patient with a history of poor compliance on HAART presents with subacute cognitive ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Restart or optimize HAART",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7779816513761468,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5057496203080929,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024496,
      "question_number": "157",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q157. What is the most common cause of polyradiculopathy, without mention of immune status?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. Tuberculosis (TB)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6567164179104478,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.476272057563817,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024497,
      "question_number": "60",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Whipple disease is caused by which of the following organisms?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Tropheryma whipplei"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024498,
      "question_number": "100",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Patient found to have positive poliovirus IgG, what is the most common presentation?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Asymptomatic",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6456692913385826,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7540436189084838,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024499,
      "question_number": "17",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q17. A patient with a known case of diabetes mellitus presents with a black spot on the nose. What i...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Amphotericin B",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7659574468085106,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7728079817367042,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024500,
      "question_number": "88",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of mucormycosis, what is the route of infection?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Direct invasion (through emissary vein)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5042016806722689,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7602916432978126,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024501,
      "question_number": "128",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with HIV presents with confusion. A CT scan shows multiple enhancing masses in the brain. ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Cryptococcus antigen test",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8366890380313199,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6425821735267989,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024502,
      "question_number": "175",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient has bilateral facial weakness, and a lumbar puncture showed high white blood cell count. A...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Ceftriaxone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8328767123287671,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7746800277805338,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024503,
      "question_number": "122",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In a case of bacterial meningitis, what is the most common organism responsible?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pneumococcus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6141732283464567,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7356026123095191,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024504,
      "question_number": "121",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the most common sporadic fatal viral meningoencephalitis worldwide?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. HSV1",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8131868131868132,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7599961645411832,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024505,
      "question_number": "95",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In a case of HSV encephalitis, what would you expect to find in the CSF?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024506,
      "question_number": "170",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An HIV patient has an MRI typical for neurocysticercosis. What is the cause?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Taenia solium"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024507,
      "question_number": "249",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is true about herpes encephalitis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024508,
      "question_number": "51",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with personality changes, headaches, and increased thirst for months. MRI shows h...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. TB meningoencephalitis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.847457627118644,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7849310222851079,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024509,
      "question_number": "92",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient with a sinus infection presents with meningitis. What is the appropriate treatmen...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Ceftriaxone, vancomycin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024510,
      "question_number": "169",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Patient came with orange retina; what is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Bartonella",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.654320987654321,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7574245275300663,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024511,
      "question_number": "152",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Malaria is caused by which species when the CNS is involved?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Plasmodium falciparum",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5619047619047619,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6694265562710825,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024512,
      "question_number": "127",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the most common site of infection in neural infections?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Lumbar",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7251461988304093,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7183859050866723,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024513,
      "question_number": "167",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A 21-year-old female, pregnant at 27 weeks and living on a dairy farm, presents with a history of me...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Vancomycin + Cefotaxime + Ampicillin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024514,
      "question_number": "132",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the most common cause of sporadic fatal meningoencephalitis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. HSV1"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024515,
      "question_number": "118",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with HIV and a CD4 count of 60 presents with a single ring-enhancing lesion at the white\u2013g...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Start sulfadiazine plus pyrimethamine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8084112149532711,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.33729682556997925,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024516,
      "question_number": "161",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q161. A 35-year-old female has a history of back pain and progressive weakness, with normal brain an...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Vacuolar myelopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7705263157894737,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6634022488211825,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024517,
      "question_number": "96",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In a patient with HIV presenting with progressive multifocal leukoencephalopathy (PML), what is the ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. HAART",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7108433734939759,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.21128349788434414,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024518,
      "question_number": "52",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the most common location of Varicella Zoster Virus (VZV) in the neuronal axis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Thoracic"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024519,
      "question_number": "160",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In an HIV patient with multiple ring-enhancing lesions, which statement is true?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024520,
      "question_number": "85",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the duration of acyclovir that will most likely decrease the chance of HSV recurrence?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "C. 14 days",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7948717948717948,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5842725741676383,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024521,
      "question_number": "107",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient developed a painful Herpes Zoster rash. Five days after the pain subsided, she de...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Herpes Zoster encephalitis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024522,
      "question_number": "168",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A middle-aged male patient with a history of headache reports fever, night sweats, and weight loss a...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. Tuberculosis meningitis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8444444444444444,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.49522423360320206,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024523,
      "question_number": "94",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A young patient with a history of CNS infection presents with fever and CSF pleocytosis. Cultures an...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Acyclovir",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8016877637130801,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6413091552410438,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024524,
      "question_number": "105",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient was brought to the emergency department with fever and confusion. Later, he developed a se...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Lymphocytes with RBC"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024525,
      "question_number": "134",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Oculomasticatory myorhythmia is diagnosed by which of the following?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Jejunal biopsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7204301075268817,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5219729278694604,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024526,
      "question_number": "162",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with weight loss and fever. MRI shows a frontal epidural collection. What is the ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Epidural empyema"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024527,
      "question_number": "114",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q114. A young Indian lady, who works as a nurse, was brought by her friend complaining of a headache...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Taenia solium",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8571428571428571,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7509124087591241,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024528,
      "question_number": "96",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A 40-year-old man is seen in the emergency department for evaluation of retinal hemorrhage, hepatosp...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Blood smear"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024529,
      "question_number": "126",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with neurobrucellosis is typically treated with which of the following antibiotics during ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Ceftriaxone and Doxycycline"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024530,
      "question_number": "164",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An HIV patient has an MRI that is typical for toxoplasmosis. What is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Start trimethoprim-sulfamethoxazole"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024531,
      "question_number": "82",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q82. A patient from India is found to have schistosomiasis. What is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Praziquantel",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7338709677419355,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.757628979143798,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024532,
      "question_number": "172",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An HIV patient who is non-compliant with his medication has an MRI that showed non-enhanced posterio...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. HAART",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7843137254901961,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4738278931750742,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024533,
      "question_number": "91",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A 19-year-old man is hospitalized in a psychiatric ward after developing visual and auditory halluci...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. HSV encephalitis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8542274052478134,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5632146357399542,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024534,
      "question_number": "59",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with features of mucormycosis, including a black nasal mass with maxillary pain a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Direct invasion"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024535,
      "question_number": "119",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with meningitis, who came from Alhaj, was found to have meningococcal meningitis. What is ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Ciprofloxacin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8288770053475936,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6548064918851436,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024536,
      "question_number": "96",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A 40-year-old man is seen in the emergency department for evaluation of retinal hemorrhage, hepatosp...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Blood smear",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9102402022756005,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.042109695757448155,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024537,
      "question_number": "120",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A young Saudi male, studying in Africa, just returned with symptoms of radiculopathy. CSF analysis s...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Praziquantel",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8723404255319149,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7870417732310315,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024538,
      "question_number": "121",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A 10- or 12-year-old female is brought by her family for complaints of progressive decline in school...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Subacute sclerosing panencephalitis (SSPE)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024539,
      "question_number": "87",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q87. A female patient diagnosed with HIV came to the clinic for evaluation of possible associated pe...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Distal symmetrical sensory neuropathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7045871559633028,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7762845849802371,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024540,
      "question_number": "68",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario of mucormycosis, what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Amphotericin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024541,
      "question_number": "50",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In the case of HSV encephalitis, what is the recommended duration of Acyclovir treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. 14 days"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024542,
      "question_number": "95",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A young male presented with headache and fever. A CT of the brain was normal. A lumbar puncture was ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Traumatic tap",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.823076923076923,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.17309853877856876,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024543,
      "question_number": "121",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q121. A 10- or 12-year-old female is brought by her family for complaints of progressive decline in ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Subacute sclerosing panencephalitis (SSPE)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8215686274509804,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.07689863361931999,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024544,
      "question_number": "68",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario of mucormycosis, what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Amphotericin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6796116504854369,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.028655470158459057,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024545,
      "question_number": "87",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A female patient diagnosed with HIV came to the clinic for evaluation of possible associated periphe...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Distal symmetrical sensory neuropathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6950092421441775,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.04609898234321997,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024546,
      "question_number": "59",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with features of mucormycosis, including a black nasal mass with maxillary pain a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Direct invasion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7665198237885462,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.02186234817813765,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024547,
      "question_number": "69",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A young lady with SLE nephritis on dialysis presents with seizures and confusion. CSF analysis shows...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Herpes Simplex Virus (HSV) encephalitis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024548,
      "question_number": "119",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with meningitis, who came from Alhaj, was found to have meningococcal meningitis. What is ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Ciprofloxacin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8288770053475936,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.05656445370646026,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024549,
      "question_number": "130",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q130. A patient from Sudan presents with fluctuating high fever, altered mental status (AMS), and an...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Anti-Malaria (specific drug name needed)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7131367292225201,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.17189928504818153,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024550,
      "question_number": "95",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A young male presented with headache and fever. A CT of the brain was normal. A lumbar puncture was ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Traumatic tap",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.823076923076923,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.02609727164887307,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024551,
      "question_number": "50",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In the case of HSV encephalitis, what is the recommended duration of Acyclovir treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. 14 days",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7837837837837838,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.044725981380170844,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024552,
      "question_number": "280",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q280. TB affected which brain vessel?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. MCA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6796116504854369,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7710539586485123,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024553,
      "question_number": "51",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An Indian patient presents with seizures and multiple small brain lesions. What is the most likely d...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Cysticercosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7535211267605634,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.603342939481268,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024554,
      "question_number": "231",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q231. A patient presented with meningitis. What should be given?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Dexamethasone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6288659793814433,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7901042822276458,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024555,
      "question_number": "326",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with headache, vomiting, fever, and nuchal rigidity two weeks after undergoing a ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Staphylococcus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8355555555555556,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5217678827289761,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024556,
      "question_number": "105",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In cases of Schistosoma Mansonia infection, what is the most common presentation?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Myelopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6610878661087866,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6325505833702555,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024557,
      "question_number": "119",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q119. A patient diagnosed with meningococcal meningitis has family members asking about prevention a...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Ciprofloxacin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6860706860706861,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.640560104426249,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024558,
      "question_number": "220",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q220. A patient came from Africa with fever and neurological symptoms. What is the most appropriate ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Blood smear (thick and thin)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024559,
      "question_number": "340",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q340. An Indian nurse presented with a new-onset generalized tonic\u2013clonic seizure. MRI FLAIR images ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Taenia solium",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8284671532846716,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6745677093452497,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024560,
      "question_number": "230",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What percentage of individuals infected with HTLV-1 will develop neurologic disease?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. 1% to 2%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024561,
      "question_number": "175",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q175. The best way to prevent post-herpetic neuralgia is?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Antiviral therapy (during acute shingles)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024562,
      "question_number": "106",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with a typical history of CJD has a family that wants him to be in an organ donation progr...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Remove them from the organ donation program",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5779816513761468,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7402354494443834,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024563,
      "question_number": "452",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q452. What is the most common presentation of poliovirus infection?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Asymptomatic",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6341463414634146,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.48448126622975146,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024564,
      "question_number": "70",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q70. A ?? year-old female was brought by her family for the complaint of progressive decline in scho...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Subacute sclerosing panencephalitis (SSPE)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024565,
      "question_number": "365",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An Indian nurse presented with her first seizure and a history of headache one week prior. She was l...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Neurocysticercosis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024566,
      "question_number": "371",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A man with multiple cognitive domain involvement has ataxia and extrapyramidal features, with pathol...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. GSS (Gerstmann-Str\u00e4ussler-Scheinker syndrome)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7713004484304933,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7785372522214627,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024567,
      "question_number": "90",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An HIV patient has an MRI typical for neurocysticercosis. What is the cause?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Taenia solium",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5991902834008097,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5569907488217839,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024568,
      "question_number": "379",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with fever and meningismus, and an MRI shows left temporal hyperintensity. What w...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Red blood cells and lymphocytic pleocytosis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024569,
      "question_number": "416",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q416. A governmental clerk presents with meningitis. What is the most common organism responsible fo...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Meningococcal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7192429022082019,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6295879766895001,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024570,
      "question_number": "402",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q402. What is the most common organism responsible for bacterial meningitis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Streptococcus pneumoniae"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024571,
      "question_number": "441",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q441. In a scenario of mucormycosis with black nasal discharge, what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Amphotericin B",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7335907335907336,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7830002196354052,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024572,
      "question_number": "152",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q152. What is the most common pattern of neuropathy seen in HIV patients?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Distal symmetrical neuropathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5819672131147541,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7642276422764228,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024573,
      "question_number": "282",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q282. What is the prevention of postherpetic neuralgia?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Antiviral",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6022727272727273,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.715122419587134,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024574,
      "question_number": "36",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q36. A patient with encephalopathy, EEG showed slow bilateral synchronous high amplitude spikes. Wha...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Measles"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024575,
      "question_number": "339",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q339. When should metronidazole be added to treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Mastoiditis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5073170731707317,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5062584421431787,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024576,
      "question_number": "297",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q297. (Source: Part II 2022mcqs.txt; Originally Neuromuscular) Retinal finding suggestive of malaria...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Malaria"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024577,
      "question_number": "296",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q296. What is a poor prognostic indicator for brain abscess?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024578,
      "question_number": "442",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with confusion, lymphadenopathy, and flaccid paralysis. What is the likely organi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. West Nile Virus (WNV)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7021276595744681,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7439638700712177,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024579,
      "question_number": "108",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the most common area affected in TB vasculopathy?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Basal ganglia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024580,
      "question_number": "53",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An HIV patient\u2019s MRI showed multiple brain abscesses. What is the causing organism?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Parasite",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7714285714285715,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.24822617618163956,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024581,
      "question_number": "58",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient has bilateral facial weakness and lumbar puncture shows high white blood cell count. A pic...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Ceftriaxone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8291316526610645,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.784630401987754,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024582,
      "question_number": "24",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An HIV patient with a CD4 count of 5 and a viral load in the thousands develops parkinsonism with ba...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Toxoplasmosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7630922693266833,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.48614834673815904,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024583,
      "question_number": "147",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In the case of a brain abscess, what is a poor prognostic factor?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024584,
      "question_number": "39",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An HIV patient non-compliant with his medication had an MRI that showed non-enhanced posterior hyper...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. HAART",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7846607669616519,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.09823484267075978,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024585,
      "question_number": "107",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q107. A patient with HIV develops meningitis. What additional medication should be given with ceftri...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Ampicillin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7715355805243446,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7045481676017668,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024586,
      "question_number": "109",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In a patient with cognitive impairment following a herpes zoster infection, what is the most likely ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. HZ encephalitis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7105263157894737,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4288198757763975,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024587,
      "question_number": "140",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient has Normal Pressure Hydrocephalus (NPH) and abdominal tuberculosis. What is the next step?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Start antitubercular therapy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024588,
      "question_number": "106",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A government clerk developed meningitis. What is the most likely organism responsible for this condi...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Pneumococcus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7545787545787546,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6967247979583157,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024589,
      "question_number": "13",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A heroin abuser presents with severe back pain and tenderness, along with fever. What is the most li...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Staphylococcus aureus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7177914110429447,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7065217391304348,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024590,
      "question_number": "106",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A government clerk developed meningitis. What is the most likely organism responsible for this condi...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. Pneumococcus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7545787545787546,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.05952688172043011,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024591,
      "question_number": "82",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In a patient suspected of having Progressive Multifocal Leukoencephalopathy (PML), what is the most ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Brain MRI with gadolinium",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7594202898550725,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7648425945489119,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024592,
      "question_number": "143",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the most common organism associated with infections in patients with external ventricular dr...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Skin flora (e.g., Staphylococcus epidermidis)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6835443037974683,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6336608066184074,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024593,
      "question_number": "131",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A child presented with chorea, has a history of flu a few weeks ago for which she received antibioti...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. ASO titer"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024594,
      "question_number": "1",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient from Tanzania presents with jaundice, low platelet count, anemia, confusion, fever, and CS...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. P. Falciparum",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8646080760095012,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.46380664652567977,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024595,
      "question_number": "42",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A 70-year-old male was brought to the ER with fever, confusion, and drowsiness. CSF analysis showed ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Vancomycin, Ceftriaxone, and Ampicillin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7058823529411765,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7240802675585284,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024596,
      "question_number": "43",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An Indian patient came with a headache. He is known to have epilepsy and is on medications. A CT bra...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Cysticercosis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024597,
      "question_number": "81",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A 27-year-old pregnant woman living on a dairy farm presents with fever and neck stiffness. How shou...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Ampicillin, ceftriaxone & vancomycin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6203208556149733,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7688690918089581,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024598,
      "question_number": "155",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A 40-year-old man is seen in the emergency department for evaluation of retinal hemorrhage, hepatosp...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Blood smear"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024599,
      "question_number": "204",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In a girl with Sydenham chorea, what laboratory test is most relevant?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. ASO titer"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024600,
      "question_number": "61",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A female patient with multiple sclerosis (MS) on Natalizumab presents with hemiparesis and hemianopi...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. PLEX (Plasmapheresis)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7739130434782608,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2935862691960253,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024601,
      "question_number": "229",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the duration of acyclovir treatment in HSV encephalitis?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. 14 days"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024602,
      "question_number": "330",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A 40-year-old female, originally from Africa, presents with a history of back pain, gradual bilatera...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Human T lymphotropic virus type 1",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8924889543446245,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6396839474320729,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024603,
      "question_number": "231",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Which of the following statements is true regarding Primary Amoebic Meningoencephalitis (PAM)?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. The primary root of infection is through the cribriform plate."
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024604,
      "question_number": "42",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient from Africa presents with a Brucella infection. What is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Doxycycline",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.743801652892562,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7871132228531695,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024605,
      "question_number": "234",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Infection with retinal whitening and orange spots is most commonly associated with which organism?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Bartonella",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8016528925619835,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6149129925164548,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024606,
      "question_number": "337",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A middle\u2010aged male patient with a history of headache reports fever, night sweats, and weight loss. ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Subdural empyema",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8587360594795539,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5320031782466672,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024607,
      "question_number": "182",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the typical treatment approach for a patient diagnosed with West Nile virus encephalitis?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Supportive care"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024608,
      "question_number": "178",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient known to have MS on interferon therapy shifted to natalizumab after recurrent relapses. Sh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Progressive multifocal leukoencephalopathy (PML)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6771378708551483,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5538623226484498,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024609,
      "question_number": "210",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In a case of Creutzfeldt-Jakob Disease (CJD) with a cortical ribbon sign on MRI, what is the next be...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Reassurance"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024610,
      "question_number": "89",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q89. What is the most common cause of polyradiculoneuropathy?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CMV",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7151515151515152,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.17755063410940752,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024611,
      "question_number": "230",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with meningitis and a positive titer for Brucella requires treatment. What is the most app...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Doxycycline-Ceftriaxone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7662337662337663,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2745382859514422,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024612,
      "question_number": "293",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q293. A 64-year-old man is brought to the emergency room by his family for fever and headache. On ex...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Ceftriaxone and vancomycin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8729792147806005,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7795646205138262,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024613,
      "question_number": "109",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with flaccid weakness and no sensory symptoms. What is the most likely cause?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Poliomyelitis (asymmetric or unilateral)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6084142394822006,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7882161021015258,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024614,
      "question_number": "165",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An 11-year-old girl is referred with rapidly deteriorating school performance and intellectual defic...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Subacute Sclerosing Panencephalitis (SSPE)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024615,
      "question_number": "233",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the most common cause of spinal epidural abscess?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Hematogenous spread from a distant source",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5436893203883495,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.31875577456113335,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024616,
      "question_number": "38",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with HIV has multiple brain MRI lesions. What is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CNS toxoplasmosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.640926640926641,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.19808241534067728,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024617,
      "question_number": "8",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with a known case of congenital heart disease presents with headache, fever, and hemipares...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Antibiotics and aspiration of the lesion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6506666666666666,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7876763177431328,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024618,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the most common artery affected in TB vasculopathy?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Middle cerebral artery"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024619,
      "question_number": "232",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient came with low-grade fever, meningism, encephalopathy, and acute flaccid paralysis...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. West Nile Virus (WNV)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7207207207207207,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.795425667090216,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024620,
      "question_number": "86",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the best treatment to prevent post-herpetic neuralgia?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Antiviral"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024621,
      "question_number": "36",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient had meningococcal meningitis. What medication should be given to his family for prophylaxi...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Rifampin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024622,
      "question_number": "118",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "In the context of West Nile virus infection, which of the following is a common clinical feature?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Flaccid weakness",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7011070110701108,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.19350785340314136,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024623,
      "question_number": "39",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q39. In neurosyphilis, which of the following can be associated?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Small pupils",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5922330097087378,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4397531085070221,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024624,
      "question_number": "211",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the most common brain abscess in patients with HIV?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Toxoplasmosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5888324873096447,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.21078037007240547,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024625,
      "question_number": "77",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with a typical history of Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease (CJD) has a family that wants him to b...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Remove them from the organ donation program",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.59765625,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7410706920729192,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024626,
      "question_number": "253",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "What is the first thing to do in case of acute meningitis when the patient arrives at the emergency ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Start antibiotics",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6419753086419753,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.732371535094829,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024627,
      "question_number": "12",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with HIV presents with pain radiating to the back. MRI of the spine is negative, and CSF i...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Vacuolar myelopathy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024628,
      "question_number": "44",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A stroke patient has a fever, and cardiac consultation shows a pansystolic murmur. What is the treat...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Antibiotics"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024629,
      "question_number": "265",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q265. In a patient with HIV on HAART presenting with multiple lesions with ring enhancement, which o...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Trimethoprim-sulfamethoxazole (TMP-SMX)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7258485639686684,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6154315340042696,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024630,
      "question_number": "12",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q12. A patient presents with orange retinal structures. Which of the following conditions could be r...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Tuberculosis (TB)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8761467889908257,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7790655992352731,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024631,
      "question_number": "13",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with retinal whitening and an orange spot. Which of the following infections coul...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Cytomegalovirus (CMV)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7458745874587459,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2783171521035599,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024632,
      "question_number": "15",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Q15. What is the most common route of spread for an epidural abscess?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Hematogenous",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6175115207373272,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7645522388059701,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024633,
      "question_number": "28",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Patient came with orange retina; what is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Bartonella",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.654320987654321,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5128033845468715,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024634,
      "question_number": "265",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "Light-near dissociation is most commonly described in which of the following conditions?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Adie's pupil",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6877470355731226,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4875397223615989,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024635,
      "question_number": "14",
      "subspecialty": "Neuro-infectious",
      "question_text": "A patient with HIV presents with a 1-month history of bilateral lower extremity weakness and numbnes...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Vacuolar myelopathy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022794,
      "question_number": "291",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Between the optic tract and the visual cortex, which structure is located?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lateral geniculate body",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5901639344262295,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7816316560820713,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022795,
      "question_number": "48",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient has tongue deviation to the left. Which area of the brain is likely affected?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Right medulla",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7024793388429752,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.586798114016288,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022796,
      "question_number": "1",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Prosopagnosia is primarily associated with which brain region?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Temporo-occipital gyrus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5922330097087378,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6129538558124935,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022797,
      "question_number": "96",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "What is the localization of prosopagnosia?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Occipital lobe",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5256410256410257,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4407979407979408,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022798,
      "question_number": "40",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "In a case of Gerstmann syndrome, where is the lesion typically found?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Angular gyrus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6118721461187214,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7351837959489872,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022799,
      "question_number": "33",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Prosopagnosia is localized to which area?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022800,
      "question_number": "123",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following embryogenic cells gives rise to the cerebral cortex?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Telencephalon",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.669683257918552,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4200107584722969,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022801,
      "question_number": "24",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q24. A patient has impaired fluency and repetition but intact comprehension. Where is the localizati...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Frontoparietal operculum",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6172839506172839,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3617108780588114,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022802,
      "question_number": "103",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with fluent speech, impaired comprehension, naming, and repetition. Where is the ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Posterior perisylvian temporal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6394984326018809,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4867030965391621,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022803,
      "question_number": "91",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "In a patient with obstructive hydrocephalus, which cranial nerve is most likely involved?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CN 6",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8285714285714286,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.39557779212395094,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022804,
      "question_number": "63",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient exhibits agraphia, acalculia, and finger agnosia (Gerstmann Syndrome). What type of aphasi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anomia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7843137254901961,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6527027027027027,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022805,
      "question_number": "102",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with ipsilateral tremor and Horner syndrome, and contralateral complete loss of ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Dorsolateral Midbrain"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022806,
      "question_number": "44",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with right-sided weakness, non-fluent speech, impaired repetition and naming, but...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Frontal Perisylvian"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022807,
      "question_number": "51",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q51. Impaired immediate recall is associated with lesions of:",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Medial temporal"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022808,
      "question_number": "90",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q90. What is colpocephaly?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022809,
      "question_number": "241",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is suggestive of a dominant parietal lobe lesion?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Finger agnosia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6574074074074074,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7467435158501441,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022810,
      "question_number": "98",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with loss of sensation in the bilateral upper extremities, with later involvement...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Central Cord Syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022811,
      "question_number": "155",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A female presents with decreased sensation to pinprick in bilateral upper limbs. What is the likely ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Syringomyelia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6967741935483871,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.39460165433173705,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022812,
      "question_number": "110",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "How can one differentiate between conus medullaris syndrome and cauda equina syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Upper and lower motor neuron signs",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.584192439862543,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6234126560665885,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022813,
      "question_number": "435",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A picture shows left tongue deviation and left Horner\u2019s syndrome. What type of lesion is indicated?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Preganglionic"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022814,
      "question_number": "390",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "In a long scenario of a patient with trigeminal neuralgia involving V1, which artery is likely causi...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. SCA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8808664259927798,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6397306397306397,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022815,
      "question_number": "376",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Localization of down-beating nystagmus is most commonly associated with which anatomical region?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Cervicomedullary junction",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7196969696969697,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7681642681642682,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022816,
      "question_number": "258",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Case about Gasterman syndrome (I did not remember the choices).",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Acalculia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6349206349206349,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6859834427633457,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022817,
      "question_number": "351",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Syringomyelia (SCA) is commonly associated with which of the following?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022818,
      "question_number": "272",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "What is the localization of postganglionic Horner's syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Postganglionic"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022819,
      "question_number": "213",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Which type of aphasia is similar to that seen in thalamic lesions?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Transcortical sensory aphasia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5752212389380531,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4874795225836649,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022820,
      "question_number": "83",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q83. A patient presents with Horner's syndrome and a left deviated uvula. What other finding would y...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Right ptosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7109634551495017,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.19759596742923613,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022821,
      "question_number": "259",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q259. Frontal operculum",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022822,
      "question_number": "218",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Which imaging study is indicated in virtually all patients suspected of having glossopharyngeal neur...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. MRI/MRA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7749077490774908,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6747889280752378,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022823,
      "question_number": "162",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q162. A patient presents with upper limb numbness and loss of pinprick sensation around the shoulder...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Syringomyelia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8571428571428571,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5783607850872867,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022824,
      "question_number": "414",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "An 18-year-old female presents with hearing loss and vision loss. What will you see on MRI?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Corpus callosum lesion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6267605633802817,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5555025293500048,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022825,
      "question_number": "238",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q238. A patient with headache, MRI showed a picture of Arnold Chiari malformation. What is the next ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Spine MRI"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022826,
      "question_number": "103",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "What is the localization of laryngeal spasms?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Insula"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022827,
      "question_number": "98",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of Broca's aphasia, where is the lesion typically located?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Frontal lobe",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6278026905829597,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6097734974139468,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022828,
      "question_number": "98",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q98. A 40-year-old man developed ankle dorsiflexion weakness, and sensation over the dorsum of the f...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Lateral portion of the sciatic nerve"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022829,
      "question_number": "15",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "In a case of alexia without agraphia with a visual field defect, the lesion is located in:",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Splenium of corpus callosum"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022830,
      "question_number": "8",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Prosopagnosia localization is associated with which area of the brain?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Occipital lobe",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6509433962264151,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7371216144450345,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022831,
      "question_number": "281",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q281. What is the location of the olfactory gyrus?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Parahippocampal gyrus"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022832,
      "question_number": "92",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario about Weber's syndrome, where is the lesion located?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Midbrain basis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7150259067357513,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7774753636790239,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022833,
      "question_number": "55",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Which language disorder is associated with Gerstmann syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Anomia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5727699530516432,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4962477438966467,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022834,
      "question_number": "53",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "In the lateral geniculate nucleus (LGN), visual information from the ipsilateral eye synapses in whi...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. 2, 3, 5",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8412698412698413,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6324324324324324,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022835,
      "question_number": "12",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "In Wernicke\u2019s Aphasia, the lesion is located in:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022836,
      "question_number": "50",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "What is the characteristic feature of syringomyelia?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022837,
      "question_number": "48",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with Broca\u2019s aphasia. What is the localization of the affected area?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Frontoparietal operculum",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6719367588932806,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7619335347432025,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022838,
      "question_number": "19",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A 20-year-old female presented to the clinic with a history of progressive bilateral upper limb decr...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Syringomyelia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8679775280898876,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5233080251449098,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022839,
      "question_number": "87",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q87. What is the Schaffer collateral?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022840,
      "question_number": "13",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A young female presents with symptoms of bilateral lower limb weakness, loss of all sensory modaliti...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thoracic",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8616187989556136,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7467243009590706,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022841,
      "question_number": "84",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q84. A lesion of the facial nerve in the stylomastoid foramen leads to which of the following?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Paralysis of facial muscles"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022842,
      "question_number": "512",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q512. (Source: Promotion 2023mcqs.txt) Which of the following thalamic structures connects the optic...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Lateral geniculate"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022843,
      "question_number": "2",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Gerstmann syndrome is linked to which area of the brain?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Angular gyrus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.625,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7695031275817302,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022844,
      "question_number": "57",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a clear description of left fourth cranial nerve palsy and a head tilted to ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Left rostral midbrain",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7661691542288557,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.523570358621905,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022845,
      "question_number": "9",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient with headache, MRI showed a picture of Arnold Chiari malformation. What is the next step?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Spine MRI",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6666666666666666,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6640337492146127,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022846,
      "question_number": "91",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q91. A patient came with Broca\u2019s aphasia. What is the localization?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Frontoparietal operculum",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5739910313901345,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7357484369253402,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022847,
      "question_number": "54",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with third nerve palsy and contralateral weakness. Where is the likely localizati...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Base of midbrain"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022848,
      "question_number": "89",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following arteries arise from the internal carotid artery?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. PCA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8045977011494253,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7234533111310363,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022849,
      "question_number": "56",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with third nerve palsy and ipsilateral ataxia. Which of the following syndromes i...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Claude syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022850,
      "question_number": "46",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q46. What is the nerve supply for shoulder adduction and internal rotation?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Subscapular nerve"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022851,
      "question_number": "88",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with upper limb numbness, loss of pain sensation, and is burning her hands. What ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Syringomyelia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.70625,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.19171162897485938,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022852,
      "question_number": "177",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Which muscle is supplied by the 12th cranial nerve?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Hyoid muscle",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.591715976331361,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.44119549747703457,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022853,
      "question_number": "51",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q51. Which structure is involved in vision and not in pupillary responses?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Lateral geniculate body",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6457399103139013,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5066731970123668,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022854,
      "question_number": "74",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q74. A patient presents with a visual field defect, impaired reading, and intact writing. This is a ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Splenium of the corpus callosum",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7220902612826603,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4290174471992654,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022855,
      "question_number": "224",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Which area of the brain is primarily associated with prosopagnosia?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Inferior occipital temporal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.616822429906542,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4100982408042038,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022856,
      "question_number": "50",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with classic trigeminal neuralgia characterized by paroxysmal lancinating facial ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. SCA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.912,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3657142857142857,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022857,
      "question_number": "86",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Which of the following paired muscles is supplied by L5?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022858,
      "question_number": "23",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "In a scenario about AICA syndrome, which artery is involved?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. AICA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022859,
      "question_number": "290",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient with quadriplegia presents with horizontal gaze palsy but has spared vertical gaz...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pons",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8497109826589595,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6973347244617282,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022860,
      "question_number": "132",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Which condition is characterized by ipsilateral Horner's syndrome due to dorsal cerebellar SCA?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Cerebellar ataxia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6460481099656358,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.42198541783510934,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022861,
      "question_number": "12",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q12. A patient with a CT scan showing a \"molar tooth\" appearance is suspected to have which conditio...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Joubert syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6447368421052632,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7942646100369324,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022862,
      "question_number": "288",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "One of the branches of the Internal Carotid Artery (ICA) is:",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Anterior Choroidal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6263736263736264,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.48543225601018947,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022863,
      "question_number": "95",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with classic trigeminal neuralgia. Which artery is most commonly responsible for ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. SCA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022864,
      "question_number": "93",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient with C5\u2013C6 radiculopathy. What muscle is involved?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Infraspinatus"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022865,
      "question_number": "63",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q63. What is the commonest presentation in Arnold-Chiari malformation?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Headache",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6732673267326733,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7919251393123752,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022866,
      "question_number": "113",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient diagnosed with trigeminal neuralgia, what artery is the cause?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Superior Cerebellar",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5809128630705395,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3858732299393122,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022867,
      "question_number": "26",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Where is prosopagnosia localized in the brain?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Occipito-temporal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5294117647058824,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.45130452101175067,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022868,
      "question_number": "3",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "What are the signs of intracranial hypotension observed in brain MRI?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022869,
      "question_number": "174",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient with a history of posterior inferior cerebellar artery (PICA) infarction presents with ver...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Interstitial nucleus of Cajal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7305122494432071,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4251301508867908,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022870,
      "question_number": "24",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "An elderly man with a one-month history of right-sided weakness and confusion has a brain CT attache...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Bridging veins rupture"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022871,
      "question_number": "60",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "In a case of trigeminal neuralgia involving the V2 distribution with decreased sensation in V3, whic...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. SCA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8811188811188811,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7475541579315165,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022872,
      "question_number": "184",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "What is the most common artery to cause trigeminal neuralgia (TN)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022873,
      "question_number": "193",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Where is the localization of internuclear ophthalmoplegia (INO)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pons (MLF)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6971428571428572,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5143631895602068,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022874,
      "question_number": "40",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q40. A lady presents with abnormal eye movements characterized by large amplitude and low frequency ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Cervicomedullary junction",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6993318485523385,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5145153189352084,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022875,
      "question_number": "97",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient with restricted vertical gaze and convergence nystagmus, with pupillary response to light ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Midbrain tectum",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7692307692307693,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7125748502994012,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022876,
      "question_number": "24",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q24. In a scenario about Parinaud's syndrome, where is the lesion located?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Midbrain tectum (dorsal midbrain)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6311111111111111,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.25304790246712106,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022877,
      "question_number": "54",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "What favors central nystagmus over peripheral nystagmus?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022878,
      "question_number": "4",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q4. A patient with a history of PICA infarction two years ago presents with oscillopsia. Where is th...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Interstitial nucleus of Cajal"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022879,
      "question_number": "13",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient with Neuromyelitis Optica (NMO) presents with intractable vomiting. Which area of the brai...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Area postrema"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022880,
      "question_number": "100",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "In a case of internuclear ophthalmoplegia (INO) with left impaired adduction and right abduction nys...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Left medial longitudinal fasciculus (MLF)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022881,
      "question_number": "32",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with right-sided ptosis and deviation of the uvula. Which of the following could ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pre-ganglionic lesion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6703296703296703,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.638939823303884,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022882,
      "question_number": "22",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of an elderly patient who had a stroke and became hyperactive with flight of ideas and...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Caudate",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8507462686567164,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5527172981313218,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022883,
      "question_number": "5",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "In a case of ocular bobbing (eyes fast downward then slowly return to primary position), which area ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pons",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.839344262295082,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.47493940104777543,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022884,
      "question_number": "4",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with one-and-a-half syndrome (unable to move both eyes to the left and cannot add...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Ipsilateral paramedian pontine reticular formation (PPRF) and medial longitudinal fasciculus (MLF)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022885,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "What brain structures are involved in peduncular hallucinosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Midbrain and thalamus"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022886,
      "question_number": "82",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q82. A patient is diagnosed with a rostral vermis defect. What is a common clinical presentation ass...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Wide base gait",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7836990595611285,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4019540791402052,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022887,
      "question_number": "59",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient has impaired adduction of the right eye and nystagmus in the left eye when looking to the ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Right MLF"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022888,
      "question_number": "309",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Pendular hallucination is associated with which type of lesion?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Midbrain lesion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5636363636363636,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7904495808991618,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022889,
      "question_number": "58",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q58. In a patient experiencing hallucinations, where is the lesion likely located?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "B. Temporal lobe",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7022222222222222,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7913392409296104,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022890,
      "question_number": "111",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "Q111. What is the resulting lesion due to a lesion in the splenium of the corpus callosum?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Alexia without agraphia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6285714285714286,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7561169507993993,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022891,
      "question_number": "20",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroanatomy",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with nystagmus at primary gaze and a slow amplitude fast beat to the right. Whic...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Cerebellar hemisphere"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022688,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Patients present with symptoms suggestive of a mitochondrial disorder. What investigation will be mo...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Lactate/pyruvate profile",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6374269005847953,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.42707788813382125,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022689,
      "question_number": "43",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A young patient presents with neuropathy, headache, and visual symptoms. An MRI shows anterior tempo...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Mitochondrial testing for MELAS",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7963800904977375,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7296596994299533,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022690,
      "question_number": "53",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A young patient has tics and seizures, and MRI shows diffuse high signal intensity. How can the diag...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Genetic testing",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.75,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6407155198699055,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022691,
      "question_number": "54",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "In a typical scenario of MELAS, how can the diagnosis be made?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Genetic testing",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5769230769230769,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6951861602106055,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022692,
      "question_number": "62",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q62. A 16-year-old female presented with oculomotor apraxia and ataxia; she had normal immunoglobuli...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Oculomotor apraxia type 2",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7230769230769231,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7100069654051544,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022693,
      "question_number": "137",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A 20-year-old patient presents with ataxia, spasticity, sensorimotor neuropathy, hypometric saccades...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Friedreich's ataxia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8373205741626795,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.643529267994623,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022694,
      "question_number": "33",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q33. Which of the following brain MRI findings is characteristic of Kearns-Sayre Syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022695,
      "question_number": "82",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with ataxia and has a family history of X-linked recessive disorders. What is the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Adrenoleukodystrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7034883720930233,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6382898578020529,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022696,
      "question_number": "25",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "An engineer diagnosed with Huntington\u2019s disease requests that you do not inform his employer about h...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Respect his wishes and record that on file",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.654627539503386,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.44865876481597006,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022697,
      "question_number": "170",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A child with insomnia and low gonadotropin levels underwent an MRI that showed agenesis of the olfac...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Kal-1"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022698,
      "question_number": "19",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q19. What is the typical age of onset for Kearns-Sayre Syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. < 10 years",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7045454545454546,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.29881751358261427,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022699,
      "question_number": "49",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A young male presents with spastic paraparesis and a positive family history. MRI of the brain shows...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Adrenoleukodystrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8215384615384616,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.46127851309490286,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022700,
      "question_number": "179",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A patient came with ataxia, optic atrophy, hearing loss, and slow saccades; what is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. SCA 7",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.768595041322314,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7695560253699789,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022701,
      "question_number": "83",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A 14-year-old boy presents with lancinating pain in his feet. His sister has similar symptoms. There...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Galactosidase activity",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9018492176386913,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7867980950271348,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022702,
      "question_number": "17",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A case of spastic paraplegia with a family history of multiple sclerosis in the brother shows perive...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. SPAST",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9068627450980392,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6767853668028799,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022703,
      "question_number": "68",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A young male presents with early dementia and bilateral lower limb weakness. His brothers are simila...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Adrenoleukodystrophy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022704,
      "question_number": "69",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A 20-year-old patient presents with a 10-year history of lower limb proximal weakness and difficulty...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. 50% affected",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9174825174825175,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.531737067991868,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022705,
      "question_number": "131",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with hypomelanotic lesions. Which condition is most likely?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Tuberous Sclerosis (TS)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022706,
      "question_number": "47",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q47. Which of the following is a major criterion for Tuberous Sclerosis (TS)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Facial angiofibroma"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022707,
      "question_number": "134",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q134. Which gene is associated with oculomotor apraxia and hypercholesterolemia?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. AOA1"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022708,
      "question_number": "138",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "In a scenario about Xeroderma pigmentosum, what are the symptoms associated with skin lesions and ke...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Photosensitivity, freckling, and increased risk of skin cancers",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5995203836930456,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6665992721391023,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022709,
      "question_number": "75",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A young male with diabetes mellitus presents with gait and limb ataxia, lower limb weakness, and hea...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Send him to cardiology to rule out cardiomyopathy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022710,
      "question_number": "166",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q166. In Huntington's disease, how many gene repeats are typically present?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. More than 48 repeats.",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6101694915254238,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7885857113101438,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022711,
      "question_number": "130",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q130. A case of ADHD is presented alongside a hyperpigmented brownish skin lesion with axillary frec...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Neurofibromatosis Type 1 (NF1)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022712,
      "question_number": "144",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with ADHD and hypermelanotic diagnosis. What is the likely condition?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Neurofibromatosis type 1 (NF1)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022713,
      "question_number": "52",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A newly diagnosed Huntington\u2019s disease patient wishes not to inform his employer about his condition...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Document this in his records and respect his wishes",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5847665847665847,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4041526845637584,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022714,
      "question_number": "12",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "In a case of Kearns-Sayre syndrome, what is the most common mutation associated with the condition?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Sporadic large mitochondrial DNA deletion"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022715,
      "question_number": "192",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "In a case of Refsum\u2019s disease, a patient had trouble with vision during the night and has polyneurop...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Refsum\u2019s disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7082152974504249,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.41639557579700714,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022716,
      "question_number": "165",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of Fabry disease, what is the enzyme that is defective?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Globotriaosylceramide",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5826086956521739,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6771653543307087,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022717,
      "question_number": "168",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q168. Case of X-linked inheritance (all the men in the family have similar symptoms); what is the an...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Adrenoleukodystrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6734006734006734,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6103165082587432,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022718,
      "question_number": "177",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q177. Same scenario asking about diagnosis:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Fragile X syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5030674846625767,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7247895229186155,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022719,
      "question_number": "183",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "In a case of Fabry disease, what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022720,
      "question_number": "30",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q30. A patient with Marfanoid habitus and lens dislocation is being evaluated. What treatment will y...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Vitamin B6",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7777777777777778,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4673531476714252,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022721,
      "question_number": "3",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A patient has had two strokes, sensory peripheral neuropathy, and a skin rash. What enzyme is involv...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Alpha-Galactosidase"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022722,
      "question_number": "24",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Which of the following cardiac abnormalities is commonly associated with Kearns-Sayre Syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Cardiac conduction defects",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6287625418060201,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6756330427563304,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022723,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "In the scenario of Wilson's disease, what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. D-penicillamine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6540284360189573,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6836003186122666,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022724,
      "question_number": "31",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "What is the common genetic mutation found in most patients with Kearns-Sayre Syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Large deletion of mitochondrial DNA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.53125,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7103835188080566,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022725,
      "question_number": "100",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A young male patient presented for evaluation of limb numbness. He is complaining of paresthesia and...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Low HDL",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9214536928487691,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6531713900134952,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022726,
      "question_number": "50",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "What is the mode of inheritance for Fahr disease?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022727,
      "question_number": "84",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "How should a young patient with Wilson disease be treated?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Chelation therapy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5352112676056338,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3890165189804179,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022728,
      "question_number": "93",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "What is the key enzyme deficiency in the diagnosis of Fabry Disease?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Alpha galactosidase A"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022729,
      "question_number": "104",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A patient with ADHD has a mother with brown pigmentations in her neck. What is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Neurofibromatosis type 1 (NF1)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6046511627906976,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7752935171005615,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022730,
      "question_number": "93",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "What is the case for the diagnosis of Fabry Disease?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Alpha galactosidase",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5230769230769231,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5413533834586466,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022731,
      "question_number": "145",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of symptoms suggestive of Fabry disease, what is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Agalsidase (Enzyme replacement therapy)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022732,
      "question_number": "437",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "What would be the response to a dopamine agonist in a patient who does not respond to L-dopa?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Aromatic decarboxylase deficiency",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5768025078369906,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3913392141138733,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022733,
      "question_number": "341",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A scenario is typical for Guillain-Barr\u00e9 Syndrome (GBS) except that the patient had intermittent epi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Acute Intermittent Porphyria (AIP)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022734,
      "question_number": "439",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with recurrent falls and an abnormal brain MRI, with a family history of similar ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Adrenomyeloneuropathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7311827956989247,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7734664548823841,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022735,
      "question_number": "44",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of spinal muscular atrophy (SMA) suggestive of autosomal recessive inheritance, w...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. 25% affected"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022736,
      "question_number": "97",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A child with insomnia and low gonadotropin levels underwent an MRI that showed agenesis of the olfac...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Kallmann Syndrome (Kal-1)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7603305785123967,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7190861494526416,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022737,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A patient exhibits startle reflex with sudden closure of his eyelids, worsening with cold. What is t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Chloride channel",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7530120481927711,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7136611046667262,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022738,
      "question_number": "76",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q76. What are potential endocrine abnormalities associated with Kearns-Sayre Syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Hypothyroidism and diabetes mellitus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5075528700906344,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5431400282885431,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022739,
      "question_number": "450",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q450. A scenario presents with oculomotor apraxia, spasticity, myoclonic seizures, and hepatosplenom...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Glucocerebrosidase",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8113207547169812,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7839054089826172,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022740,
      "question_number": "294",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q294. What is the likely diagnosis for a patient presenting with hyperammonemia and low L-citrulline...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Urea cycle disorder",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6217008797653959,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.15013687092019373,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022741,
      "question_number": "26",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Which disease is characterized by the presence of globoid cells?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Krabbe Disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.56,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7853524131188339,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022742,
      "question_number": "235",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A patient with ADHD presents with light brown lesions. What is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Neurofibromatosis (NF)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022743,
      "question_number": "40",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of Fabry disease, what is the enzyme that is defective?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Alpha-galactosidase A",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5826086956521739,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5419681620839363,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022744,
      "question_number": "86",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Case of X-linked inheritance (all the men in the family have similar symptoms); what is the answer?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Adrenoleukodystrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.662020905923345,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7305703873209594,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022745,
      "question_number": "55",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Same scenario asking about diagnosis:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022746,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Pediatric patient had a bullous rash that worsens with sun exposure, and he has conjunctivitis; what...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Xeroderma pigmentosum"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022747,
      "question_number": "59",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A child presents with encephalopathy and hyperammonemia. What is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Urea cycle disorder."
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022748,
      "question_number": "22",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q22. A patient presents with blurry vision, ataxia, and ophthalmoplegia. Which condition is most lik...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "B. Ataxia with ocular apraxia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6513157894736842,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.44986357435197816,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022749,
      "question_number": "51",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Pediatric patient had mental retardation, tremor, and ataxia; his sister had ovarian insufficiency; ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Bilateral cerebellar hyperintensity"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022750,
      "question_number": "296",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q296. An infant presents with a head circumference at the 100th percentile, height at the 10th perce...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Neurofibromatosis Type 1 (NF1)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022751,
      "question_number": "15",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A 7-year-old boy presents with myoclonic epilepsy, cognitive decline, and hypotonia. Pathology shows...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Neuronal ceroid lipofuscinosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7777777777777778,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6474945533769063,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022752,
      "question_number": "235",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "In a case of Neurofibromatosis type 1 (NF1) with light brown macules, what is the name of the skin l...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Caf\u00e9 au lait spot",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.723404255319149,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.745350962055251,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022753,
      "question_number": "297",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A child with a facial port wine stain and a CT brain showing tram-track calcification is diagnosed w...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Sturge-Weber syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7054794520547946,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6012147764612168,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022754,
      "question_number": "6",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A 2-week-old infant developed progressive hypotonia and feeding difficulties. He was found to have i...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Maple syrup urine disease"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022755,
      "question_number": "175",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A 60-year-old male presented at age 40 with ophthalmoplegia and visual symptoms but no visual loss. ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Kearns-Sayre syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.743455497382199,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6925512104283054,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022756,
      "question_number": "9",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A 4-year-old male patient presents with microcephaly, seizures, and has a musty odor to his urine. W...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Phenylketonuria",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7539267015706806,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3425988700564972,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022757,
      "question_number": "10",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Phenylketonuria (PKU) is caused by a defect in the hydroxylation of which amino acid?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Phenylalanine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7387387387387387,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7377900935226879,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022758,
      "question_number": "11",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is a symptom of untreated Phenylketonuria (PKU)?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Severe mental retardation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6126126126126126,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6653710901351101,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022759,
      "question_number": "2",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A child presents with areas of sun-exposed pigmentation, eye problems, and seizures. What is the mos...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Sturge-Weber syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7055214723926381,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5580390886513336,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022760,
      "question_number": "22",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Pediatric patients with presentations suggestive of Menkes disease (friable hair) will typically sho...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Low copper level",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6805194805194805,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.236976252642049,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022761,
      "question_number": "45",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A child is diagnosed with ataxia-telangiectasia. Which of the following is a common non-neurologic s...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. High incidence of malignancies",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7535410764872521,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4937230825620819,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022762,
      "question_number": "81",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A 10-year-old boy has impaired vision, progressive cognitive decline, and myoclonic seizures. MRI sh...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Neuronal ceroid lipofuscinosis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022763,
      "question_number": "123",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A child presents with short stature, microcephaly, sensorineural hearing loss (SNHL), developmental ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Cerebellar abnormalities",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7396694214876033,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7460518731988472,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022764,
      "question_number": "16",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q16. A 4-year-old male patient with microcephaly and seizures has brown hair and musty odor urine. W...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Phenylketonuria"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022765,
      "question_number": "154",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Which of the following metabolic diseases is associated with bilateral subdural hematoma?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Glutaric Aciduria Type 1 (GA1)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6197183098591549,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5678441729943876,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022766,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A hypotonic baby with colorless hair and seizures has a CT brain showing subdural collection. What l...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Elevated glutaric acid and 3-hydroxyglutaric acid in urine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022767,
      "question_number": "147",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A young boy presents with cognitive decline and behavioral changes, and has very long-chain fatty ac...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. X-linked adrenoleukodystrophy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022768,
      "question_number": "92",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A patient with developmental delay and bilateral basal ganglia high signal intensity. What is the di...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Leigh syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5492227979274611,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.47164906580016247,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022769,
      "question_number": "178",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A child presents with encephalopathy and hyperammonemia. What is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Urea cycle disorder",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6015625,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6118465035432544,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022770,
      "question_number": "100",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Pediatric patient had hepatosplenomegaly, hypotonia, flaccid paralysis, MRI showed white matter chan...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Glucocerebrosidase"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022771,
      "question_number": "173",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A pediatric patient had bullous lesions that worsen with sun exposure, and he has conjunctivitis. Wh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Xeroderma pigmentosa"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022772,
      "question_number": "17",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "In a typical scenario of CADASIL, which gene is associated with the condition?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. NOTCH3 gene"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022773,
      "question_number": "185",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "In a case of Gaucher disease, which visual manifestation is commonly observed?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Vertical gaze palsy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022774,
      "question_number": "169",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A patient presents in early childhood with developmental delay. Brain MRI shows symmetric high T2 si...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Leigh syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4389836175192243,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022775,
      "question_number": "375",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A 5-year-old male with developmental delay shows bilateral symmetrical putamen and globus pallidus s...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Leigh disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8166666666666667,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5853880447638977,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022776,
      "question_number": "171",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q171. A pediatric patient had hepatosplenomegaly, hypotonia, flaccid paralysis, and MRI showed white...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Glucocerebrosidase deficiency"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022777,
      "question_number": "287",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q287. A patient presents with an ischemic stroke and exhibits marfanoid habitus. What is the most ap...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Vitamin B6",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7673716012084593,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7631175794714669,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022778,
      "question_number": "181",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "In a typical scenario of MELAS, how can the diagnosis be made?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Lactate-pyruvate profile",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5172413793103449,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7640572114859701,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022779,
      "question_number": "242",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q242. A young patient has tics and seizures. An MRI showed diffuse high signal intensity. How can th...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Skin biopsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7365079365079366,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7412755716004813,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022780,
      "question_number": "178",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with seven flat brown lesions. What is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Caf\u00e9 au lait spots",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6533864541832669,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.536702017051362,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022781,
      "question_number": "103",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q103. A patient with stroke and marfanoid features is being treated. What is the recommended treatme...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Vitamin B6"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022782,
      "question_number": "181",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Patient came with Leber optic neuropathy; what is your next step?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. ECG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6428571428571429,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6791058912672855,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022783,
      "question_number": "449",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q449. In a scenario suggestive of oculomotor apraxia, what is the gene associated with this conditio...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. APTX",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8319327731092437,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7499212102111567,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022784,
      "question_number": "5",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A patient with mitochondrial encephalomyopathy, lactic acidosis, and stroke\u2010like episodes (MELAS) pr...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Muscle biopsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8285077951002228,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7308641975308642,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022785,
      "question_number": "4",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A patient with a family history of speech and motor issues is brought in for evaluation. The family ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "C. Chromosomal analysis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8143100511073254,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7577109987107011,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022786,
      "question_number": "22",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "An elderly 50-year-old patient presents with seizures and has a history of recurrent emergency room ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Porphyria",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8120649651972158,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7969357690041249,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022787,
      "question_number": "47",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "You inherited a 14-year-old boy who was diagnosed with Duchenne muscular dystrophy (DMD) at age 4. Y...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. CK level"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022788,
      "question_number": "17",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old female presents with progressive gait and limb ataxia. Genetic testing reveals a mutat...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Spinocerebellar ataxia type 3 (SCA3)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7168949771689498,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7718663747977539,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022789,
      "question_number": "10",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "In a child with dopa\u2010responsive dystonia, what is the gene responsible?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. GCH1",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8023255813953488,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7920812603648425,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022790,
      "question_number": "10",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "In a child with dopa-responsive dystonia, what is the gene responsible?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. GCH1",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8023255813953488,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.056120993056216116,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022791,
      "question_number": "16",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q16. A patient with migraine headaches has a family history of early stroke (father died young from ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Skin biopsy for eosinophilic inclusions",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6818181818181818,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6800593938335225,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022792,
      "question_number": "2",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q2. (Source: Part 2 - 2023mcqs.txt) Which of the following is associated with Congenital Myasthenia ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Dok7"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022793,
      "question_number": "247",
      "subspecialty": "Neurogenetics",
      "question_text": "Q247. A 40-year-old male patient presented with a history of left-sided weakness, numbness, and dysa...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. NOTCH 3",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.88,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7183745867935177,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023364,
      "question_number": "8",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A multiple sclerosis (MS) patient who is receiving natalizumab developed progressive multifocal leuk...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Start plasmapheresis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023365,
      "question_number": "5",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A multiple sclerosis (MS) patient who is receiving natalizumab and developed progressive multifocal ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Stop natalizumab"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023366,
      "question_number": "31",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A female known to have relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS) is stopping disease-modifying t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Fingolimod",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8355555555555556,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6832085561497326,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023367,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A 16-year-old patient presents with confusion. An MRI shows bilateral white matter changes. What is ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Acute disseminated encephalomyelitis (ADEM)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6430517711171662,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7496951467360378,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023368,
      "question_number": "22",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient diagnosed with relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS) started on disease-modifying ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Alemtuzumab"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023369,
      "question_number": "28",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What is the cardinal feature in a case scenario suggestive of Neuromyelitis Optica (NMO)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Optic neuritis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6590038314176245,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7864553642686125,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023370,
      "question_number": "67",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q67. In a case of multiple sclerosis, the criteria for diagnosis were questioned due to the presence...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Only dissemination in time was met",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7149606299212599,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4038755736868944,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023371,
      "question_number": "72",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q72. MRI findings in patients with NMOSD typically show which of the following?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023372,
      "question_number": "66",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "The most common cause of myelopathy in young adults in temperate zones is:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Multiple Sclerosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5934959349593496,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.43411284335560507,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023373,
      "question_number": "53",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In a patient with bilateral optic neuritis and longitudinally extensive transverse myelitis (LETM), ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Aquaporin 4 antibodies"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023374,
      "question_number": "93",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young female presents with a new relapse of sudden left-sided weakness for 5 days after a history ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Emergent pulse steroid"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023375,
      "question_number": "73",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with multiple sclerosis (MS) who was on disease-modifying therapy (DMT) stopped her medica...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Rebound inflammatory activity due to immune reconstitution after stopping DMT",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7009472259810555,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7473705100218297,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023376,
      "question_number": "38",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In the scenario of a patient with Giant Cell Arteritis (GCA), which vessel is most commonly involved...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Posterior ciliary artery",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6510067114093959,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6663966791535891,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023377,
      "question_number": "54",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A case scenario describes a patient with recurrent oral ulcers presenting with neurological deficits...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Neuro Beh\u00e7et's disease"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023378,
      "question_number": "136",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is considered a red flag for Multiple Sclerosis (or demyelinating disease)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Persistent enhancement for 3 months",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5191256830601093,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.48061234766844596,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023379,
      "question_number": "74",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Multiple Sclerosis, what finding is expected on Visual Evoked Potentials (VEP)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Prolonged P100",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7045454545454546,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3147868509699152,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023380,
      "question_number": "139",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Patient was diagnosed with Multiple Sclerosis and suffers from lower limb tonic spasm. What is the t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Carbamazepine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023381,
      "question_number": "120",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is suggestive of Multiple Sclerosis, but not vascular white matter disease?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Involving U fibers"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023382,
      "question_number": "135",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient known to have Neuromyelitis Optica (NMO) after a long episode of cervical myelitis reporte...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Carbamazepine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023383,
      "question_number": "107",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What is the risk of developing clinically definite MS (CDMS) in patients with no MRI lesions after 5...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. 16%",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8813559322033898,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7264186873175067,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023384,
      "question_number": "102",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with multiple sclerosis (MS) presented with shortness of breath (SOB) and an allergic reac...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Stop infusion and treat the patient"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023385,
      "question_number": "169",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young lady presents with acute right diplopia. No previous attacks. Brain MRI shows enhancement of...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Start steroids",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7153652392947103,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.31463928383359663,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023386,
      "question_number": "151",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young female presents with symptoms of bilateral lower limb weakness, loss of all sensory modaliti...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Transverse myelitis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023387,
      "question_number": "141",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "To prevent PML in patients receiving Tysabri, what is the best approach?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Check JC virus before starting treatment",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5533596837944664,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5972841901066925,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023388,
      "question_number": "75",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "For patients who cannot tolerate high-dose corticosteroids or have refractory disease, which of the ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Rituximab",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.791907514450867,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6069164906038029,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023389,
      "question_number": "159",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q159. A young female treated for confirmed HSV presents with behavioral changes, a normal MRI of the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-NMDA receptor encephalitis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6167883211678832,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.444681797952826,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023390,
      "question_number": "160",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A 22-year-old female presented with acute confusion and later developed seizures and orofacial dyski...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Anti-NMDA receptor antibodies",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8043875685557587,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6170341547773455,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023391,
      "question_number": "174",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young male patient with isolated optic neuritis is concerned that he may have multiple sclerosis. ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Brain MRI"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023392,
      "question_number": "145",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "An MS patient on natalizumab started to have shortness of breath, tachycardia, and tachypnea after t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Stop the dose and start prophylaxis management"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023393,
      "question_number": "185",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with symptoms of stiff person syndrome. What is the most likely antibody associat...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-GAD"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023394,
      "question_number": "218",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following MRI characteristics is the best predictor of future disability in patients wi...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Baseline T2 lesion volume",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6453333333333333,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3979848866498741,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023395,
      "question_number": "197",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Opsoclonus-myoclonus syndrome presents with subacute opsoclonus (irregular, rapid eye movements) and...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Paraneoplastic"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023396,
      "question_number": "175",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q175. A young male is brought by his father with complaints of catatonia, psychosis, seizure, and dy...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Anti-NMDA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023397,
      "question_number": "186",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What is the most appropriate diagnostic method for primary CNS angiitis (PACNS)?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Biopsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7368421052631579,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5916106773197748,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023398,
      "question_number": "242",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In a case of transverse myelitis, MRI reveals multiple enhancing lesions in the brain and spinal cor...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Multiple sclerosis (MS)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6956521739130435,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.41525821596244133,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023399,
      "question_number": "260",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What does the absence of brain lesions predict regarding the risk of MS over the next 15 years?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Low risk (<20%)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7315175097276264,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7571667596207473,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023400,
      "question_number": "254",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What is the estimated risk of developing multiple sclerosis (MS) in patients with normal brain MRI a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. 10%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023401,
      "question_number": "244",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which MRI feature is most closely associated with the progression of disability in multiple sclerosi...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "B. T1 hypointensities",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7051282051282052,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6523083484379998,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023402,
      "question_number": "274",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A 19-year-old man presents with confusion. MRI shows right thalamic hyperintensity on FLAIR and arou...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. NMO antibodies",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7918367346938775,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4561123841785394,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023403,
      "question_number": "219",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which medication is used to improve MS-related fatigue?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Amantadine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6428571428571429,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6261479723454751,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023404,
      "question_number": "262",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In idiopathic partial transverse myelitis, what is the likelihood of evolving multiple sclerosis at ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. 30%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023405,
      "question_number": "256",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old woman with a greater-than-20-year history of multiple sclerosis is nonambulatory and d...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Pregabalin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8816855753646677,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7375853141915745,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023406,
      "question_number": "164",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient came with a 1-month history of fever, headache, and personality changes. Brain MRI shows b...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Multiple sclerosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8755364806866953,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6390041493775933,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023407,
      "question_number": "314",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A case of relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS) with a history of type 1 diabetes mellitus a...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Fingolimod",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7930174563591023,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5569815690437132,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023408,
      "question_number": "319",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In a scenario involving a patient with multiple sclerosis, what criteria are applied for diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. McDonald criteria",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6759581881533101,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7987314531657039,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023409,
      "question_number": "326",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A female patient is admitted to the psychiatric ward with delusions and hallucinations, and then dev...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-NMDA receptor encephalitis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023410,
      "question_number": "276",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A female patient with optic neuritis has one periventricular MRI lesion. What is the next step in ma...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Start interferon",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6524390243902439,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7049250535331906,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023411,
      "question_number": "315",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with painful visual loss in one eye with disc edema. What is the recommended trea...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. IV methylprednisolone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7027027027027027,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6439362668207711,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023412,
      "question_number": "305",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young female with bilateral optic neuritis, brain MRI showed enhanced contrast in the posterior se...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. PLEX."
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023413,
      "question_number": "363",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with multiple sclerosis (MS) presents with tonic spasms. What is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Carbamazepine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7456140350877193,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5466818984318206,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023414,
      "question_number": "334",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A 28-year-old female with a history of multiple sclerosis (MS) on natalizumab presents with left-sid...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. PLEX (5 sessions)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023415,
      "question_number": "360",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A 35-year-old female patient, medically free, presents with heat intolerance, lower limb weakness, s...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Brain MRI",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8223140495867769,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7514042398985323,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023416,
      "question_number": "303",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following infections is more common with a B-cell lysis agent compared to interferon?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Oral herpes",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6666666666666666,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7706645056726094,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023417,
      "question_number": "304",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q304. What is the risk of malignancies associated with the use of a B-cell lysis agent?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. 1.5%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023418,
      "question_number": "336",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A 32-year-old female presents with bilateral blurry vision and decreased visual acuity. Initial MRI ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. NMOSD",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.871447902571042,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2734999365723709,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023419,
      "question_number": "238",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with type 1 diabetes mellitus presents with a history of stiffness. What is the most likel...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Anti-GAD65"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023420,
      "question_number": "382",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What is the pathophysiology of sarcoidosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023421,
      "question_number": "366",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In a typical scenario of a stiff person, an EMG showed continuous contractions. What is the antibody...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-GAD",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8295819935691319,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.683805862566074,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023422,
      "question_number": "367",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient came with bilateral optic neuritis; MRI showed high signal intensity in the bilateral opti...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-MOG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7029972752043597,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4922498825739784,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023423,
      "question_number": "377",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient known to have multiple sclerosis (MS) but also has psoriasis. What disease-modifying thera...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Dimethyl fumarate (DMF)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023424,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In the scenario of a male patient with unilateral optic neuritis and brain MRI showing 3 supracortic...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Clinically Isolated Syndrome (CIS)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.773784355179704,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6510784500858943,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023425,
      "question_number": "4",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In the scenario of a male patient with isolated optic neuritis, what will help you in the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Brain MRI",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7452471482889734,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.735526429997396,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023426,
      "question_number": "353",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young female with subacute behavioral change is admitted under psychiatric care. An MRI shows mesi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Ovarian teratoma"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023427,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A 20-year-old female patient known to have multiple sclerosis is on interferon therapy. She had righ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Urinalysis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023428,
      "question_number": "29",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A child presents with symptoms suggestive of multiple sclerosis (MS). What is the most significant r...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Epstein-Barr Virus (EBV)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7396449704142012,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.47297297297297297,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023429,
      "question_number": "16",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is considered a red flag in multiple sclerosis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023430,
      "question_number": "57",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In a case of multiple sclerosis fulfilling diagnostic criteria, what is the next step after acute ma...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Start treatment",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6948051948051948,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6020671834625323,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023431,
      "question_number": "30",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q30. Treatment of acute attacks of NMOSD includes which of the following?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023432,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In a pediatric patient with progressive focal seizures, hemiparesis, and MRI evidence of unilateral ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-GLUR3",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8844621513944223,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7526320693189229,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023433,
      "question_number": "10",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of Miller Fisher syndrome, which antibody is typically associated with this condition?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Anti-GQ1B"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023434,
      "question_number": "87",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q87. Autonomic dysfunction can be associated with which of the following antibodies?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Anti-ganglionic Acetylcholine antibody"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023435,
      "question_number": "62",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young female with relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS) on Interferon presents with MRI sh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Start Natalizumab",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7799564270152506,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6890927624872579,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023436,
      "question_number": "85",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q85. Increased liver enzymes and increased erythrocyte sedimentation rate are findings that support ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Sarcoidosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7277777777777777,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6195721438324988,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023437,
      "question_number": "71",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q71. In a case scenario of a patient with MS on natalizumab, attached to an MRI brain and spine, wha...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Anti-JCV antibodies"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023438,
      "question_number": "27",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A female patient came in with encephalitis (history of seizure, fever, psychosis). What is the likel...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-NMDA (the common cause of limbic encephalitis in young females)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.672566371681416,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2473002159827214,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023439,
      "question_number": "112",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q112. What is recommended regarding the use of corticosteroids during the first trimester of pregnan...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Use should be avoided if possible",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6781609195402298,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7916050295857988,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023440,
      "question_number": "103",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "For progressive multiple sclerosis, which of the following is a characteristic of the primary progre...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Leg weakness",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7133757961783439,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7735155018392013,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023441,
      "question_number": "140",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young female presented with decreased vision in the right eye and was found to have optic neuritis...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Start beta interferon",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7972027972027972,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7400452488687783,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023442,
      "question_number": "65",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q65. In a typical case of stiff person syndrome (history of lordosis), what is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Stiff person syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6219081272084805,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7534100802940892,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023443,
      "question_number": "122",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario, what is the best next step of treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pulse steroid course",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5769230769230769,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6186648805536951,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023444,
      "question_number": "88",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q88. A female patient with multiple neurological complaints, hearing loss, and retinal artery occlus...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Susac syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7540983606557377,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6571548468317248,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023445,
      "question_number": "106",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q106. In a patient who has had an episode of optic neuritis and a normal MRI, what is the 5-year ris...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. 16%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023446,
      "question_number": "91",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In a longitudinal study, what was the 15-year risk of developing Multiple Sclerosis (MS) based on cl...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. 25%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023447,
      "question_number": "123",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient diagnosed with multiple sclerosis and started on disease-modifying therapy (DMT) one year ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Astrocytopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8644338118022329,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3225594390270626,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023448,
      "question_number": "148",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "An MS patient who is pregnant received IV Methylprednisolone. What will happen to the newborn?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Transient leukocytosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6814814814814815,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5988221923752454,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023449,
      "question_number": "153",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with two or more clinical attacks of multiple sclerosis requires:",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Start DMT",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.592,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.47005261027923917,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023450,
      "question_number": "162",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A 7-year-old boy has recurrent focal seizures involving the right side of his body. Sometimes, these...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. None of the above",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9125596184419714,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.519910605444941,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023451,
      "question_number": "170",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which cells in the brain are mostly responsible for MS pathogenesis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Oligodendrocytes"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023452,
      "question_number": "158",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q158. A young female patient presents with right leg weakness and incontinence, with no previous neu...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Multiple Sclerosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8264462809917356,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7017441860465117,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023453,
      "question_number": "217",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q217. What is the recommended action in the event of anaphylaxis with Natalizumab?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Discontinue treatment"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023454,
      "question_number": "202",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Ataxia can be present in which of the following conditions?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023455,
      "question_number": "163",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with relapsing\u2013remitting multiple sclerosis on disease-modifying therapy reports bilateral...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Fingolimod"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023456,
      "question_number": "150",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with one clinical attack of multiple sclerosis has:",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023457,
      "question_number": "246",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In young adults presenting with nausea and vomiting, which condition is associated with the area pos...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Neuromyelitis optica (NMO)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6933333333333334,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6839169507282306,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023458,
      "question_number": "252",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which medication is contraindicated if the patient has a history of seizure?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Dalfampridine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023459,
      "question_number": "240",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Decreased consciousness and ataxia can be present in which condition?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Bickerstaff brainstem encephalitis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023460,
      "question_number": "239",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is associated with acute pandysautonomia?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Ach antibodies",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5943396226415094,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6232823838196696,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023461,
      "question_number": "249",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q249. A 24-year-old female with a previous history of mouth ulcers presents with a 4-day history of ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Neuro-Behcet's disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.851063829787234,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6581734214507524,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023462,
      "question_number": "259",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q259. In idiopathic acute transverse myelitis, which region is most commonly affected?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Thoracic region",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6859504132231405,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3745746563223084,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023463,
      "question_number": "263",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with transient headache and on-off hemiplegia, lumbar puncture shows CSF lymphocy...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. HaNDL",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.806060606060606,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6450348432055749,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023464,
      "question_number": "258",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What is the most common diagnostic test used to assess MS?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. MRI"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023465,
      "question_number": "272",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q272. A 45-year-old lady has progressive lower limb weakness and spasticity. She has two siblings wi...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Primary Progressive Multiple Sclerosis (PPMS)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7359307359307359,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6322400558269365,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023466,
      "question_number": "275",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A child presents with decreased vision in both eyes, papilledema, and no confusion. An orbital MRI s...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. MOG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.836272040302267,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7602092318986877,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023467,
      "question_number": "255",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q255. The presence of characteristic MS lesions may allow patients to meet MS diagnostic criteria. W...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "B. Inferior temporal pole",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7481296758104738,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.41634014172571904,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023468,
      "question_number": "264",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q264. What is the significance of lesion location in predicting rapid disability in CIS patients?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Infratentorial and spinal cord lesions are most predictive."
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023469,
      "question_number": "284",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following risk factors is associated with an odds ratio of 3.6 for multiple sclerosis?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Epstein-Barr virus seropositivity",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6666666666666666,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7952038369304556,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023470,
      "question_number": "302",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q302. What is the percentage of infections observed in patients treated with a B-cell lysis agent co...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. 60%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023471,
      "question_number": "309",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q309. A patient with multiple sclerosis (MS) experiences spasticity and difficulty with gait. Which ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Dalfampridine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8095238095238095,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4561696792393689,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023472,
      "question_number": "268",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q268. What is the DMT that requires antiviral prophylaxis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Alemtuzumab",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.64,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5767229343825359,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023473,
      "question_number": "310",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young female with a history of two optic neuritis attacks presents with new symptoms of spinal cor...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Relapsing-Remitting Multiple Sclerosis (RRMS)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6793103448275862,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5319148936170213,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023474,
      "question_number": "311",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following scenarios is most likely to develop multiple sclerosis (MS)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023475,
      "question_number": "371",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What is a red flag for multiple sclerosis (MS)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023476,
      "question_number": "372",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A 24-year-old female developed abrupt vision loss in the left eye, which then affected the right eye...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Pulse steroids",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8571428571428571,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6358314940984551,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023477,
      "question_number": "313",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "An MRI of the spine suggests demyelination. The patient complains of contractions and pain, and the ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Diazepam"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023478,
      "question_number": "375",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A case of MOG presenting with bilateral optic neuritis and brain MRI shows anterior optic nerve swel...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. MOG Antibody Disease (MOGAD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6810551558752997,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7884260965720604,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023479,
      "question_number": "379",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q379. Which DMT causes immune thrombocytopenic purpura (ITP)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Alemtuzumab"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023480,
      "question_number": "357",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q357. A female patient with a long history of MS on fingolimod presents with decreased vision and ha...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Stop fingolimod",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7886710239651417,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7719298245614035,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023481,
      "question_number": "316",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young patient presents with a history of encephalopathy, weakness, and hearing loss. An MRI of the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Susac syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023482,
      "question_number": "270",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q270. What is a red flag for demyelination?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023483,
      "question_number": "331",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Young lady with SLE complained of seizures and confusion this time. SLE nephritis on dialysis. What ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. PRES",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.71875,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.771755961598018,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023484,
      "question_number": "378",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q378. Which DMT has a 20% increased risk of autoimmune disorders?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Alemtuzumab"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023485,
      "question_number": "13",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A woman with multiple sclerosis on fingolimod has a brain MRI showing new active lesions in the left...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Switch to natalizumab"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023486,
      "question_number": "381",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q381. A young female with relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS) has a previous history of tr...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Rebound disease"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023487,
      "question_number": "97",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario of the young female with sudden left-sided weakness, what would you give for he...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pulse steroid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7492795389048992,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6755615281244001,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023488,
      "question_number": "269",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q269. Which symptom indicates worsening in primary progressive multiple sclerosis (PPMS)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Leg weakness"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023489,
      "question_number": "1",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with multiple sclerosis presented with leg weakness that improved with steroids but recurr...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Urinalysis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7555555555555555,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5915562913907285,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023490,
      "question_number": "152",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following has an indication in multiple sclerosis disease progression?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Cortical atrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6612903225806451,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.24847611659093427,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023491,
      "question_number": "248",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In patients with high-risk clinically isolated syndrome (CIS), which of the following factors is pre...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Presence of T2 lesions"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023492,
      "question_number": "380",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A trident sign is observed on MRI spine in a case of relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS) t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Sarcoidosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7276264591439688,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6873728680957597,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023493,
      "question_number": "6",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In which case would steroids have an effect?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023494,
      "question_number": "220",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is considered a red flag in multiple sclerosis (MS)?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023495,
      "question_number": "385",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q385. What is the risk of multiple sclerosis (MS) in 15 years if there is a history of optic neuriti...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. 30% with need to start DMT"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023496,
      "question_number": "144",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q144. A 19-year-old female presented with a history of seizures. One month before presentation, she ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. NMDA encephalitis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023497,
      "question_number": "154",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following MRI characteristics is the best predictor of future disability in patients wi...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Baseline T2 lesion volume"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023498,
      "question_number": "128",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient diagnosed with Multiple Sclerosis is being evaluated. What would be a favorable factor in ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "C. Young age of onset",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6858974358974359,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6521421870113625,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023499,
      "question_number": "306",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following treatments causes rebound multiple sclerosis (MS) if stopped?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Fingolimod"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023500,
      "question_number": "373",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What is the most important risk factor for multiple sclerosis (MS)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Epstein-Barr virus (EBV)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5898617511520737,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7890121227753417,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023501,
      "question_number": "58",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "AQP4-IgG is a specific, pathogenic biomarker of which condition?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023502,
      "question_number": "177",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young male had an isolated single attack of focal neurological deficit and did not start on DMT. W...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. 20%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023503,
      "question_number": "23",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A male patient with limbic encephalitis (seizures, psychosis) is asked about the most common antibod...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-NMDA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023504,
      "question_number": "273",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient was treated for multiple sclerosis and presents with myelitis, showing a trident sign and ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Astrocytopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8296943231441049,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.24706375838926176,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023505,
      "question_number": "156",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A female with pure sensory neuropathy and nerve conduction studies showing a demyelinating neuropath...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-MAG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7933333333333333,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7652401477832512,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023506,
      "question_number": "245",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What type of cell is primarily involved in MS lesions?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. T cell",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6625,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7790386567026478,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023507,
      "question_number": "282",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is a characteristic of primary progressive multiple sclerosis according to Mc...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023508,
      "question_number": "129",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which DMT causes ITP? (attached picture of purpura)",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Alemtuzumab"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023509,
      "question_number": "101",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "For patients without brain lesions at the onset of optic neuritis, when was the risk of developing M...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. First 5 years"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023510,
      "question_number": "121",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q121. A patient was diagnosed with Multiple Sclerosis for 8 months, based on an initial attack of tr...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. MS pseudorelapse",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8559670781893004,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.45115257958287597,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023511,
      "question_number": "271",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "An MS patient with a history of recurrent relapses has been stable on natalizumab for the past 7 mon...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Brain MRI with contrast",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.775974025974026,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.742106845745214,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023512,
      "question_number": "125",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q125. What DMT has a 30% increased risk of secondary autoimmune disorders?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Alemtuzumab"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023513,
      "question_number": "92",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A woman who had repeated episodes of vomiting for one month visited the ER and was given omeprazole....",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Neuromyelitis Optica (NMO)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7966942148760331,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.790962462195339,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023514,
      "question_number": "253",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A female patient with MS on glatiramer acetate wants to take the flu vaccine. What is the best recom...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023515,
      "question_number": "95",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In patients with optic neuritis, what was the risk of developing MS when MRI evidence of prior demye...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. 72%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023516,
      "question_number": "80",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Gadolinium contrast enhancement is present in essentially all cases of which condition?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Acute Disseminated Encephalomyelitis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5566343042071198,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.613035019455253,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023517,
      "question_number": "173",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "The periventricular white lesion typical of multiple sclerosis (MS) follows a specific pattern in th...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Venules",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7943661971830986,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7688026713308952,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023518,
      "question_number": "115",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with autonomic dysfunction and pupillary changes (miosis). What is the antibody a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-Ganglionic Acetylcholine antibody"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023519,
      "question_number": "247",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In the evaluation of autoimmune myelopathy, what is standard practice regarding MRI?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. It is standard",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6307692307692307,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.609159626500667,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023520,
      "question_number": "3",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "An MS patient on disease-modifying therapy (DMT) lost follow-up and presented to the ER with low pla...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Alemtuzumab"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023521,
      "question_number": "359",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with a known case of Multiple Sclerosis (MS) used a medication that causes flushing. What ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. NRF2"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023522,
      "question_number": "143",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Typical multiple sclerosis (MS) presentation includes one or more episodes of:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023523,
      "question_number": "33",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q33. In the scenario of a patient with Giant Cell Arteritis (GCA) presenting with loss of vision, wh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. High-dose corticosteroids",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6472019464720195,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6848072562358276,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023524,
      "question_number": "243",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q243. In the case of PML (Progressive Multifocal Leukoencephalopathy) occurring in patients treated ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Plasmapheresis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023525,
      "question_number": "17",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is considered a red flag in multiple sclerosis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Complete ophthalmoplegia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5655737704918032,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4020492259717118,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023526,
      "question_number": "298",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with multiple sclerosis on fingolimod for a couple of years developed weakness and slurred...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Repeat JCV and perform an urgent MRI of the brain"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023527,
      "question_number": "185",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q185. In a case of Susac syndrome, a young female presents with sensorineural hearing loss (SNHL), e...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Immune-mediated vascular endotheliopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.623015873015873,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7108367324440524,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023528,
      "question_number": "133",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Young female patient with multiple sclerosis suffers from fatigue, what is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Amantadine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.710204081632653,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.571513825343147,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023529,
      "question_number": "11",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following statements is true regarding multiple sclerosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023530,
      "question_number": "335",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q335. Which condition is associated with features of encephalitis and an ovarian tumor?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-NMDA receptor encephalitis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023531,
      "question_number": "171",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q171. A young lady presents with unilateral optic neuritis. Brain MRI shows enhancing lesions. What ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. OCB testing"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023532,
      "question_number": "279",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A child with a history of vaccination presents with confusion. What is the likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. ADEM"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023533,
      "question_number": "157",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In a patient with ataxia and breast cancer presenting with opsoclonus myoclonus, which antibody is m...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-Ri",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8172757475083057,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6594101123595506,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023534,
      "question_number": "161",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Demyelination is commonly linked to which organism?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. EBV"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023535,
      "question_number": "96",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A woman who had an episode of nausea and vomiting, along with visual changes in both eyes at differe...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Pulse steroid"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023536,
      "question_number": "251",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following medications is considered safe for use in pregnant patients with multiple scl...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Glatiramer acetate (GA)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7162162162162162,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6001493373156618,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023537,
      "question_number": "149",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In evaluating a patient for multiple sclerosis, which of the following is NOT typically assessed?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Family history of migraines"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023538,
      "question_number": "168",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS) has been stable on disease-modifying th...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Sphingosine 1 phosphate receptor modulator"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023539,
      "question_number": "126",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Young lady, with encephalopathy and hearing impairment, no visual symptoms mentioned, MRI attached s...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Microvascular endothelial proliferation damage",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6733668341708543,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6703162023041098,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023540,
      "question_number": "221",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What is the chance for the development of Multiple Sclerosis (MS) with an abnormal MRI, especially p...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. 44\u2009\u2013\u200993%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023541,
      "question_number": "2",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q2. What virus is most commonly associated with multiple sclerosis (MS)?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. EBV",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8095238095238095,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7065600752410064,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023542,
      "question_number": "122",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Patient was diagnosed with Multiple sclerosis and has psoriasis. What is an appropriate DMT for her ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Dimethyl fumarate",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7304964539007093,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6393762183235867,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023543,
      "question_number": "142",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A middle-aged female presents with lower limb stiffness mainly affecting hip muscles and has lumbar ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-GAD and amphiphysin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023544,
      "question_number": "146",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q146. (Source: Part I 2018mcqs.txt) Typical features of multiple sclerosis include:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Relapses and remissions"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023545,
      "question_number": "172",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with intractable vomiting and nausea was admitted under GI and investigated with no identi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Optic neuritis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8208333333333333,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6118366212836899,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023546,
      "question_number": "138",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Young lady presented with acute decrease in vision bilaterally, MRI brain done showed hyperintensity...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. IV methylprednisolone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7922077922077922,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5129916997473836,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023547,
      "question_number": "364",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q364. A scenario presents a case of limbic encephalitis. What is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-NMDA receptor encephalitis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6132404181184669,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5683336342300054,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023548,
      "question_number": "362",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In a patient with stiff person syndrome, which antibody is typically found?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Anti-GAD",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7336683417085427,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7960533007832367,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023549,
      "question_number": "267",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q267. What is the treatment for LETM with spasms?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Carbamazepine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6143790849673203,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.663547680668923,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023550,
      "question_number": "147",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A female with a history of Type 1 diabetes mellitus presented with symptoms of axial and peripheral ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-GAD",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.865979381443299,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.34206402507275574,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023551,
      "question_number": "361",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A female patient with a known case of multiple sclerosis (MS) came with increased sensory symptoms a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Pseudorelapse"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023552,
      "question_number": "183",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q183. In a scenario of limbic encephalitis, what is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Autoimmune encephalitis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5576208178438662,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6105527638190955,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023553,
      "question_number": "68",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In patients with NMOSD, neurologic involvement is seen in what percentage of cases?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. 25-30%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023554,
      "question_number": "16",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient presents with areflexia (tendon reflexes absent), ophthalmoplegia, and impaired f...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. IVIG"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023555,
      "question_number": "29",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q29. A patient with multiple sclerosis (MS) on disease-modifying therapy (DMT) developed hyperthyroi...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Alemtuzumab",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7965616045845272,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7467239967239967,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023556,
      "question_number": "27",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q27. (Source: SleepNeurology) A patient on Natalizumab develops progressive multifocal leukoencephal...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Stop Natalizumab",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6762589928057554,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.38179888564605996,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023557,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q41. A patient with multiple sclerosis developed tonic spasms. Which medication is most appropriate ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Carbamazepine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.784452296819788,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6770900633156739,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023558,
      "question_number": "43",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A 35-year-old female patient, medically free, came with heat intolerance, lower limb weakness, and s...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Brain MRI",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8180039138943248,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7393536695862277,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023559,
      "question_number": "23",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q23. (Source: CriticalCareNeurology) A patient with relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS) an...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Dimethyl fumarate",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.813141683778234,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7695352839931153,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023560,
      "question_number": "28",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q28. A young man diagnosed with left eye optic neuritis was planned to start Teriflunomide. He has n...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Bilateral onset should suspect a diagnosis other than multiple sclerosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6247191011235955,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.25738117304382363,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023561,
      "question_number": "38",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with a known case of Multiple Sclerosis used a medication that causes flushing. What is th...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. NRF2",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6551724137931034,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7241458381105251,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023562,
      "question_number": "266",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A lady diagnosed with RRMS is about to start DMT. What will you give her?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Dimethyl fumarate",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6513761467889908,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7992781231201123,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023563,
      "question_number": "58",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A female patient with a known case of multiple sclerosis (MS) came with increased sensory symptoms a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pseudorelapse",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.730593607305936,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.30879327310135074,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023564,
      "question_number": "60",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q60. A patient came with bilateral optic neuritis; MRI showed high signal intensity in the bilateral...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-MOG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7093333333333334,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.48981288981288984,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023565,
      "question_number": "71",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q71. A 72-year-old woman presents with a 2-week history of new-onset severe temporal headache and tr...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Start prednisolone 60\u201380 mg/day",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8270042194092827,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5808930425752855,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023566,
      "question_number": "84",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient diagnosed with multiple sclerosis (MS) is on treatment but shows no improvement, continuin...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Perform Schirmer's test",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7836456558773425,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5695285359801489,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023567,
      "question_number": "81",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q81. A young female has a history of left-sided weakness that lasted for 10 days and then improved. ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Level a regular exercise and conservative measures",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7556390977443609,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2882211011186664,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023568,
      "question_number": "67",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young lady known to have MS is pregnant and asks about the percentage risk of her baby having MS. ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. 2 \u2013 4%",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8223684210526315,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6014696058784235,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023569,
      "question_number": "69",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with optic neuritis and one periventricular lesion is evaluated. What do the McDonald crit...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. Fulfilling only space but not time",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5957446808510638,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6552033876555884,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023570,
      "question_number": "85",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q85. Which of the following indicates disease progression in Multiple Sclerosis (MS)?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. All of the above",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6022304832713755,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5374377965513251,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023571,
      "question_number": "70",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q70. (Source: Neuroanatomy) In neuromyelitis optica (NMO), which statement is correct?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023572,
      "question_number": "83",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q83. A patient known to have multiple sclerosis (MS) on natalizumab develops an infusion reaction. W...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Stop natalizumab infusion and treat the reaction",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5450733752620545,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5354481177145041,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023573,
      "question_number": "64",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q64. (Source: Neuroanatomy) What is the odds ratio for infectious mononucleosis as a risk factor for...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "D. 2.5",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8778625954198473,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.23074562749309604,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023574,
      "question_number": "76",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q76. (Source: Neuroanatomy) What is the estimated risk of progressive multifocal leukoencephalopathy...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. 1 in 10,000",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7796610169491526,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6192640114051501,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023575,
      "question_number": "141",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q141. (Source: MovementDisorders) MS pathophysiology is most commonly associated with which of the f...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. EBV",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7761194029850746,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7157916710155516,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023576,
      "question_number": "166",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "An MS patient developed a tremor. What is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Propranolol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6875,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5193108516371356,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023577,
      "question_number": "130",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q130. Which of the following antibodies is associated with myoclonus dystonia?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Anti-GB1"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023578,
      "question_number": "111",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q111. A patient with multiple sclerosis developed a tremor. What is the most appropriate treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Propranolol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7649402390438247,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7147858874225693,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023579,
      "question_number": "208",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q208. In a case of testicular cancer, which antibody is most likely to be present?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-MA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7488151658767772,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7354538401861909,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023580,
      "question_number": "204",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q204. A 34-year-old male presents with myoclonus and abnormal eye movements. What is the most likely...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Autoimmune encephalitis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.723404255319149,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.570144141572713,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023581,
      "question_number": "176",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q176. (Source: Neuromuscular) A young female presented with unilateral optic neuritis features. She ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. She has DIS and DIT",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8283185840707965,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7431294326241135,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023582,
      "question_number": "186",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young patient with multiple new acute strokes on MRI has a history of sensorineural hearing loss. ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Susac syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6253101736972705,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4584999200383816,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023583,
      "question_number": "142",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q142. Which risk factor has an odds ratio of 0.5 and is considered unknown in its association with m...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "C. Alcohol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7945205479452054,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.23924031245213662,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023584,
      "question_number": "319",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with a long history of multiple sclerosis presents with fatigue. What medication would you...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Amantadine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8246153846153846,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.610989969472307,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023585,
      "question_number": "451",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q451. A patient receiving their third infusion of Natalizumab develops an allergy with shortness of ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Stop infusion and treat anaphylaxis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6203473945409429,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5813240702901512,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023586,
      "question_number": "210",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q210. A patient with optic neuritis and one periventricular lesion. What is her McDonald criteria?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Fulfilling only space but not time",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5555555555555556,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7878534031413612,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023587,
      "question_number": "3",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q3. (Source: SleepNeurology) A lady known to have multiple sclerosis (MS) presents with a history of...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Change to a different disease-modifying therapy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7712854757929883,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6240292370945637,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023588,
      "question_number": "275",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q275. (Source: Neuromuscular) A patient diagnosed with multiple sclerosis (MS) continues to experien...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Sarcoidosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8438661710037175,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6891658328026926,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023589,
      "question_number": "274",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A female patient came with relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS) and an attached MRI of the ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. T Cell",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8595988538681948,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7897654584221748,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023590,
      "question_number": "115",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In a paraneoplastic case, what should be done next?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023591,
      "question_number": "103",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS) received 5 days of intravenous methylpr...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. PLEX",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8359788359788359,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6047153536515238,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023592,
      "question_number": "118",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which factor is associated with a worse prognosis in multiple sclerosis (MS)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Male sex",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6915887850467289,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5283108268182896,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023593,
      "question_number": "69",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q69. Which of the following indicates disease progression in multiple sclerosis (MS)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Brain atrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6639344262295082,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6226345765203013,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023594,
      "question_number": "279",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "An MS patient developed tonic spasms. What is the appropriate treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Carbamazepine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023595,
      "question_number": "193",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with focal seizures that progressed to complex partial seizures and multiple epi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Glur3 antibody",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7806691449814126,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7571130396572558,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023596,
      "question_number": "87",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which condition is based on astrocyte pathology?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. NMOSD",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5193370165745856,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7051303903187319,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023597,
      "question_number": "49",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with onset of right optic neuritis. MRI of the brain shows a brain stem lesion th...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Dissemination in both time and space",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7491166077738516,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6672100605496041,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023598,
      "question_number": "129",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient has worsening neurological symptoms for 3 years with positive oligoclonal bands (OCB). Wha...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Ocrelizumab"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023599,
      "question_number": "220",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Patient came with focal seizure with secondary generalization; he has focal atrophy in the brain; wh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. GluR3"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023600,
      "question_number": "104",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with multiple sclerosis experiences painful muscle spasms multiple times per day. Which me...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Baclofen"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023601,
      "question_number": "79",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Patient presents with focal seizures with secondary generalization and progressive unilateral cortic...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. GluR3",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8894117647058823,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5574452003023431,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023602,
      "question_number": "247",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A 24-year-old female presents with fever, headache, meningeal signs and psychiatric manifestations. ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Anti-NMDA receptor encephalitis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023603,
      "question_number": "405",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q405. What is the next step to confirm small vessel CNS vasculitis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Brain Biopsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6220095693779905,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7275214298741565,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023604,
      "question_number": "117",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with RRMS on Natalizumab presents with worsening lower limb weakness and blurred vision ov...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Stop Natalizumab",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6504424778761062,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.618701343143126,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023605,
      "question_number": "82",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q82. In a long scenario for a patient with neuropathy and asthma, what is the next step in managemen...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. ANCA testing for Churg-Strauss syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023606,
      "question_number": "124",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In a scenario involving diabetes mellitus with stiff person syndrome, what is the most likely antibo...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-GAD"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023607,
      "question_number": "8",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q8. A patient with MS on medication presents with blurry vision and macular edema. What medication i...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Fingolimod"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023608,
      "question_number": "205",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In the scenario of Susac syndrome, which of the following findings can be seen on MRI?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. High signals in the corpus callosum",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5694915254237288,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5357068929828193,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023609,
      "question_number": "13",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In the same case of Mononeuritis Multiplex with weight loss and fever, what is the most appropriate ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Cyclophosphamide",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.75,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2466270402868195,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023610,
      "question_number": "336",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A female with a history of systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE) presents with acute onset periorbital ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Brain MRI/MRV"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023611,
      "question_number": "88",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What is known about the pathology of multiple sclerosis (MS)?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023612,
      "question_number": "204",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In patients treated with natalizumab, which of the following is considered a risk factor for develop...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. High index of JC virus in serum",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6253687315634219,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7660639144774253,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023613,
      "question_number": "279",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following cranial nerves is primarily responsible for controlling the muscles of mastic...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Trigeminal nerve (V)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6774193548387096,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.24714736586550135,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023614,
      "question_number": "541",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q541. What is the first-line treatment for Chronic Inflammatory Demyelinating Polyneuropathy (CIDP)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. IV Immunoglobulin (IVIG)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6906474820143885,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2940650925335035,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023615,
      "question_number": "338",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q338. A patient with multiple sclerosis (MS) is experiencing fatigue but has stable disease and no m...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Amantadine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8338028169014085,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6069698759598346,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023616,
      "question_number": "440",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q440. A patient has stiffness and neuromyotonia on EMG, recurrent loss of consciousness, but is curr...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Isaac's syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7584650112866818,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7159439626417612,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023617,
      "question_number": "197",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young patient in his 30s presented to the emergency room with limb weakness that started one week ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Peripheral demyelination."
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023618,
      "question_number": "49",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following cranial nerves is primarily responsible for the sense of smell?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Olfactory nerve (CN I)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6367041198501873,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5572254335260116,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023619,
      "question_number": "295",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q295. A female patient had optic neuritis with one non-enhancing periventricular lesion. According t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Dissemination in Space but not Time"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023620,
      "question_number": "378",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with a history of MS relapse 3 weeks ago while on interferon presents with worsening weakn...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Urinalysis (Rule out UTI as trigger)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6108949416342413,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7886944818304172,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023621,
      "question_number": "415",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A female patient presents with a first episode of optic neuritis and MRI showing multiple white-matt...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Teriflunomide",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8520499108734403,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7404303510758777,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023622,
      "question_number": "84",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "An MS patient presents with tonic spasms. What is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Carbamazepine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6702702702702703,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3403434304456878,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023623,
      "question_number": "395",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which disease-modifying therapy (DMT) requires pre-antiviral agent prophylaxis?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Alemtuzumab",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7004608294930875,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.20764617691154422,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023624,
      "question_number": "83",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is a classic presentation of Heerfordt syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Uveoparotid fever",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6278026905829597,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6823917685886236,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023625,
      "question_number": "97",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient is diagnosed with opsoclonus-myoclonus-ataxia syndrome. Which of the following antibodies ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-Ri",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8603988603988604,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7729093336569972,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023626,
      "question_number": "358",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A lady with sleep disturbances and increased sleep has an MRI showing diencephalic hyperintensity. W...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. AQP4 antibody test"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023627,
      "question_number": "318",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with optic neuritis has an MRI of the spine that shows long-sequence enhancement and is OG...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Send for aquaporin-4 antibodies (NMO)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023628,
      "question_number": "357",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A female patient with a known case of multiple sclerosis (MS) shows MRI findings consistent with neu...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Demyelination (Astrocytopathy in NMO)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7435294117647059,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5806309287447606,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023629,
      "question_number": "514",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In a case of primary progressive multiple sclerosis with typical MRI features and normal cerebrospin...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. 4-pyridine derivative (Dalfampridine/4-aminopyridine)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.736318407960199,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3276990718124084,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023630,
      "question_number": "67",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q67. A 16-year-old patient presents with confusion, and MRI shows bilateral white matter changes. Wh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Acute Disseminated Encephalomyelitis (ADEM)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023631,
      "question_number": "81",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q81. A female patient, known to have relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis and maintained on diseas...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Plasma exchange",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9057591623036649,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7748221767514372,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023632,
      "question_number": "318",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A long scenario describes a lady who came with optic neuritis and had papilledema. What will you sen...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-MOG"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023633,
      "question_number": "83",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young female patient presents with right leg weakness and urinary incontinence. Brain MRI shows tw...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Multiple sclerosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7851002865329513,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.23864574731626756,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023634,
      "question_number": "320",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young male patient with a known case of relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS) on natalizum...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Plasma exchange"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023635,
      "question_number": "106",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What is the best way to prevent progressive multifocal leukoencephalopathy (PML) in patients with MS...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Pretreatment JC virus titer levels screen",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6348448687350835,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7627763496143959,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023636,
      "question_number": "48",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is considered a red flag in multiple sclerosis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023637,
      "question_number": "125",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Chronic Inflammatory Demyelinating Polyneuropathy (CIDP), what is a common finding...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Elevated protein levels",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6213592233009708,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7039337474120083,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023638,
      "question_number": "105",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old lady presented to the ER with worsening weakness in all four extremities and sensory s...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Serum AQP-4"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023639,
      "question_number": "107",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young female patient presents with right leg weakness and incontinence. An MRI report shows two pe...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Start treatment",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7974882260596546,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4614800759013283,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023640,
      "question_number": "84",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young female with a previous history of two optic neuritis attacks presents with new symptoms of s...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Neuromyelitis optica spectrum disorder",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.706766917293233,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2618627104674438,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023641,
      "question_number": "88",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young female presented with a typical history of optic neuritis. Brain and spine MRI were normal. ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. 16% risk of conversion to MS"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023642,
      "question_number": "103",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with typical optic neuritis, and her brain MRI was abnormal. What is the most ap...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Initiate corticosteroids"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023643,
      "question_number": "57",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q57. A patient presents with a triad of areflexia, ophthalmoplegia, and ataxia (Miller Fisher syndro...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Intravenous immunoglobulin (IVIG)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023644,
      "question_number": "99",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What are the characteristic findings in the cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) of a patient with Acute Inflam...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Elevated protein with normal cell count",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5961123110151187,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.34953032587266614,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023645,
      "question_number": "82",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old male, known case of type 1 diabetes mellitus, presented 3 months ago with optic neurit...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Fingolimod",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9162303664921466,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5669130767269946,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023646,
      "question_number": "113",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "An MS female patient had a relapse 3 weeks ago, which improved after she received steroids. Two days...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. UA and urine culture",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7782426778242678,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7194928684627575,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023647,
      "question_number": "78",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q78. In a patient with ataxia-telangiectasia, which of the following immunoglobulin levels is typica...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Extremely low or absent serum immunoglobulin A",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.583554376657825,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7552088679051627,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023648,
      "question_number": "14",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In the management of a patient diagnosed with PML, what is the most appropriate step?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Stop natalizumab",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6125461254612546,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7991964204182267,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023649,
      "question_number": "58",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following disease-modifying therapies (DMT) is known to cause paresthesia?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Teriflunomide",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7088607594936709,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6361844698462751,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023650,
      "question_number": "208",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Trigeminal neuralgia in young age, diagnosis is best made by:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. MRI",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7239263803680982,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.19385058851789574,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023651,
      "question_number": "68",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A female patient with a long history of multiple sclerosis (MS) on fingolimod presents with spastici...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. 4-aminopyridine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8207343412526998,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5513656746840603,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023652,
      "question_number": "13",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario [Implicitly related to an MS/NMO context], what is the most likely diagnosis fo...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Neuromyelitis optica",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6239554317548747,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6501019120644472,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023653,
      "question_number": "43",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What is the diagnosis for a patient presenting with symptoms consistent with Chronic Inflammatory De...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. CIDP",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8851351351351351,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.39297248417517117,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023654,
      "question_number": "312",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A female patient with jaw claudication and temporal headache, who also has joint pain and diffuse mu...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. ESR",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7344632768361582,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5712375859434683,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023655,
      "question_number": "50",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q50. A lady presents with personality changes and hearing loss. MRI findings are pending. Which cond...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Susac's syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7609254498714653,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6458638062733626,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023656,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A 55-year-old patient presented with left lower limb paresthesia and heaviness that progressively wo...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Acute Inflammatory Demyelinating Polyneuropathy (AIDP)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7564625850340136,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6442764747136289,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023657,
      "question_number": "33",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "An 18-year-old boy presents with vertigo and an exaggerated dermatological reaction during IV insert...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Beh\u00e7et's disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.811965811965812,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5481883164900172,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023658,
      "question_number": "15",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of neuromyelitis optica (NMO) with bilateral optic neuritis and transverse myelitis ex...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Serum aquaporin-4 antibody testing"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023659,
      "question_number": "89",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following adverse effects is most commonly associated with the first infusion of a B-ce...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Flushing and throat irritation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6745562130177515,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3994627782041443,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023660,
      "question_number": "38",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q38. A patient with multiple sclerosis presents with the left eye showing no abduction or adduction,...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. One-and-a-half syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023661,
      "question_number": "16",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient presents with areflexia (tendon reflex not obtained), ophthalmoplegia, and impair...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. IVIG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7330677290836654,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.020517928286852588,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023662,
      "question_number": "46",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with relapsing\u2013remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS) has been on fingolimod for 18 months. H...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Natalizumab",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8468809073724007,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7494627304603552,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023663,
      "question_number": "3",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A 54-year-old male presents with neck pain and tingling sensations in both hands. He has a history o...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Rheumatoid Pannus"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023664,
      "question_number": "196",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q196. A 15-year-old girl presents to the emergency room with confusion and seizure. Her parents note...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. NMDA receptor antibody"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023665,
      "question_number": "3",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with multiple sclerosis presents with optic neuritis (ON). The MRI shows one periventricul...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Clinically Isolated Syndrome (CIS)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6181015452538632,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5022374856904985,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023666,
      "question_number": "29",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "In multiple sclerosis (MS), what is the pattern of distribution of lesions?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Venules",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6574074074074074,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6654596660631663,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023667,
      "question_number": "187",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What is the odds ratio for smoking as a risk factor for multiple sclerosis?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "C. 2.0",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8222222222222222,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.24243890636341642,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023668,
      "question_number": "268",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient with systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE) complicated by nephritis presents with acute behav...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. SLE cerebritis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023669,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which statement is true regarding multiple sclerosis (MS)?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023670,
      "question_number": "30",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is a feature of optic neuritis due to multiple sclerosis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Pain with eye movement",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5683453237410072,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6435713279819744,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023671,
      "question_number": "188",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What is the mechanism of action of Ocrelizumab?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023672,
      "question_number": "66",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young lady with systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE) complained of seizures and confusion. She has S...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Posterior Reversible Encephalopathy Syndrome (PRES)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6651982378854625,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6622633910592026,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023673,
      "question_number": "265",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "What is the best way to diagnose small vessel vasculitis?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023674,
      "question_number": "206",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is a probable risk factor for multiple sclerosis with an odds ratio of 1.4?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Infectious mononucleosis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023675,
      "question_number": "404",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A 78-year-old female presents with bilateral headaches and facial pain when eating, accompanied by d...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Ischemic optic neuropathy due to short ciliary artery involvement"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023676,
      "question_number": "70",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A patient over 60 years old presents with a 1-month history of blurry vision and headache. What is t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Erythrocyte Sedimentation Rate (ESR)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023677,
      "question_number": "31",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which one of the following is a feature of optic neuritis due to multiple sclerosis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Pain with eye movements"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023678,
      "question_number": "179",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is the most common presentation of Giant Cell Arteritis (GCA)?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Headache"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023679,
      "question_number": "327",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Young lady with SLE who has a neurological deficit. What is your diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "D. Lupus Cerebritis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6186440677966102,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.631967970434247,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023680,
      "question_number": "301",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "An 18-year-old woman is referred to your office after branch retinal artery occlusion occurred in ea...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Susac syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9039692701664532,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5242424242424243,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023681,
      "question_number": "30",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A key feature associated with optic neuritis in the context of Multiple Sclerosis (MS) is:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Pain with eye movement"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023682,
      "question_number": "342",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q342. An elderly patient presented with a visual field defect but denied having left homonymous hemi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Visual anosognosia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023683,
      "question_number": "338",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young female patient was admitted to the psychiatric ward with non-specific abnormal movements, ag...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Paraneoplastic encephalitis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7862595419847328,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6716781365802011,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023684,
      "question_number": "69",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "A young lady presents with persistent nausea and vomiting. Brain MRI is unremarkable. Based on the s...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Optic neuritis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7988505747126436,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6551451881744013,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023685,
      "question_number": "214",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q214. Regarding Teriflunomide 14 mg compared to interferon, which statement is correct?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023686,
      "question_number": "209",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroimmunology",
      "question_text": "Q209. (Source: Vascularneurologystroke) Which of the following is counted as a red flag of Multiple ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Complete gaze palsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6206896551724138,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3198981756470089,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024636,
      "question_number": "554",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q554. What is a common nerve conduction study (NCS) or electromyography (EMG) finding in ALS?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Fasciculations",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6327272727272727,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6866952789699571,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024637,
      "question_number": "19",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q19. What are the histological findings observed in a case of dermatomyositis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024638,
      "question_number": "84",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "The typical age of onset for Hyperkalemic Periodic Paralysis is:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. First decade"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024639,
      "question_number": "561",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q561. A 34-year-old man had difficulty climbing stairs and respiratory difficulties requiring BiPap....",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Acid maltase deficiency",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6937669376693767,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.709785335935322,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024640,
      "question_number": "458",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q458. In a scenario about a patient with eosinophils on pathology, what condition is suggested?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Calpainopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6594982078853047,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7961062321447466,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024641,
      "question_number": "69",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q69. What percentage of patients with ocular Myasthenia Gravis have positive AChR-binding antibodies...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. 30%",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8761061946902655,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6165182008138128,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024642,
      "question_number": "60",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A post-bariatric surgery patient presents with symptoms of vitamin B12 deficiency, but serum levels ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Copper"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024643,
      "question_number": "30",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q30. Case of a patient with weak hip adductors, which nerve is affected?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Obturator",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.700507614213198,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.43223689745099686,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024644,
      "question_number": "55",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient diagnosed with breast cancer underwent chemotherapy and radiation. An EMG showed myokymia ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Radiation-induced plexopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.692144373673036,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.611501934576152,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024645,
      "question_number": "140",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 34-year-old man has progressive difficulty climbing stairs and respiratory difficulties requiring ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Acid maltase deficiency",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7167919799498746,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4616051308719015,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024646,
      "question_number": "15",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In the scenario of Kennedy disease (gynecomastia and family history), which of the following is corr...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Normal CK",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7434944237918215,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6482708541345193,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024647,
      "question_number": "54",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What type of muscle biopsy finding is associated with Kearns-Sayre Syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Ragged-red fibers on Gomori trichrome stain",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5514705882352942,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.710240427426536,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024648,
      "question_number": "157",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q157. A patient with myotonia is being evaluated. Which of the following conditions is associated wi...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Myotonic dystrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7009646302250804,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6651346865824077,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024649,
      "question_number": "249",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a patient with painful diabetic neuropathy who is nonambulatory and has severe spasticity, which ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Intrathecal baclofen"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024650,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q21. Peripheral neuropathy case: what is the antibody?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti MAG"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024651,
      "question_number": "65",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with bilateral foot drop and left ulnar neuropathy with abductor digiti minimi we...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Multifocal Motor Neuropathy (MMN)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7597765363128491,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.704274919780561,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024652,
      "question_number": "487",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with polymyalgia rheumatica is on steroids (5 mg) post-myocardial infarction and is also t...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Stop atorvastatin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8558558558558559,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7328427177819613,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024653,
      "question_number": "166",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young lady presents with weakness in knee extension and numbness in the medial aspect of the thigh...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Femoral nerve",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7910863509749304,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6513424052960647,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024654,
      "question_number": "497",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q497. A patient with myasthenia gravis and thymus hyperplasia is on pyridostigmine and is experienci...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Low and slow steroid regimen",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7302231237322515,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6128308658591296,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024655,
      "question_number": "161",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Typical scenario of Myasthenia Gravis in a young lady with fluctuating ptosis. What is the best sero...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Anti-Ach receptor antibodies"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024656,
      "question_number": "257",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "When should Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome be suspected?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024657,
      "question_number": "96",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of Acute Inflammatory Demyelinating Polyneuropathy (AIDP) on day 5, what will the nerv...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Sural sparing with affected median and ulnar nerves"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024658,
      "question_number": "150",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with generalized weakness, bilateral ptosis, respiratory involvement, and areflex...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Fast repetitive nerve stimulation (RNS) will show a 10% decrement"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024659,
      "question_number": "22",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In hyperkalemic periodic paralysis, which of the following is a characteristic feature?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Triggered by rest",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.625,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7813105854982552,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024660,
      "question_number": "39",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is a characteristic feature of Kearns-Sayre Syndrome (KSS)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Chronic progressive external ophthalmoplegia (CPEO)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5047923322683706,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.214371617558629,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024661,
      "question_number": "521",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with right upper limb weakness and intrinsic hand muscle atrophy with diminished ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Multifocal motor neuropathy (MMN)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6984126984126984,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7928433608138923,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024662,
      "question_number": "38",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is assessed in the examination of femoral nerve function?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Hip flexion, knee extension & medial leg sensation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5683453237410072,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6702053602506092,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024663,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which of the following may be elevated in patients with Kearns\u2013Sayre syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Lactate and pyruvate concentrations",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5641025641025641,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4985049124305852,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024664,
      "question_number": "237",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient who underwent radiation therapy for breast cancer 28 months ago presents with numbness in ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. MRI"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024665,
      "question_number": "13",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q13. Which condition is characterized by myotonia that worsens with exercise?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Paramyotonia congenita"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024666,
      "question_number": "531",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A typical case of Hirayama disease presents with right upper limb weakness with preserved brachiorad...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Focal cervical cord atrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7538461538461538,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.766443787902348,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024667,
      "question_number": "520",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Acute Inflammatory Demyelinating Polyneuropathy (AIDP), what is the characteristic...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Progressive, symmetrical muscle weakness with absent deep tendon reflexes"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024668,
      "question_number": "463",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A case about ulnar nerve injury presents with claw hand. What is the likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Ulnar nerve palsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6387832699619772,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7808373590982287,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024669,
      "question_number": "32",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In patients with generalized Myasthenia Gravis, positive AChR-binding antibodies are found in what p...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. 80%",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8931297709923665,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7541080389648726,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024670,
      "question_number": "2",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with a picture of limb-girdle muscular dystrophy (LGMD) underwent three surgeries under ge...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. He still has the risk",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7149187592319055,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6422055137844611,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024671,
      "question_number": "165",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A pregnant lady presents with hyperemesis gravidarum and sensory disturbances in her distal limbs. W...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Thiamine deficiency",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7283582089552239,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6307168491764056,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024672,
      "question_number": "24",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 50+ year old male presents with weakness in hand flexors and quadriceps. What is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Inclusion Body Myositis (IBM)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024673,
      "question_number": "254",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q254. What percentage of Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome patients experience recurrence?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. 2-5%",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8125,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2532188841201717,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024674,
      "question_number": "428",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with clear symptoms of periodic paralysis lasting for hours. What is the next tes...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Long exercise test"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024675,
      "question_number": "38",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In the context of periodic paralysis, which of the following statements is true regarding serum pota...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Always low in hypokalemic periodic paralysis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5481481481481482,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.47104337631887455,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024676,
      "question_number": "33",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q33. Scenario of progressive bulbar palsy: what is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Bulbar onset ALS"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024677,
      "question_number": "79",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with upper extremity painful neuropathy and atrophy. What is the recommended trea...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Duloxetine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7455197132616488,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2807138744962579,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024678,
      "question_number": "563",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 35-year-old obese female has delayed muscle relaxation, complains of tingling in her hands, and ha...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. TFT",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8047058823529412,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7983659177122848,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024679,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the effect of cold in hypokalemic periodic paralysis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. May induce an attack"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024680,
      "question_number": "63",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q63. In congenital myasthenia gravis, which channel types are involved?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Slow channel",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6415094339622641,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6450212836991904,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024681,
      "question_number": "58",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient with volar hand weakness may be suspected of having which condition?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Inclusion Body Myositis (IBM)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024682,
      "question_number": "43",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which of the following conditions is characterized by paralysis that typically occurs in the first t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Hypokalemic Periodic Paralysis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7192575406032483,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6916129032258065,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024683,
      "question_number": "68",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In an elderly patient presenting with neuropathy and weakness, which of the following is a recommend...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Fat aspiration"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024684,
      "question_number": "67",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with hand stiffness that worsens and becomes weak with exercise and cold. What is...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Paramyotonia congenita"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024685,
      "question_number": "301",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 55-year-old male has a history of lower limb weakness for days, initially starting with numbness a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Acute Intermittent Porphyria (AIP)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8210116731517509,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5718107746564515,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024686,
      "question_number": "70",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with an acetabular fracture presents post-admission with inability to dorsiflex his right ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Common peroneal nerve",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7584905660377359,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7537651298161323,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024687,
      "question_number": "542",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of Acute Inflammatory Demyelinating Polyneuropathy (AIDP) on day 5, what will the nerv...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024688,
      "question_number": "151",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the most sensitive test to diagnose myasthenia gravis (MG)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Single fiber EMG"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024689,
      "question_number": "10",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with ALS presents with fatigue. What is the next best step in management?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Pulmonary function test"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024690,
      "question_number": "519",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A case of Bell\u2019s palsy underwent EMG. Which muscle is likely to show findings?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Stylohyoid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7004608294930875,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6772179155900087,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024691,
      "question_number": "64",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which of the following electrodiagnostic tests is most helpful in the diagnosis of periodic paralysi...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Long exercise testing",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5976331360946746,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7844189489267209,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024692,
      "question_number": "245",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Anti-MuSK Myasthenia gravis is characterized by which of the following features?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Tongue fasciculation and atrophy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024693,
      "question_number": "550",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient has muscle stiffness that worsens with exercise. What is the likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Paramyotonia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6394052044609665,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.575648042961892,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024694,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Most common presentation of post-polio syndrome:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024695,
      "question_number": "98",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with back pain radiating to the left lower limb and normal ankle reflexes is evaluated. Wh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Superior gluteus"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024696,
      "question_number": "73",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the nerve supply to the sartorius muscle?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Femoral nerve",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5454545454545454,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4609290601368383,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024697,
      "question_number": "426",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 38-year-old male presents with a history of generalized weakness, a \u201cspring\u201d face, and respiratory...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Acetazolamide"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024698,
      "question_number": "46",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with a picture of Myasthenia Gravis (eye, proximal weakness, and bulbar symptoms) and a fl...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Anti-MuSK"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024699,
      "question_number": "470",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "How to differentiate between C8 and ulnar neuropathy?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024700,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Most common presentation of post-polio syndrome:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024701,
      "question_number": "431",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A poorly controlled type 1 diabetic male with an HbA1c of 14% became controlled one week ago and sta...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Gabapentin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024702,
      "question_number": "548",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the characteristic clinical presentation of Multifocal Motor Neuropathy (MMN)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024703,
      "question_number": "114",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario with congenital myasthenia gravis, where the patient has hand involvement and proximal...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Slow channel myasthenia gravis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6435845213849287,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5118516574827254,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024704,
      "question_number": "127",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q127. A patient presented with back pain, facial sweating, and intermittent epigastric pain associat...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Acute intermittent porphyria"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024705,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q41. A 70-year-old male patient came with progressive spastic lower limb weakness that progressed ov...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis (ALS)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024706,
      "question_number": "342",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q342. In a scenario about a patient with static weakness sparing the brachioradialis, what would you...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Spinal Segment Atrophy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024707,
      "question_number": "52",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a case of limb girdle muscular dystrophy type 2A, what is the recommended diagnostic test?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Pulmonary function test",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6816479400749064,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6007671232876712,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024708,
      "question_number": "78",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis (ALS), what is a characteristic finding on EMG?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Fibrillation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.674074074074074,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6896682106059174,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024709,
      "question_number": "130",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "An infant with hypotonia, macroglossia, feeding problems, trouble breathing, muscle weakness, and an...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Acid fast Maltase (Acid alpha-glucosidase)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.695,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7104,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024710,
      "question_number": "186",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the most common cause of femoral neuropathy?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Diabetes mellitus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5862068965517241,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.47538513060951104,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024711,
      "question_number": "261",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Kearns-Sayre syndrome",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024712,
      "question_number": "47",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q47. A case with features of POEMS presents with lower limb edema and neuropathy. What is the likely...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. VEGF",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8345323741007195,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6731654481451395,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024713,
      "question_number": "544",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q544. In a scenario of AIDP, what are the early findings in nerve conduction studies (NCS)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024714,
      "question_number": "247",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In the management of acute attacks of hypokalemic periodic paralysis, potassium is typically given o...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. 5\u201310 mEq every 15\u201330 minutes",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6380697050938338,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.019326005556226596,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024715,
      "question_number": "270",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "EMG",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024716,
      "question_number": "250",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is one of the diagnostic criteria for Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Exclude other causes"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024717,
      "question_number": "31",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A diabetic patient presents with features of small fiber neuropathy (pain worse at night, intact ref...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Pregabalin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024718,
      "question_number": "193",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Distal acquired demyelinating symmetric neuropathy (DADS) is characterized by which of the following...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Presence of anti-MAG antibodies",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5975609756097561,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5828406633020908,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024719,
      "question_number": "376",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "An anti-MuSK patient who developed hepatotoxicity with azathioprine, what medication should be given...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Rituximab"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024720,
      "question_number": "138",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Vitamin B6 deficiency can lead to which type of peripheral neuropathy?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Sensory neuropathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6133333333333333,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7306160693370812,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024721,
      "question_number": "126",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with left wrist drop and has a history of right wrist drop that improved, as well...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. PMP22 deletion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8576709796672828,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6947539461467038,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024722,
      "question_number": "444",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient has a fracture in the acetabulum and notices numbness on the dorsum of the foot with weak ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Lateral aspect of the sciatic nerve (Peroneal division)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024723,
      "question_number": "432",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is commonly associated with anti-MuSK antibodies?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024724,
      "question_number": "76",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In congenital myasthenic syndromes, what is the gene defect that causes worsening of symptoms with a...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Slow channel (CHRNE)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8113207547169812,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7940052894504849,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024725,
      "question_number": "474",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 40-year-old male patient presents with left arm weakness, thenar and hypothenar atrophy, fascicula...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Limb onset amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6995708154506438,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.73491145645103,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024726,
      "question_number": "63",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with channelopathy. What is the best workup?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Long exercise test"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024727,
      "question_number": "61",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q61. What is the effect of oral potassium in the management of Hypokalemic Periodic Paralysis?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Relieves attack"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024728,
      "question_number": "536",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient who underwent bariatric surgery developed progressive weakness and a large\u2010fiber periphera...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Copper"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024729,
      "question_number": "58",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient develops myotonia after repetitive exercise and subsequently experiences weakness. There i...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Paramyotonia congenita",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.745920745920746,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7016008935219658,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024730,
      "question_number": "47",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is a common presenting feature of Multifocal Motor Neuropathy (MMN)?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Wrist drop"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024731,
      "question_number": "455",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with dysferlinopathy presents with a CK level elevated 35 times the normal and mild upper ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Miyoshi Myopathy (LGMD2B)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024732,
      "question_number": "98",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young man who had abdominal pain around 1 week back and had a flu vaccine recently presented with ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Acute Inflammatory Demyelinating Polyneuropathy (AIDP)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024733,
      "question_number": "480",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A male patient with diabetes who is on metformin and has multiple comorbidities developed anemia wit...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Metformin related (metformin caused B12 deficiency)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024734,
      "question_number": "131",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with symptoms suggestive of chronic inflammatory demyelinating polyneuropathy (CIDP) was n...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Rituximab"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024735,
      "question_number": "110",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of AIDP, what are the early findings in NCS?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024736,
      "question_number": "189",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young lady post-vaginal hysterectomy presents with weakness in hip adductors and hip flexion. Whic...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Obturator nerve"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024737,
      "question_number": "530",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q530. In a scenario typical for paramyotonia congenita, what is the gene involved?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Sodium channel (SCN4A)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024738,
      "question_number": "369",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome scenario, what is the predicting factor for intubation?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Presence of dysautonomia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5412541254125413,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2149906015037594,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024739,
      "question_number": "141",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 40-year-old female has proximal muscle weakness and progressive dysphagia. On examination, she has...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. IV methylprednisolone"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024740,
      "question_number": "539",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q539. A young patient came with weakness and is unable to extend his elbow and has toe walking; ECG ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Emery-Dreifuss muscular dystrophy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024741,
      "question_number": "57",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which factor is known to trigger an attack in Paramyotonia Congenita?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Cold exposure"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024742,
      "question_number": "534",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient came with channelopathy. What is the best workup?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Long exercise test"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024743,
      "question_number": "68",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with Sj\u00f6gren's disease presents with neurological symptoms. Which of the following is a po...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Present with polyneuropathy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024744,
      "question_number": "420",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "An infant presents with respiratory issues, electrical myotonia, and macroglossia. What is the likel...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pompe",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7397260273972602,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7609174311926605,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024745,
      "question_number": "518",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A female patient presents with right Bell\u2019s palsy. You performed the blink reflex test, and the EMG ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Stylohyoid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8148148148148148,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.774869109947644,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024746,
      "question_number": "47",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 52-year-old female with dyslipidemia on a statin was admitted with pneumonia. After starting eryth...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Concomitant use of erythromycin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024747,
      "question_number": "454",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A clear scenario about MMN presents with severe weakness and no atrophy, asking about the diagnosis,...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Multifocal motor neuropathy without conduction block",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6447638603696099,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7886285238491733,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024748,
      "question_number": "199",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the most common myopathy in elderly individuals above 50 years of age?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Inclusion body myositis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6363636363636364,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.28992097001190864,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024749,
      "question_number": "28",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the most common myopathy disease in patients above 50 years of age?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Inclusion Body Myositis (IBM)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024750,
      "question_number": "483",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A typical scenario of a patient presents with decreased sensation and bilateral weakness in the lowe...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Acute inflammatory demyelinating polyneuropathy (AIDP)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024751,
      "question_number": "443",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A lady with a history of treated breast cancer presents with one week of numbness in the 4th and 5th...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. NCS/EMG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8361344537815126,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5610978716410552,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024752,
      "question_number": "471",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient wakes up from sleep with right upper limb pain followed by weakness and multiple nerve inv...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Parsonage-Turner syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6765432098765433,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.38482501434308664,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024753,
      "question_number": "201",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with subacute flaccid quadriplegia following diarrheal illnesses, with sparing of...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. AMAN (Acute Motor Axonal Neuropathy)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8253968253968254,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5802144066202746,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024754,
      "question_number": "187",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Scenario of recurrent painless multifocal mononeuropathies at common compression sites. PMP-22 delet...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Demyelination (Tomacula / sausage-like thickenings)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024755,
      "question_number": "50",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q50. A typical case of Hirayama disease presents with right upper limb weakness, preserved brachiora...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Focal cervical cord atrophy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024756,
      "question_number": "79",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q79. Which of the following is a function of the femoral nerve?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024757,
      "question_number": "526",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q526. What is the first-line treatment for Acute Inflammatory Demyelinating Polyneuropathy (AIDP)?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. IV Immunoglobulin (IVIG)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024758,
      "question_number": "244",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with weakness that is induced by cold exposure. Which channel is likely affected?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Sodium channel",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7050359712230215,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5084469774068797,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024759,
      "question_number": "562",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young man played football for one day, developed generalized weakness mainly in the proximal limbs...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. CPT II deficiency"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024760,
      "question_number": "78",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 16-year-old presented with calf hypertrophy. Which of the following conditions is most likely?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. LGMD2A (Calpainopathy)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024761,
      "question_number": "445",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the recommended treatment for Inclusion Body Myositis (IBM)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Supportive care",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5284552845528455,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5708936595107339,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024762,
      "question_number": "231",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a case of dysautonomia with carpal tunnel syndrome (CTS), what is the most appropriate diagnostic...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Abdominal fat aspiration"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024763,
      "question_number": "56",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In congenital Myotonic dystrophy type 1 (DM1), which of the following symptoms is typically absent o...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Myotonia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7338129496402878,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6713826366559486,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024764,
      "question_number": "504",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a case of a patient with colchicine toxicity\u2013induced myopathy, who presents with high CK levels a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Colchicine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9085271317829458,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.503278485710751,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024765,
      "question_number": "48",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young man came to the ER who went to sleep at 10 PM and woke up at midnight with weakness in his w...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Short exercise test",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8291139240506329,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7750303256508351,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024766,
      "question_number": "482",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q482. A young patient presents with proximal painful weakness, and a biopsy result shows CD+8 lympho...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Polymyositis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024767,
      "question_number": "14",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which of the following muscles is innervated by the ulnar nerve?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Adductor pollicis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5316455696202531,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6878317893202873,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024768,
      "question_number": "382",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with moderate muscle weakness, hyperkeratosis on the hands, and lung crackles. Wh...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Anti-synthase antibody"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024769,
      "question_number": "546",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 55-year-old patient presented with ptosis, extraocular muscle weakness, dysphagia, and proximal we...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. GCG Repeat"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024770,
      "question_number": "77",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young woman who was recently diagnosed with diabetes mellitus (DM) was not controlled at all after...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Gabapentin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024771,
      "question_number": "136",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q136. A 40-year-old previously healthy male developed gastrointestinal symptoms, then had generalize...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Botulism",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.795131845841785,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7462393078360043,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024772,
      "question_number": "61",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with peripheral neuropathy and transient central nervous system (CNS) symptoms. W...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Charcot-Marie-Tooth disease type X (CMTX)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6237623762376238,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4250737084989104,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024773,
      "question_number": "81",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q81. In Paramyotonia Congenita, the effect of cold exposure is:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Induces attack"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024774,
      "question_number": "65",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of Charcot-Marie-Tooth disease type 2 (CMT2), what would you find?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024775,
      "question_number": "50",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In Hyperkalemic Periodic Paralysis, the duration of paralysis is typically:",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Minutes to hours"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024776,
      "question_number": "167",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 31-year-old male has hand grip myotonia, facial weakness, significant atrophy of facial muscles, p...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Diabetes mellitus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8074245939675174,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6236263736263736,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024777,
      "question_number": "53",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a case of Spinal Muscular Atrophy (SMA), which of the following is a supportive finding?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Neurogenic finding on EMG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5838926174496645,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7856744393618208,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024778,
      "question_number": "6",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In hypokalemic periodic paralysis, which of the following is true regarding the incidence of paralys...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Predominantly male",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6158536585365854,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.773573277455935,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024779,
      "question_number": "62",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "If single-fiber EMG is normal in clinically affected muscles, what can be concluded?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. The diagnosis of MG is excluded."
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024780,
      "question_number": "49",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Spinobulbar muscular atrophy (Kennedy's Disease) is primarily caused by which genetic mutation?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. CAG expansion in the androgen-receptor (AR) gene"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024781,
      "question_number": "76",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In Parsonage-Turner syndrome, which plexus is affected?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024782,
      "question_number": "104",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario about dermatomyositis, which antibody is associated with the condition?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Anti-Mi2",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7345132743362832,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4646860376537164,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024783,
      "question_number": "16",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q16. A case scenario about central core myopathy mentions a family history of malignant hyperthermia...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Central core myopathy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024784,
      "question_number": "153",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 55-year-old patient presented with progressive numbness and burning sensation in the lower limbs, ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Amyloidosis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024785,
      "question_number": "148",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the most common myopathy in patients older than 50 years?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Inclusion Body Myositis (IBM)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5289256198347108,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.738704362154193,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024786,
      "question_number": "17",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of POEMS syndrome, what will you find in the serum?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. VEGF"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024787,
      "question_number": "484",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A female patient complains of hand numbness that wakes her from sleep and improves with shaking her ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Carpal tunnel syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024788,
      "question_number": "553",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with flaccid weakness. What is a possible cause?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024789,
      "question_number": "99",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient post hip replacement surgery presents with right lower limb weakness. Examination showed h...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Peroneal nerve"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024790,
      "question_number": "86",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with typical features of myasthenia gravis has negative ACHR antibody and Anti-MUSK tests....",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. LRP4 antibody"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024791,
      "question_number": "121",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q121. A 55-year-old patient is complaining of generalized weakness, weight gain, and tingling in her...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Thyroid test"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024792,
      "question_number": "59",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a patient with median nerve conduction studies (NCS) at the elbow and wrist, what is the likely f...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Conduction block"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024793,
      "question_number": "94",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with Limb-Girdle Muscular Dystrophy (LGMD) and a positive family history is likely to have...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. Calpainopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7764705882352941,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7148231753197893,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024794,
      "question_number": "122",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a case of acute inflammatory demyelinating polyneuropathy (AIDP) with prior diarrhea 4 weeks ago,...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Acute motor axonal neuropathy (AMAN)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024795,
      "question_number": "85",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A male patient presented with symptoms suggestive of proximal muscle weakness. He has two cousins wi...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Inherited myopathy.",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8369565217391305,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4945098039215686,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024796,
      "question_number": "109",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q109. A 50-year-old male patient is complaining of chronic progressive bilateral ptosis associated w...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Oculopharyngeal muscular dystrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.840937114673243,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7229557069846678,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024797,
      "question_number": "108",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A male patient presented to the outpatient clinic for evaluation of limb weakness. He has upper limb...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Hirayama disease"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024798,
      "question_number": "424",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient on statin therapy develops necrotizing myositis. What is the most likely cause?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Erythromycin interaction"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024799,
      "question_number": "109",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A case of Facioscapulohumeral muscular dystrophy is presented. What is the likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Facioscapulohumeral Muscular Dystrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5844155844155844,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7337418823744626,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024800,
      "question_number": "253",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is a potential early complication of Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "C. Cardiac arrhythmias",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6280193236714976,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7120365667851701,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024801,
      "question_number": "251",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is a treatment option for Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Plasma exchange",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6127659574468085,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7655284552845528,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024802,
      "question_number": "537",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with multifocal mononeuropathy multiplex. A sural nerve biopsy reveals vessel wal...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Vasculitic neuropathy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024803,
      "question_number": "525",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young female presented with dilated pupils, dysphagia, and descending weakness; what is the diagno...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Presynaptic NMJ disorder",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6622516556291391,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.25590361445783133,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024804,
      "question_number": "123",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q123. In a case of Dermatomyositis, which of the following findings is typically observed?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Perifascicular atrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6327272727272727,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7176864750484924,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024805,
      "question_number": "57",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q57. Which muscle is tested in L5 EMG testing?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024806,
      "question_number": "77",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Paramyotonia is associated with which type of channel?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Sodium Channel (SCN4A)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5463917525773195,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.698930106989301,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024807,
      "question_number": "138",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A child presented with proximal muscle weakness and was diagnosed with laminopathy (or LMNA mutation...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Elbow and ankle contractures"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024808,
      "question_number": "20",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with weak facial muscles (cannot blow air) and weakness in the arm flexors and ex...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Facioscapulohumeral muscular dystrophy (FSHD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.746615087040619,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.75617847072483,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024809,
      "question_number": "75",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q75. A nerve conduction study (NCS) shows a drop in amplitude. Which of the following could explain ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Conduction block",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7322033898305085,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7423632488752072,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024810,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In paramyotonia congenita, what clinical feature is observed in cold conditions?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Stiffness of the tongue, eyelids, face, and limb muscles"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024811,
      "question_number": "90",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient is admitted with proximal myopathy and high CK levels (around 6000). A biopsy shows necrot...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Age older than 50",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8247422680412371,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6722285952654082,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024812,
      "question_number": "23",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a case of inclusion body myositis (IBM), what are the histology findings?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Rimmed vacuoles"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024813,
      "question_number": "461",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q461. In LGMD1B, what physical findings are typically observed?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Elbow and ankle contractures"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024814,
      "question_number": "77",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "The chromosome associated with the genetic basis of Hyperkalemic Periodic Paralysis is:",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. 12q24"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024815,
      "question_number": "501",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q501. A patient presents with gradual proximal weakness, has a history of being on a statin and 5 mg...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Statin myopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8649425287356322,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6627423822714681,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024816,
      "question_number": "345",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with urinary incontinence and symptoms suggesting autonomic dysfunction along wit...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Abdominal fat pad biopsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.84375,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6750044988303041,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024817,
      "question_number": "25",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Case of a lady post-hysterectomy presented with weakness in hip flexion and knee extension. What is ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Femoral nerve",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.75,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5457275457275458,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024818,
      "question_number": "528",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "The same patient is asking about the antibody associated with his condition. What is the antibody?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-GM1"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024819,
      "question_number": "383",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 20-year-old presents with respiratory symptoms, an aneurysm, PAS on pathology, negative forearm ex...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pompe",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8198198198198198,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7325222755311858,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024820,
      "question_number": "299",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with progressive hand muscle weakness and severe atrophy, with plantars upgoing i...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis (ALS)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024821,
      "question_number": "527",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the most common presentation of post-polio syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Asymptomatic",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5462962962962963,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7936410883521858,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024822,
      "question_number": "246",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with a history of HCV presents with peripheral neuropathy. Which of the following is the m...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Cryoglobulinemia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7603833865814696,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7602677464672342,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024823,
      "question_number": "38",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is NOT a characteristic feature of Myotonic dystrophy?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Proximal muscle weakness"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024824,
      "question_number": "381",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario typical for GBS, the patient presents with bone pain and recent vaccination. What woul...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Prolonged latency, normal CMAP, absent SNAPs",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6876155268022182,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.573143886331799,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024825,
      "question_number": "234",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 57-year-old male is referred to neurology consultation from the gastro team. He has a complaint of...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. IBM"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024826,
      "question_number": "232",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient experiences leg cramps at the beginning of exercise that improve with rest. What test is m...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Ischemic forearm test"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024827,
      "question_number": "559",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 16-year-old patient has difficulty climbing stairs, a positive Gower sign, and scapular winging. W...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Becker muscular dystrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7206703910614525,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7663288853215612,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024828,
      "question_number": "154",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with a history of back of throat pain and tongue pain experiences episodic syncope. What i...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Refer to ENT for laryngoscope",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6460674157303371,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5640130353817505,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024829,
      "question_number": "255",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which variant of Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome is characterized by bilateral facial weakness and paraesthe...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Classic sensorimotor"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024830,
      "question_number": "179",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario with amyloidosis, what is the next step in management?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Fat aspiration",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5569620253164557,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5572656406156307,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024831,
      "question_number": "300",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient has myotonia symptoms since age 10 for 5 years. The father had myotonia, and there is no m...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Thomson"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024832,
      "question_number": "94",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young man who had abdominal pain around 1 week back and had a flu vaccine 2 weeks ago presented wi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. IV IG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9004329004329005,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7948550250708524,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024833,
      "question_number": "71",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In the same previous scenario, with a lesion distal to a nerve root, what is most useful in localiza...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024834,
      "question_number": "158",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient who recently underwent right femoral replacement surgery has weakness in hip adductors and...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Obturator nerve",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7819148936170213,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7800204394481349,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024835,
      "question_number": "201",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the most common deficit that occurs post elbow joint trauma?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Wrist drop",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5903083700440529,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.30645900137425564,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024836,
      "question_number": "469",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with episodic weakness that worsens while eating tomatoes and bananas. What ion c...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Na channel"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024837,
      "question_number": "81",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a dysferlinopathy scenario, which condition is indicated by gastrocnemius muscle atrophy?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Dysferlinopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5901639344262295,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.723156285823462,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024838,
      "question_number": "250",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is NOT included in the Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome (GBS) spectrum?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Myasthenia gravis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5774647887323944,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7448615384615385,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024839,
      "question_number": "258",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q258. A case of hypokalemic periodic paralysis is presented. What is the most helpful diagnostic tes...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Long exercise test"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024840,
      "question_number": "59",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In Hyperkalemic Periodic Paralysis, the degree of paralysis is usually described as:",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Occasionally severe",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7130434782608696,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7203548085901027,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024841,
      "question_number": "78",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the most common subtype of acetylcholine receptor (AchR) antibody?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Binding"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024842,
      "question_number": "465",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with hypertension and bulbar weakness presents with generalized weakness. What is the like...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. P/Q calcium channel"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024843,
      "question_number": "558",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A Filipino man who did intense exercise then developed generalized weakness with an intact level of ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Serum potassium level",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7530562347188264,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.48361902829901615,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024844,
      "question_number": "516",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with proximal weakness and there is no history of statin use. A pathology slide i...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Duchenne muscular dystrophy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024845,
      "question_number": "162",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with upper limb numbness and pinprick sensation around the shoulder. The preserve...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Syringomyelia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8467966573816156,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7329387186629527,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024846,
      "question_number": "159",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In Hereditary Neuropathy with Liability to Pressure Palsies (HNPP), which nerve is most commonly aff...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Fibular nerve",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.75,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.784970804772785,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024847,
      "question_number": "198",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "An 18-year-old patient presented with progressive limb weakness. On examination, he has normal facia...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Calpain-3 related."
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024848,
      "question_number": "427",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q427. A scenario is suggestive of amyloidosis with autonomic symptoms, lower limb pain, and carpal t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Fat pad biopsy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024849,
      "question_number": "69",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q69. In an elderly female presenting with chronic demyelinating polyneuropathy and an associated mon...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Monthly IVIg",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.815668202764977,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3707865168539326,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024850,
      "question_number": "57",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the typical age demographic affected by Multifocal Motor Neuropathy (MMN)?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Young adults, with 2/3 being 45 years or less",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.535593220338983,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7414480841290947,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024851,
      "question_number": "545",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a patient with AIDP, what cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) finding is expected?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Elevated protein with normal cell count",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.505338078291815,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5634977707464404,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024852,
      "question_number": "54",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young patient with distal myopathy (posterior calf) has a high CK level of 7000. Which of the foll...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Miyoshi myopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7214854111405835,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4879861283131038,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024853,
      "question_number": "56",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with weakness in hand flexors and quadriceps femoris. What is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Inclusion Body Myositis (IBM)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024854,
      "question_number": "58",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old woman with breast cancer is treated with radiation therapy to the left axilla for lymp...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. EMG myokymia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024855,
      "question_number": "57",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which diagnostic study is used to identify focal motor conduction block in MMN?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Nerve conduction studies (NCS)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024856,
      "question_number": "202",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario involving a female patient with ocular myasthenia gravis, what is the best sensitive t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Single fiber EMG"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024857,
      "question_number": "78",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with hypokalemic periodic paralysis has a potassium level of 2.6. After administering pota...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Acetazolamide",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7473118279569892,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5868615910385419,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024858,
      "question_number": "200",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presented to the outpatient clinic with complaints of wrist drop. Examination showed weakn...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Posterior interosseous nerve",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7880910683012259,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5299299299299299,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024859,
      "question_number": "163",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 40-year-old male with proximal upper and lower limb weakness associated with tremors and tongue at...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Typical scenario of Kennedy disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7797979797979798,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.49686609686609684,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024860,
      "question_number": "422",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A Filipino male patient presents with a history of generalized weakness upon waking. What laboratory...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Potassium level",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7197640117994101,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6701052631578948,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024861,
      "question_number": "26",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of a patient with findings suggestive of dermatomyositis (hints: dermal lesions, ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Perifascicular atrophy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024862,
      "question_number": "538",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the treatment for Inclusion Body Myositis (IBM)?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Supportive treatment",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6057142857142858,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4954867379530621,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024863,
      "question_number": "117",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 16-year-old patient has difficulty climbing stairs, a positive Gower sign, and on examination has ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Calpainopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8027923211169284,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7380513709764821,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024864,
      "question_number": "555",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with proximal upper and lower limb weakness and dysmorphic features underwent a muscle bio...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. RYR1-related myopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7458432304038005,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3978046549446082,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024865,
      "question_number": "385",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A case of a patient with cramps and stiffness that relieve with movements is noted, with a similar h...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thomson syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7593052109181141,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.717704362558238,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024866,
      "question_number": "111",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with proximal upper and lower limb weakness and dysmorphic features underwent a muscle bio...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. RYR1-related myopathy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024867,
      "question_number": "555",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is the most common cause of ischemic stroke?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Large artery atherosclerosis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024868,
      "question_number": "429",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with hypokalemic periodic paralysis has a potassium level of 2.3 mEq/L. What is the first-...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Acetazolamide",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6827794561933535,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5218937125748503,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024869,
      "question_number": "462",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a long face and central core on pathology. What condition might this suggest...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Central Core Disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.66,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7702453690233731,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024870,
      "question_number": "183",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 35-year-old male has progressive asymmetric weakness starting in the right leg that ascends to bot...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis (ALS)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024871,
      "question_number": "464",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with upper limb and lower limb weakness and numbness with bilateral lower limb ed...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. POEMS syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024872,
      "question_number": "543",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is a hallmark finding in the cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) of patients with CIDP?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Elevated protein with normal cell count",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5231788079470199,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.537421777221527,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024873,
      "question_number": "419",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In the context of neuromyopathies, which medication is commonly associated with treatment?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Chloroquine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7302904564315352,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6098076923076923,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024874,
      "question_number": "532",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a patient with AIDP, what is the expected nerve conduction study (NCS) finding at day 5?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024875,
      "question_number": "481",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with high CK levels and myositis is currently on statin therapy. What is the recommended m...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Stop statin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024876,
      "question_number": "387",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q387. SMA",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024877,
      "question_number": "298",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with back pain and L5 radiculopathy. Which muscle is involved?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Gluteus medius",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6370967741935484,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7774944214217405,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024878,
      "question_number": "552",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 15-year-old male has myotonia and weakness that improves after exercise; his father has the same c...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thomsen disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7435158501440923,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6508923524186384,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024879,
      "question_number": "560",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young man presents with myotonia that improves after exercise. His father had the same diagnosis. ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thomsen's disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7257617728531855,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.41458644886690443,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024880,
      "question_number": "206",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a patient diagnosed with Chronic Inflammatory Demyelinating Polyneuropathy (CIDP), what is the ch...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Symmetrical sensorimotor polyneuropathy with proximal and distal motor involvement",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5622317596566524,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3961895456765999,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024881,
      "question_number": "61",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 15-year-old male has myotonia and weakness that improves after exercise; his father has the same c...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thomsen disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7435158501440923,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.565290743448431,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024882,
      "question_number": "137",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis (ALS), which of the following findings is typically ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Normal SNAPs",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7872860635696821,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3443722713236077,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024883,
      "question_number": "552",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which of the following cranial nerves is primarily responsible for controlling the muscles of facial...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Facial nerve (Cranial Nerve VII)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7938997821350763,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024884,
      "question_number": "242",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q242. What is the treatment of choice for acute attacks of hypokalemic periodic paralysis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Potassium",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7068273092369478,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5429855013273432,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024885,
      "question_number": "46",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q46. A case scenario of findings suggestive of multifocal motor neuropathy (MMN) is presented. What ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. MMN",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8648648648648649,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4876294277929155,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024886,
      "question_number": "219",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with hypokalemic periodic paralysis has a potassium level of 2.6. After you give potassium...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Acetazolamide"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024887,
      "question_number": "224",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the first-line treatment for Chronic Inflammatory Demyelinating Polyneuropathy (CIDP)?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. IVIG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7368421052631579,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.38641434592182466,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024888,
      "question_number": "343",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario about botulism with an increment on high-frequency repetitive nerve stimulation (RNS),...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Prevent acetylcholine release from presynaptic vesicles"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024889,
      "question_number": "303",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 20-year-old male has a history of limb weakness. Examination reveals significant weakness of the p...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Calpain 2A"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024890,
      "question_number": "523",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 55-year-old patient came with lower limb paresthesia and heaviness that is getting worse, reaching...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. AIDP",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8156424581005587,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6550047066206464,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024891,
      "question_number": "63",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q63. A decrement greater than 10% in CMAP during a Two-hertz to 5-Hz RNS study is indicative of what...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Neuromuscular transmission defect",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6067415730337079,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6972210097482904,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024892,
      "question_number": "78",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is the most common cause of acute ischemic stroke?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. Large artery atherosclerosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.582995951417004,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6975572351845766,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024893,
      "question_number": "149",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 22-year-old Filipino male presented with generalized weakness after heavy exercise. On examination...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. K level"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024894,
      "question_number": "80",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a patient with a stab wound resulting in ulnar neuropathy, what would you expect to find in nerve...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Fibrillations"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024895,
      "question_number": "473",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with dysphagia, tongue fasciculation, and an exaggerated jaw reflex for 18 month...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Progressive bulbar palsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7801418439716312,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7612287041817243,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024896,
      "question_number": "467",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient taking a multivitamin is experiencing sensory neuronopathy. Which vitamin is most likely i...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Vitamin B6"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024897,
      "question_number": "27",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A Filipino male had sudden generalized weakness after vigorous exercise. What laboratory test should...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. K levels",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7142857142857143,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5956013890350416,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024898,
      "question_number": "557",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A case presents with weakness in distal hand and forearm muscles that progressed over 18 months and ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Hirayama disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7368421052631579,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6080655785698602,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024899,
      "question_number": "45",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A case scenario of a patient with myopathy and malignant hyperthermia is presented. What is the like...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Central core myopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6666666666666666,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7882824918628416,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024900,
      "question_number": "11",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient with uncontrolled diabetes presents with foot drop, thigh pain, and weight loss. ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Tight glycemic control and foot care"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024901,
      "question_number": "551",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with scapular winging and weakness. He has very high CK levels, and a muscle biop...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Calpainopathy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024902,
      "question_number": "177",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient who had a mastectomy presents with arm pain and dysesthesia over the fourth and fifth fing...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Nerve conduction studies",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.75,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6118118787068749,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024903,
      "question_number": "160",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q160. What histological finding is associated with a sural nerve biopsy in HNPP?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024904,
      "question_number": "466",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with myasthenia gravis (MG) presents. What is the most sensitive test for diagnosing this ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Single fiber EMG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6523076923076923,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7669068495529126,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024905,
      "question_number": "164",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient presents with a progressive, symmetric sensorimotor peripheral neuropathy. On exa...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. POEMS syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.901060070671378,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.701028741117828,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024906,
      "question_number": "374",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In an anti-MuSK case, which statement is true?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024907,
      "question_number": "549",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 35-year-old patient presented with posterior thigh weakness and calf weakness and is unable to per...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Dysferlinopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7745901639344263,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5893151815181518,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024908,
      "question_number": "14",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with weakness provoked by exercise but then improves shortly after. What is the l...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Myophosphorylase deficiency",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6686217008797654,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6253923962329961,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024909,
      "question_number": "65",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 20-year-old patient presents with a 10-year history of lower limb proximal weakness and difficulty...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Limb-girdle muscular dystrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8183254344391785,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6291520792417385,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024910,
      "question_number": "12",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with Anti-Musk antibodies is likely to present with which of the following symptoms?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Tongue weakness and atrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7181467181467182,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6920306168392616,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024911,
      "question_number": "116",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario with stiffness and difficulty walking with an episode of loss of consciousness, where ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Morvan syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024912,
      "question_number": "524",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young male patient came with eyelid myotonia that increased after eating ice cream or being expose...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Paramyotonia congenita"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024913,
      "question_number": "74",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A man who developed progressive weakness of the right hand showed severe weakness and muscle atrophy...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Riluzole"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024914,
      "question_number": "430",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario suggesting periodic paralysis in a Filipino patient with generalized muscle weakness, ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Potassium level",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7512953367875648,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6286672254819782,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024915,
      "question_number": "133",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What should be regularly assessed in a patient with Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Muscle strength",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6329113924050633,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7118739448508723,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024916,
      "question_number": "292",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 26-year-old male presented with proximal weakness and bilateral scapular winging, painless, with n...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. LGMD2A (Calpainopathy)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8866396761133604,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.771748205042578,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024917,
      "question_number": "256",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 50-year-old male presents with a history of progressive lower limb weakness with tingling and numb...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Chronic Inflammatory Demyelinating Polyneuropathy (CIDP)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024918,
      "question_number": "384",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 23-year-old male presents with respiratory failure and a cerebral aneurysm. Electromyography (EMG)...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Myotonic dystrophy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024919,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In paramyotonia congenita, what happens to the amplitude of the compound muscle action potential (CM...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Decreases"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024920,
      "question_number": "423",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A scenario is suggestive of Mononeuritis multiplex with pathology showing monoclonal cells and necro...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Vasculitic neuropathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6968973747016707,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6356168884507968,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024921,
      "question_number": "535",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the first abnormality typically seen in nerve conduction studies (NCS) or electromyography (...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Prolonged or absent F wave and absent H reflexes",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5934065934065934,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7344992050874404,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024922,
      "question_number": "475",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with multifocal motor neuropathy (MMN) is being considered for treatment. What is the firs...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. IVIG"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024923,
      "question_number": "547",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of facioscapulohumeral muscular dystrophy (FSH), what is the likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Facioscapulohumeral muscular dystrophy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024924,
      "question_number": "425",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with ocular muscle weakness, ptosis, mild facial weakness, and proximal weakness....",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Oculopharyngeal muscular dystrophy (OPMD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6127450980392157,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.764203852718849,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024925,
      "question_number": "48",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the most sensitive test for diagnosing Myasthenia Gravis (MG)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Single fiber EMG (SFEMG)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024926,
      "question_number": "66",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with progressive inability to drink with a straw, proximal weakness, scapular wi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Facioscapulohumeral dystrophy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024927,
      "question_number": "418",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with symmetrical proximal and distal weakness, numbness in toes and fingers, fasc...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Chronic Inflammatory Demyelinating Polyneuropathy (CIDP)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024928,
      "question_number": "472",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Anti-striatal antibody in Myasthenia Gravis (MG) indicates:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thymoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5863874345549738,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6574585635359116,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024929,
      "question_number": "113",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario involving amyloidosis, what is the next step in management?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Fat aspiration"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024930,
      "question_number": "132",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A Filipino patient has muscle stiffness and intermittent weakness. What should be tested for him?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Potassium level",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6909090909090909,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2650654549388727,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024931,
      "question_number": "112",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q112. What is the medication that causes neuropathy and myopathy?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Chloroquine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024932,
      "question_number": "188",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a patient with sensory and autonomic neuropathy, a family history of restrictive cardiomyopathy i...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Amyloidosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8035714285714286,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6402248093135287,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024933,
      "question_number": "67",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of LGM1B (laminopathy) with elevated heart enzyme levels, what is the expected finding...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Late contracture in LGMD1B (AD)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5495750708215298,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7331468279036188,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024934,
      "question_number": "51",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of a patient with findings suggestive of hereditary motor and sensory neuropathy ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Onion bulb"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024935,
      "question_number": "184",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q184. A patient has difficulty blowing air in the mouth and presents with an asymmetrical right foot...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. FSHD (Facioscapulohumeral Muscular Dystrophy)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7645429362880887,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6025042048215287,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024936,
      "question_number": "346",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "An adult presents with a history of gait issues. Examination shows significant weakness and atrophy ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Dysferlin 2B",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7766179540709812,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.69617827972169,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024937,
      "question_number": "66",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the typical recovery pattern following an episode of Hereditary Neuropathy with Liability to...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Complete recovery within days or weeks"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024938,
      "question_number": "54",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which cranial nerve is primarily responsible for the sense of smell?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Olfactory nerve (CN I)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5800865800865801,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7448293363786321,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024939,
      "question_number": "12",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with hand extension weakness but no sensory loss. Which nerve is likely affected?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Posterior Interosseous Nerve (PIN)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024940,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young patient presents with distal myopathy (posterior calf) and a high creatine kinase level of 7...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Miyoshi myopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7262569832402235,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.004051316677920324,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024941,
      "question_number": "241",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Dermatomyositis is associated with which of the following findings?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Perifascular inflammation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5665236051502146,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7984715888080858,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024942,
      "question_number": "29",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the most common gene associated with familial Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis (ALS)?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. C9orf72"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024943,
      "question_number": "239",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A case presents with stiffness induced by exercise, and the patient experiences forced eye closure w...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Sodium channel",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.826271186440678,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7661538461538462,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024944,
      "question_number": "72",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In the context of Inclusion Body Myositis (IBM), what is the primary treatment approach?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Supportive care",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.680161943319838,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.43876095373955576,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024945,
      "question_number": "113",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Acute Inflammatory Demyelinating Polyneuropathy (AIDP), what is the first abnormal...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. F wave abnormalities"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024946,
      "question_number": "93",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A middle-aged female has a history of diarrhea two weeks prior to presentation and now has paresthes...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Acute inflammatory demyelinating polyneuropathy (AIDP)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6492374727668845,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4725778712019874,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024947,
      "question_number": "40",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Case scenario of a patient with inner arm and forearm tingling sensation, thenar muscle weakness, an...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. C8-T1",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8830409356725146,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7910216718266254,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024948,
      "question_number": "556",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario with congenital myasthenia gravis (MG), the patient has hand involvement and proximal ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Slow-channel myasthenic syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024949,
      "question_number": "11",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In ulnar neuropathy, what will you find on day 5 in nerve conduction studies (NCS)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Decreased recruitment"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024950,
      "question_number": "48",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 35-year-old patient presented with posterior thigh weakness and calf weakness, and he cannot perfo...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Dysferlinopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7689161554192229,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6352047070360383,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024951,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 55-year-old patient presented with ptosis, extraocular muscle weakness, dysphagia, and proximal we...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. GCG Repeat"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024952,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with C5\u2013C6 radiculopathy is evaluated. Which muscle is involved?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Biceps brachii"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024953,
      "question_number": "49",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with shoulder pain and weakness in the forearm and arm is evaluated. What is the most comm...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Upper trunk"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024954,
      "question_number": "59",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "The same patient is asking about the treatment. What is the most effective treatment for this condit...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. IV immunoglobulin (IVIG)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6891891891891891,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4583883751651255,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024955,
      "question_number": "238",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q238. A patient presents 2 days postpartum with flaccid paralysis, decreased reflexes, and normal se...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Nerve Conduction Study (NCS)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024956,
      "question_number": "234",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q234. What is the characteristic presentation of monomelic amyotrophy?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024957,
      "question_number": "172",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q172. A 44-year-old female presents with a 3-week history of left leg numbness and right hand and ar...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Mononeuritis multiplex",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7915567282321899,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6466396030672079,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024958,
      "question_number": "52",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Type 2 Charcot-Marie-Tooth disease, what is the typical feature?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. SNAP drop",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5714285714285714,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6774988794262663,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024959,
      "question_number": "187",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 35-year-old female with a known case of Myasthenia Gravis for 5 years presents with worsening gene...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Referral to surgery for thymectomy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.837410071942446,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6528034839412085,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024960,
      "question_number": "236",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 2-month-old infant presents with apnea, macroglossia, and hypertrophic cardiomyopathy. What is the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Pompe Disease"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024961,
      "question_number": "144",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In anti-MuSK positive myasthenia gravis, which muscle group is most commonly affected?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Bulbar",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7850467289719626,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4279342068580987,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024962,
      "question_number": "233",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "An image of nerve conduction studies (NCS) of the median nerve shows:",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Prolonged latency"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024963,
      "question_number": "48",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A scenario typical for paramyotonia congenita is presented. What is the gene involved?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Sodium channel",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.672,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7961595273264401,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024964,
      "question_number": "468",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient is losing the clutch, has Lhermitte sign, and experiences ataxia that worsens at night. Th...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Subacute combined degeneration (B12 deficiency)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.731457800511509,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7862948605727148,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024965,
      "question_number": "230",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis (ALS), what is a key clinical finding?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024966,
      "question_number": "45",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q45. (Source: Part 2 2021mcqs.txt) What is the treatment for Inclusion Body Myositis (IBM)?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Supportive treatment",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7058823529411765,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7939560439560439,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024967,
      "question_number": "149",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young male presents with neck and shoulder pain, along with decreased sensation in the medial wris...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Ulnar nerve injury"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024968,
      "question_number": "8",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with myotonic dystrophy presents with shoulder pain. What is the most appropriate manageme...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Extensive physiotherapy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7612903225806451,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.49833960593314147,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024969,
      "question_number": "9",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with a neuropathy after a mild car accident and was found to have a PMP22 gene d...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Sausage shaped"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024970,
      "question_number": "129",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the typical recovery time for Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024971,
      "question_number": "44",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with mononeuritis multiplex. Nerve biopsy demonstrates transmural vessel wall nec...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Vasculitic neuropathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7639484978540773,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7821447625822515,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024972,
      "question_number": "52",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q52. A patient presents with scapular winging and weakness, and he has very high CK levels. Muscle b...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Calpainopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7317073170731707,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7482370407027094,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024973,
      "question_number": "5",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with a known case of diabetes mellitus presents with peripheral neuropathy and has impaire...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Epidermal nerve fiber density",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7484143763213531,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6486344996073641,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024974,
      "question_number": "28",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which of the following statements about Kennedy disease (Spinal and Bulbar Muscular Atrophy) is corr...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024975,
      "question_number": "19",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a patient with a familial history of amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS), which gene mutations ar...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. SOD1"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024976,
      "question_number": "57",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q57. In a typical scenario of a stiff person, EMG showed continuous contractions. What is the antibo...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-GAD"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024977,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "After radiation therapy, a patient presents with shoulder abduction weakness (4/5), impaired sensati...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Axillary and lateral antebrachial"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024978,
      "question_number": "32",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 22-year-old female patient presented with difficulty walking and climbing stairs; however, she has...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Neurogenic change in EMG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8292079207920792,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7743673626479362,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024979,
      "question_number": "45",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A middle-aged man presents to the outpatient clinic with a history of peripheral neuropathy. His pas...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Churg-Strauss syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8258064516129032,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7390321121664405,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024980,
      "question_number": "47",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young patient presented with weakness and cannot extend his elbow; he has toe walking, and ECG sho...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Emery-Dreifuss muscular dystrophy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024981,
      "question_number": "47",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of a patient with inner arm and forearm tingling sensation, thenar muscle weaknes...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. C8-T1",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8387096774193549,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.755465175394001,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024982,
      "question_number": "33",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 35-year-old male presented to the clinic due to weakness that started in the last 3 years and prog...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Nusinersen",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.933852140077821,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6976391231028668,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024983,
      "question_number": "94",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with acute shoulder pain develops subsequent weakness in muscles of the forearm and arm. W...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Upper trunk",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.826530612244898,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7798217643692258,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024984,
      "question_number": "82",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "An elderly thin female presents with foot drop and decreased sensation in the first and second toes....",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Peroneal nerve injury",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7126436781609196,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3366827936980524,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024985,
      "question_number": "148",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q148. What is the treatment for Lambert-Eaton myasthenic syndrome (LEMS) assuming it is paraneoplast...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. 3,4-DAP + Prednisolone"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024986,
      "question_number": "339",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with polymyalgia rheumatica is on steroids (5 mg) post-myocardial infarction and is also t...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Statin myopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8473053892215568,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7869053457577244,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024987,
      "question_number": "48",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young patient with congenital myasthenia gravis (MG) has a history suggestive of slow channel type...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Quinidine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8148148148148148,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7181003242418462,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024988,
      "question_number": "99",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of Miller Fisher syndrome, what is the associated antibody?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. GQ1b"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024989,
      "question_number": "343",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old female with a picture of Miller Fisher syndrome is asked about treatment. What is the ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. IVIG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7861635220125787,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.789193899782135,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024990,
      "question_number": "323",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A scenario about a patient with CIDP is presented. What is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Intravenous immunoglobulin (IVIG)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5819672131147541,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.19623931623931623,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024991,
      "question_number": "384",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q384. In a case of neurofascin 51, what is the pathophysiology?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Paranodal dissection"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024992,
      "question_number": "166",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Typical case of a young lady with diurnal proximal muscle weakness with dysarthria and tongue fascic...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Anti-muscle antibody Myasthenia Gravis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6715686274509803,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7450077945215648,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024993,
      "question_number": "354",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q354. In Myasthenia Gravis, which statement is correct regarding the association with thymoma?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Related to thymoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6594202898550725,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5545099431818182,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024994,
      "question_number": "167",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "An elderly female presents with typical features of CIDP (Chronic Inflammatory Demyelinating Polyneu...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Anti-MAG antibodies",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7653061224489796,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.27673104097974566,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024995,
      "question_number": "100",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A lady who has symptoms of peripheral neuropathy (among other symptoms) and electrophoresis showed t...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Periodic IVIG"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024996,
      "question_number": "199",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Steroid myopathy is due to atrophy of which muscle fiber type?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Type IIb"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024997,
      "question_number": "92",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with back pain radiating to the left lower limb and normal ankle reflex. What muscle is in...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Iliopsoas"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024998,
      "question_number": "44",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the typical serum potassium level in Hypokalemic Periodic Paralysis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Low",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7853403141361257,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6748128577719067,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024999,
      "question_number": "317",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with right hand pain, left leg pain, absent brachioradialis tendon reflex, and ab...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Mononeuritis multiplex",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8134831460674158,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4569487791444832,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025000,
      "question_number": "195",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the cause of prolonged duration and decreased amplitude of the compound muscle action potent...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Conduction block in some fibres"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025001,
      "question_number": "340",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q340. A 69-year-old lady was healthy until age 42 when she started to have myalgia and was diagnosed...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Chronic Progressive External Ophthalmoplegia (CPEO)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8112965340179717,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3520368946963874,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025002,
      "question_number": "95",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q95. What is the management for IgG gammopathy?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. IVIG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6428571428571429,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6359872918070665,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025003,
      "question_number": "56",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with progressive proximal weakness and an autosomal recessive pattern in siblings...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Spinal Muscular Atrophy (SMA)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7692307692307693,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.647373107747106,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025004,
      "question_number": "324",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A female patient with myasthenia gravis (MG) and thymus hyperplasia (grade 4) shows no improvement i...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thymus removal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7651715039577837,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6337973403841667,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025005,
      "question_number": "56",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with progressive proximal weakness and an autosomal recessive pattern in siblings...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Spinal Muscular Atrophy (SMA)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7692307692307693,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.02163331530557058,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025006,
      "question_number": "184",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the typical nerve conduction study (NCS) finding in a patient with motor neuron disease (MND...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Normal SNAPs, reduced CMAP amplitude",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5464788732394367,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.716295427901524,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025007,
      "question_number": "110",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 40-year-old male presented to the outpatient clinic with a history of progressive bilateral upper ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Anti-Mi-2",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9372197309417041,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.396800360522758,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025008,
      "question_number": "110",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 40-year-old male presented to the outpatient clinic with a history of progressive bilateral upper ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Anti-Mi-2",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9372197309417041,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.06697938256790663,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025009,
      "question_number": "4",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which of the following genetic mutations is associated with myotonic dystrophy type 1 (DM1)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CTG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8436018957345972,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5659298361376883,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025010,
      "question_number": "383",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a case of neurofascin 51, what is the appropriate treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Rituximab"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025011,
      "question_number": "86",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is a known association between hepatitis C virus (HCV) and neuropathy?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Cryoglobulinemia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025012,
      "question_number": "12",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q12. The Miller Fisher variant is characterized by which of the following features?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Ophthalmoplegia, gait ataxia, areflexia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025013,
      "question_number": "36",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q36. In a scenario of Hereditary Sensory and Autonomic Neuropathy type 1 (HSAN 1) characterized by p...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. SPTLC1",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8849557522123894,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.663232047103354,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025014,
      "question_number": "26",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of a patient with an androgen receptor gene defect suggestive of Kennedy syndrome...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Testicular atrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7783783783783784,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6561872909698997,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025015,
      "question_number": "11",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the inheritance pattern of paramyotonia congenita?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Autosomal dominant"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025016,
      "question_number": "27",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is a common endocrine complication associated with Myotonic dystrophy?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Insulin resistance",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.673992673992674,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6297061524334252,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025017,
      "question_number": "122",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old male has severe demyelinating neuropathy with palpable nerves and a biopsy showing oni...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Charcot-Marie-Tooth disease type 3 (CMT3)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6549019607843137,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6305369463053695,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025018,
      "question_number": "86",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Scenario of recurrent painless multifocal mononeuropathies at common compression sites. Charcot-Mari...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. PMP-22 deletion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8106796116504854,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7464426877470356,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025019,
      "question_number": "157",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A case of Duchenne muscular dystrophy presents with Gower\u2019s sign and calf hypertrophy. What is the m...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Genetic testing"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025020,
      "question_number": "129",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q129. (Source: Part II 2019mcqs.txt) What type of neurofibrillary tangles are associated with PD-ALS...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Ubiquitin neurofibrillary tangles",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6464646464646465,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.750840579710145,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025021,
      "question_number": "38",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q38. What is the mode of inheritance for adult familial ALS?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Autosomal Dominant"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025022,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of Charcot-Marie-Tooth (CMT) disease with episodic dysarthria and ataxia, where nerve ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. CMT 2",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9239766081871345,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3947175348495965,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025023,
      "question_number": "155",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the most common familial gene associated with amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. C9ORF72",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8130841121495327,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3816003549770744,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025024,
      "question_number": "45",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q45. In a congenital myopathy scenario, a biopsy shows central core features. What is the gene assoc...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. RYR1",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.856140350877193,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5762904140669314,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025025,
      "question_number": "188",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a case of a young female who developed episodic and recurrent weakness at different sites (compre...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. PMP22 deletion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7874720357941835,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7448130595050027,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025026,
      "question_number": "29",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q29. (Source: Part 1 2021mcqs.txt) The genetic inheritance pattern of Hypokalemic Periodic Paralysis...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Autosomal Dominant"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025027,
      "question_number": "98",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with muscle stiffness that worsens with exercise. What is the likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Paramyotonia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6552901023890785,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5744528166487263,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025028,
      "question_number": "200",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q200. A 48-year-old male presents with toe walking and weakness. His family history reveals normal p...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Dysferlinopathy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025029,
      "question_number": "151",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with lower limb distal weakness. The family pedigree showed autosomal dominant i...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Test for MPZ"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025030,
      "question_number": "77",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "The HNPP gene is associated with which of the following?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. PMP22 deletion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5612244897959183,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7912637545848616,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025031,
      "question_number": "63",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q63. A patient was diagnosed with Metachromatic Leukodystrophy. What will you find on nerve conducti...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Demyelinating neuropathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6274509803921569,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6909849915515356,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025032,
      "question_number": "145",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A male patient presents with sensory motor axonal neuropathy, decreased pain, temperature, and vibra...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. SPTLC",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9067357512953368,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7638246717218421,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025033,
      "question_number": "14",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of a patient with cardiomegaly, bilateral carpal tunnel syndrome, peripheral sensory p...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Genetic testing",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8208333333333333,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7131074232336282,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025034,
      "question_number": "121",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young female presents with recurrent neuropathy after minor trauma. Which of the following is the ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. PMP22 deletion"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025035,
      "question_number": "39",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young man who went to sleep at 10 PM woke up at midnight with weakness in his whole body and short...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Carbonic anhydrase",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8678500986193294,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7190202963089835,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025036,
      "question_number": "76",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q76. A case about a male with external ophthalmoplegia and ptosis, with onset before he was 10 years...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Large deletion of mitochondrial DNA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025037,
      "question_number": "176",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Type 2 Charcot\u2013Marie\u2013Tooth disease, what is the typical feature?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. SNAP drop",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.54421768707483,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4648465129438393,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025038,
      "question_number": "44",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 13-year-old boy presents for evaluation of muscle pain and stiffness over the past year. His muscl...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Sodium channel (SCN4A)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025039,
      "question_number": "110",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the diagnosis for a patient with symptoms consistent with Monomelic Amyotrophy (Hirayama dis...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Monomelic Amyotrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8015564202334631,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5621848739495798,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025040,
      "question_number": "60",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with hereditary peripheral neuropathy and transient CNS symptoms presents. What is the lik...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CMTX",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8582375478927203,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7020098441345365,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025041,
      "question_number": "140",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q140. In Charcot\u2010Marie\u2010Tooth disease type 2A (CMT2A), what would you expect?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025042,
      "question_number": "229",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a case of Duchenne muscular dystrophy where the patient\u2019s brother has the same disease, which of ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. The mother is a carrier.",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6485148514851485,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7773885970033081,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025043,
      "question_number": "168",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A typical scenario of hereditary motor and sensory neuropathy (HMSN) shows a biopsy revealing onion ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. PMP-22",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8945868945868946,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7212574850299401,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025044,
      "question_number": "70",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which of the following statements is true regarding Paramyotonia congenita?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025045,
      "question_number": "128",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A one-month-old baby presented with a history of one week of lethargy, weak cry, and weak sucking. E...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Botulism"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025046,
      "question_number": "5",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 2-month-old infant had apnea, macroglossia, and cardiac disease. What is the likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pompe Disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6174496644295302,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7979183205433537,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025047,
      "question_number": "302",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A female patient with a history of neuropathic ulcer underwent testing for PMP22 deletion and duplic...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. HSANI"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025048,
      "question_number": "42",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of paramyotonia congenita, which channel is involved, particularly worsened by cold an...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. SCN4A"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025049,
      "question_number": "42",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with findings suggestive of Myotonic dystrophy. Which gene is associated with thi...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. DMPK",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7534246575342466,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3637137989778535,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025050,
      "question_number": "108",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In hereditary neuropathy with liability to pressure palsies (HNPP), what is the gene involved?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. PMP22 deletion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.703125,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6630269942371854,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025051,
      "question_number": "344",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "An infant presents with hypotonia, cardiomegaly, and macroglossia. Creatine Kinase (CK) levels are e...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Acid Maltase deficiency (Pompe disease)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025052,
      "question_number": "243",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A newborn presents with macroglossia, hypotonia, and myotonia. Which enzyme deficiency is most likel...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. Glycogen phosphorylase",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7308781869688386,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7325756813838882,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025053,
      "question_number": "66",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A man with a long history of malnutrition presented with peripheral neuropathy, ataxia, deafness, an...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Vitamin E",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8618266978922716,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7939900539625436,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025054,
      "question_number": "229",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient who had bariatric surgery developed progressive lower\u2010extremity weakness, sensory ataxia, ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Copper"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025055,
      "question_number": "44",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q44. A patient with history of mastectomy presents with arm pain and dysesthesia over the fourth and...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. MRI of plexus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.739946380697051,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.487185628742515,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025056,
      "question_number": "40",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "After gastric bypass surgery, a patient presents with symptoms of Vitamin B1 deficiency. What is the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Vitamin B1 (Thiamine)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7924528301886793,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.672589339189459,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025057,
      "question_number": "397",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient who underwent bariatric surgery 6 months ago presents with weakness and imbalance. Symptom...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Copper deficiency"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025058,
      "question_number": "31",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient came with right upper limb weakness and intrinsic hand atrophy and diminished reflexes. Wh...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Multifocal motor neuropathy (MMN)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6631299734748011,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5705329153605015,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025059,
      "question_number": "3",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A case scenario of a patient with Vitamin B12 deficiency (with symptoms involving vibration and prop...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Homocysteine (if their methylmalonic acid is elevated, it will be the answer)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025060,
      "question_number": "75",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A lady post-bariatric surgery is noted to have posterior column symptoms and numbness with weakness....",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Vitamin B12"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025061,
      "question_number": "2",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with a radial fracture one month ago presents with pain and erythema. The exam was difficu...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Complex regional pain syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025062,
      "question_number": "58",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with spasticity and upper motor neuron signs. A video shows tongue fasciculations...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025063,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young female presents with dilated pupils, dysphagia, and descending weakness. What is the diagnos...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Presynaptic NMJ disorder",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6325878594249201,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.534195195914133,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025064,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A young male patient presents with eyelid myotonia that increases after eating ice cream or exposure...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Paramyotonia congenita",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7282913165266106,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6926356589147287,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025065,
      "question_number": "26",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q26. A patient with Crohn\u2019s disease who underwent resection presents with fat in the stool, ataxia, ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Vitamin E deficiency"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025066,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q7. A patient presents after a hysterectomy with weakness in hip flexion and knee extension. Which n...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Femoral"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025067,
      "question_number": "5",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with peripheral neuropathy, and his symptoms were provoked after minor surgery. W...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Cobalamin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025068,
      "question_number": "190",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is most common in the pathophysiology of Myasthenia Gravis (MG)?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Acetylcholine blocking",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4072835377183203,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025069,
      "question_number": "215",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Regarding the age of onset of myasthenia gravis (MG), which of the following statements is correct?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025070,
      "question_number": "199",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A smoker male presents with bilateral ptosis and proximal weakness. Where is the lesion located?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Neuromuscular junction (NMJ)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025071,
      "question_number": "9",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a known case of Duchenne muscular dystrophy, what are the first symptoms?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Walk on toe",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6016260162601627,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.29235963486307365,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025072,
      "question_number": "15",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A male patient presents with stiffness that worsens with repeated exercise. Which of the following c...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Paramyotonia congenita",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6776859504132231,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6695783937962385,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025073,
      "question_number": "15",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q15. A male patient presents with perioral fasciculation, areflexia, and systemic manifestations. Wh...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Diabetes Mellitus (DM)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.767816091954023,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7046295460698493,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025074,
      "question_number": "5",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with a known case of diabetes mellitus presents with peripheral neuropathy and has impaire...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "C. Epidermal nerve fiber density",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.566990291262136,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.03633314700950251,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025075,
      "question_number": "16",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a patient with myasthenia gravis, which medication should be avoided in the case of decreased thi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Azathioprine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8010899182561307,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6592121982210928,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025076,
      "question_number": "1",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "What is the cause of prolonged duration and drop amplitude in CMAP?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Conduction block in some fibres"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025077,
      "question_number": "254",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A 14-year-old boy presents with gastrointestinal symptoms and features of Guillain-Barr\u00e9 syndrome. H...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Intravenous immunoglobulin (IVIG)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.841726618705036,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.48351095074263656,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025078,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with hip flexion weakness, thigh adduction weakness, and knee extension weakness ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Femoral at iliacus"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025079,
      "question_number": "19",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q19. In a case of dermatomyositis, what are the histology findings?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025080,
      "question_number": "4",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q4. A patient presents with shoulder and arm pain; MRI of the cervical spine shows a disc prolapse a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Infraspinatus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8148148148148148,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6998522559381748,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025081,
      "question_number": "16",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A case of Crohn\u2019s disease underwent resection and presented with ataxia and decreased reflexes. What...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Vitamin B12 deficiency"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025082,
      "question_number": "111",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "A patient with a radial fracture one month ago complains of pain and erythema. Examination was diffi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Complex regional pain syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025083,
      "question_number": "3",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a case of Mononeuritis Multiplex with weight loss and fever, which histologic finding is most cha...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "B. Lymphocyte infiltration",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7166123778501629,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7882843075369271,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025084,
      "question_number": "19",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "Q19. In a case of dermatomyositis, what are the histology findings?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025085,
      "question_number": "237",
      "subspecialty": "Neuromuscular",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Bell\u2019s palsy, which muscle is involved?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Stylohyoid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6285714285714286,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7706399609184172,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023687,
      "question_number": "80",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Which visual field defect is characterized by contralateral homonymous hemianopia with macular spari...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Contralateral homonymous hemianopia with macular sparing",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6053412462908012,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5654180530213588,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023688,
      "question_number": "108",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A young male presents with central vision loss in the right eye, followed by central vision loss in ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Susac syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7835051546391752,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7259834871296746,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023689,
      "question_number": "52",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q52. In a case of relative afferent pupillary defect (RAPD) in the right eye with right homonymous h...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Left optic tract",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7119565217391305,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5846495557749259,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023690,
      "question_number": "51",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient with headache and papilledema, the headache increases when she lies down, and she has mild...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Weight loss",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7125890736342043,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.730889048646058,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023691,
      "question_number": "11",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient is unable to track with his eyes and has to shake his head to change his gaze. What is thi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Oculomotor apraxia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6842105263157895,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.37642343080987517,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023692,
      "question_number": "6",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q6. What imaging is needed for the evaluation of a suspected diabetic 3rd nerve palsy?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Orbital MRI"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023693,
      "question_number": "33",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A 32-year-old obese woman (BMI 35) presents with progressive headache and transient blurry vision. O...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Acetazolamide",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8663282571912013,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7572614107883817,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023694,
      "question_number": "28",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient with stroke who is unable to move his eyes from one object to another and uses head thrust...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Oculomotor apraxia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023695,
      "question_number": "9",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A 32-year-old male is involved in a high-speed road-traffic accident. On examination he has unilater...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Preganglionic",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8422818791946308,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7019214419316443,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023696,
      "question_number": "15",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "In a patient with right eye optic neuritis, what would you expect to see in the visual evoked potent...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Prolonged P100 latency in the right eye"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023697,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "In Horner\u2019s syndrome, what can hydroxyamphetamine do?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023698,
      "question_number": "47",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with binocular diplopia, with a vertical image from the right eye. The diplopia w...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Right superior oblique muscle"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023699,
      "question_number": "39",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "In a patient with bilateral papilledema, which cranial nerve is most likely to be affected?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. 6th cranial nerve",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6691729323308271,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5155482815057283,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023700,
      "question_number": "38",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient has left eye hypertropia and improves with a head tilt to the left. Where is the lesion?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Left midbrain",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7272727272727273,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7203457295576027,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023701,
      "question_number": "101",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q101. A female patient presents with impaired adduction on right gaze and nystagmus in the other eye...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Right internuclear ophthalmoplegia (INO)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023702,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q34. A patient with a history of blurry vision and headache has acne and is taking vitamin A. Examin...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Acetazolamide",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8143712574850299,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.32735672643273567,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023703,
      "question_number": "212",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Which visual field defect is associated with damage to the optic chiasm?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Bitemporal hemianopia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023704,
      "question_number": "29",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q29. A patient with right optic neuritis will show what in visual evoked potential?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023705,
      "question_number": "33",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q33. A classic presentation of Idiopathic Intracranial Hypertension (IIH) is described. What is the ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Acetazolamide therapy to reduce cerebrospinal fluid production",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5284738041002278,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3613050653802209,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023706,
      "question_number": "48",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q48. Requires diagnosis of internuclear ophthalmoplegia (INO), a specific gaze abnormality, based on...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023707,
      "question_number": "106",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with acute, rapid-onset vision loss in the right eye without any visual field def...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Prefixed chiasm",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8081841432225064,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6666666666666666,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023708,
      "question_number": "48",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A female patient presents with impaired adduction on the right gaze and nystagmus in the other eye. ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Right internuclear ophthalmoplegia (INO)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023709,
      "question_number": "22",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "For the following visual field defect, where do you localize the lesion?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Optic tract",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5263157894736842,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5599192512387594,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023710,
      "question_number": "8",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario, a patient experiences diplopia that worsens when looking toward his left hand do...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Left trochlear nerve"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023711,
      "question_number": "237",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Downbeat Nystagmus is most commonly associated with which of the following lesions?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Cerebellar vermis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023712,
      "question_number": "401",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "For each patient with visual loss, select the most likely loss area from the list below.",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Vitreous",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7226890756302521,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4759066916397071,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023713,
      "question_number": "45",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with horizontal nystagmus in primary gaze that reverses every 90 seconds. What is...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Periodic alternating nystagmus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6647058823529411,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7666995722277065,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023714,
      "question_number": "51",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q51. A 28-year-old obese woman presents with daily throbbing headaches, transient visual obscuration...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Weight loss and acetazolamide therapy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023715,
      "question_number": "216",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A 5-day postpartum patient presents with right eye ptosis. On examination, the right pupil measures ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Horner's syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8198529411764706,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3611723226090789,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023716,
      "question_number": "17",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient with headache and papilledema, the headache increased when she lies down and she had mild ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Weight loss",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7653061224489796,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6828202995008319,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023717,
      "question_number": "43",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "What suggests central nystagmus?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023718,
      "question_number": "36",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "What MRI finding is commonly associated with idiopathic intracranial hypertension (IIH)?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Empty sella"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023719,
      "question_number": "6",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "What is true about popping nystagmus?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023720,
      "question_number": "53",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "In a case of right eye complete vision loss with superior temporal defects in the contralateral eye,...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Anterior chiasm"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023721,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old man suffers bilateral vertebral artery dissections and multiple brainstem and cerebell...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. 1-Hz pendular oscillation comprising conjugate vertical and torsional components; the right eye intorts"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023722,
      "question_number": "44",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient after minor trauma was reading a newspaper and presented with diplopia, worse when the pat...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Right Superior oblique",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7888446215139442,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7562248043632914,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023723,
      "question_number": "65",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient with right relative afferent pupillary defect (RAPD) and right homonymous hemianopia is ev...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Left optic tract",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6983240223463687,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6581328625027588,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023724,
      "question_number": "146",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Which visual field defect is characterized by loss of vision in the lower quadrant of the visual fie...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Contralateral inferior quadrantopia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6181818181818182,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5110208102450438,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023725,
      "question_number": "413",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "What is the most common cause of fourth cranial nerve (CN) palsy?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Microvascular",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6850828729281768,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6727822145478092,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023726,
      "question_number": "49",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient has left eye hypertropia that improves with a head tilt to the left. Where is the lesion l...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Left midbrain",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7446808510638298,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3473766992472756,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023727,
      "question_number": "91",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "In a scenario about right internuclear ophthalmoplegia (INO), where is the lesion located?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Right MLF"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023728,
      "question_number": "10",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A 22-year-old male presents with symptoms suggestive of right fourth cranial nerve palsy. What is th...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Trauma"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023729,
      "question_number": "113",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Susac syndrome is associated with a clinical triad of which of the following?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. All of the above",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5223367697594502,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6596485122672698,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023730,
      "question_number": "38",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q38. Requires interpretation of the Bielschowsky head tilt test to localize the side of a trochlear ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023731,
      "question_number": "5",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A case scenario of a patient with one eye ptosis and normal pupils is presented. What is the most li...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Small vessel ischemia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6606060606060606,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.499637943519189,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023732,
      "question_number": "510",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A case scenario describes a patient with a history of blurry vision and headache. She has acne and i...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Acetazolamide"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023733,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "The amplitude of the oscillation is larger in the right eye. Which of the following structures is mo...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Left inferior olive",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7008086253369272,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6224226804123711,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023734,
      "question_number": "3",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old man suffers bilateral vertebral artery dissection leading to brain stem and cerebellar...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Left inferior olive",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.896551724137931,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.363501895165018,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023735,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with symptoms and signs consistent with idiopathic intracranial hypertension (IIH...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Immediate lumbar puncture with CSF drainage and acetazolamide therapy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023736,
      "question_number": "42",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q42. A clinical feature suggestive of right medial longitudinal fasciculus (MLF) involvement include...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Right MLF"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023737,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q21. Requires localization of the lesion causing specific pendular nystagmus post-brainstem stroke b...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Lesion in the dorsal medulla affecting the inferior olivary nucleus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5772058823529411,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7598268398268399,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023738,
      "question_number": "26",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "What would suggest central nystagmus rather than peripheral nystagmus?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023739,
      "question_number": "27",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Most common cause of isolated 4th nerve palsy is:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Trauma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6037735849056604,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4450076026355803,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023740,
      "question_number": "26",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q26. In a patient with ipsilateral scotoma and contralateral quadrantanopia, where is the localizati...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Optic chiasm",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8074866310160428,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.33625657729892255,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023741,
      "question_number": "68",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Which visual field defect is characterized by loss of vision in the upper quadrant of the visual fie...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Contralateral superior quadrantopia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6181818181818182,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.40850033032371724,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023742,
      "question_number": "27",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "In a case of acute painless vision loss (Non-AION), what is the appropriate treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. No treatment available",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6612903225806451,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6448720343732487,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023743,
      "question_number": "55",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Hydroxyamphetamine drops help differentiate between which conditions?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023744,
      "question_number": "16",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "In the case of giant cell arteritis, what is the next step in management?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Steroid therapy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023745,
      "question_number": "111",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q111. A young patient presents with one eye visual loss followed by hearing loss. What is the likely...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Susac syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7081967213114754,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.22420564084255623,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023746,
      "question_number": "293",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following has a large effect on Relative Afferent Pupillary Defect (RAPD)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Optic nerve",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.680161943319838,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6915846016114593,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023747,
      "question_number": "206",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with eye pain that worsens with movement. Which of the following conditions could...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Optic neuritis"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023748,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "In the case of the largest relative afferent pupillary defect (RAPD), which structure is primarily a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Optic nerves",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7222222222222222,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.31174447174447173,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023749,
      "question_number": "55",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q55. Focuses on the utility of hydroxyamphetamine drops in localizing Horner's syndrome (differentia...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023750,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "In an embryological problem of the optic chiasm, what finding would you expect to see in the examina...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Seesaw nystagmus",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7030716723549488,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3661122458904776,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023751,
      "question_number": "108",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Requires recognition of Susac syndrome based on key features including visual and hearing loss.",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023752,
      "question_number": "20",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q20. Examination of patients with anisocoria using hydroxyamphetamine eye drops helps in the diagnos...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pre and post ganglionic lesion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6819672131147541,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.51201248049922,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023753,
      "question_number": "123",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of Leber's Hereditary Optic Neuropathy (LHON), what diagnostic tests would you conside...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. ECG"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023754,
      "question_number": "50",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "In a case of optic neuritis in the right eye, which of the following findings is consistent with the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Prolonged P100 in the right eye"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023755,
      "question_number": "363",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient had left eye heterotopia and skew deviation, tilting to the right. Where is the lesion?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Left midbrain"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023756,
      "question_number": "31",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A middle-aged patient presented with sudden severe headache and double vision. Examination shows com...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Pituitary apoplexy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023757,
      "question_number": "54",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient with Horner syndrome did not respond to either hydroxyamphetamine or cocaine. What is the ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. ICA dissection",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7800586510263929,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.41607898448519043,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023758,
      "question_number": "73",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q73. A patient with Horner syndrome did not respond to either hydroxyamphetamine or cocaine. What ty...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Pre-ganglionic",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6527415143603134,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6872490407780851,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023759,
      "question_number": "323",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q323. What is the most common cause of trochlear nerve atrophy?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Trauma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6130653266331658,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.12089124200308846,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023760,
      "question_number": "67",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A 75-year-old male patient with a history of hypertension and diabetes mellitus presents with chroni...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Oral Steroid"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023761,
      "question_number": "235",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A female patient presents with central nervous system manifestations, including hearing loss and ret...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Susac syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8105515587529976,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7390069532856723,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023762,
      "question_number": "14",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q14. What is the most common cause of trochlear nerve palsy?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Trauma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6373626373626373,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5649318827795746,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023763,
      "question_number": "180",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old female presented with visual blurring and is diagnosed with Brun\u2019s nystagmus. Brun\u2019s n...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Ipsilateral vestibular system",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9133089133089133,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.21566523605150215,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023764,
      "question_number": "96",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with Horner\u2019s syndrome that does not react to cocaine or amphetamine. What type o...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Post-ganglionic",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7100591715976331,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.45080469769464987,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023765,
      "question_number": "352",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q352. What is the artery associated with a left sectoranopia sparing the horizontal meridian?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. MCA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023766,
      "question_number": "268",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient with subarachnoid hemorrhage (SAH) complains of visual issues, and examination shows retin...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Vitreous"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023767,
      "question_number": "354",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A young lady presents with proptosis, ptosis, complete ophthalmoplegia, and decreased sensation in V...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Urgent neuroimaging (MRI with contrast) and referral to neuro-ophthalmology",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5304347826086957,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5121891561353444,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023768,
      "question_number": "104",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of idiopathic intracranial hypertension, what can you see on brain MRI?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Empty Sella",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7248908296943232,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5821665438467207,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023769,
      "question_number": "279",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q279. A patient came with right optic atrophy and left papilledema. Where is the localization of the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Left frontal",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7357142857142858,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5737992971495509,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023770,
      "question_number": "12",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q12. A patient is worse when he looks down to the left, with intact horizontal gaze and no other neu...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Left trochlear nerve"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023771,
      "question_number": "90",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient with right relative afferent pupillary defect (RAPD) and right homonymous hemianopia; wher...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Left optic tract",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6746987951807228,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7990003029385034,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023772,
      "question_number": "74",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A male presents with progressive external ophthalmoplegia and bilateral ptosis, with symptom onset b...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Kearns-Sayre syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6784140969162996,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7755329008341056,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023773,
      "question_number": "57",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Patient came with Leber optic neuropathy; what is your next step?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. ECG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5163934426229508,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.46560967263602143,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023774,
      "question_number": "438",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A patient with ptosis is evaluated with Hydroxyamphetamine. What does this test differentiate?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023775,
      "question_number": "30",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q30. A patient had optic neuritis in the right eye. What is the finding in the visual potential test...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Right eye prolonged in P100"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023776,
      "question_number": "135",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A 73-year-old male presented with severe temporal-sided headache associated with jaw claudication an...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Posterior ciliary artery"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023777,
      "question_number": "124",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q124. Which of the following infections can cause internuclear ophthalmoplegia (INO)?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. All of the above"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023778,
      "question_number": "64",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A young adult has progressive bilateral painless decrease in visual acuity over 2\u20133 years. His broth...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. ECG"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023779,
      "question_number": "23",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Q23. Where is the location of popping nystagmus?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pons",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6524822695035462,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.07016754750927696,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023780,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "A young male presents with progressive bilateral ptosis and ophthalmoparesis, with no family history...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Kearns-Sayre syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6616915422885572,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.18523659305993692,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023781,
      "question_number": "194",
      "subspecialty": "Neuroophthalmology",
      "question_text": "Which type of visual field defect is characterized by a loss of vision in one eye?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Monocular vision loss"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022648,
      "question_number": "23",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "Which antipsychotic medication has the highest risk of weight gain?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Clozapine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6875,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7130248729606847,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022649,
      "question_number": "30",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "Which condition is improved with acetylcholinesterase inhibitors?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Apathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6736842105263158,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.657323055360897,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022650,
      "question_number": "19",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A patient with new-onset behavioral changes is referred first to psychiatry and then to neurology. W...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Send for ammonia level",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7535410764872521,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4684169482713803,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022651,
      "question_number": "1",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "Q1. What is the most common psychiatric manifestation of Wilson's disease?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Depression",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7384615384615385,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6933061375857593,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022652,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "Anxiety most commonly complicates which of the following diseases?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Parkinson\u2019s Disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5462184873949579,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6116133235605505,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022653,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A delirious patient presents to the emergency department. What is your next step?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Metabolic panel"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022654,
      "question_number": "32",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "In Alzheimer's disease, which antipsychotic medication is known to increase weight?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Olanzapine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7297297297297297,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7013502779984114,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022655,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A 60-year-old male patient had visual loss and denied it. Upon examination, he had a visual field de...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Visual anosognosia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7873015873015873,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4323104693140794,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022656,
      "question_number": "29",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "Q29. Which of the following is a common psychiatric manifestation in Wilson's disease?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Depression",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7671232876712328,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4695970695970696,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022657,
      "question_number": "26",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "Which of the following antipsychotic medications has the highest affinity for D2 dopamine receptors?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "B. Risperidone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7644787644787645,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.56398243045388,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022658,
      "question_number": "27",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "Which of the following antipsychotic medications causes the most weight gain?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Olanzapine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7169811320754716,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7349809514506203,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022659,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient presented with a visual field defect but denied having left homonymous hemianopia...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Visual anosognosia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022660,
      "question_number": "38",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "After a traumatic brain injury (TBI), a patient wakes up apathetic. Which part of the brain is likel...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Frontal lobe",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7544483985765125,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.560337726523888,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022661,
      "question_number": "16",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "In a case of Gerstmann syndrome, what is the associated language deficit?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anomia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6228070175438597,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6199065872121114,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022662,
      "question_number": "31",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "What is the primary characteristic that differentiates apraxia of speech from dysarthria?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Impaired coordination of speech movements"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022663,
      "question_number": "28",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "An epilepsy patient on Levetiracetam presents with low mood. What would be a feature of depression?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Suicidal ideation"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022664,
      "question_number": "33",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A soldier who was driving a military tank that exploded has some injuries, but two of his friends di...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "C. Adjustment disorder",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8057851239669421,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6254919108001749,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022665,
      "question_number": "24",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient presents with symptoms of delirium, showing decreased attention but no focal neur...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Urine analysis and culture"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022666,
      "question_number": "115",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A middle-aged male presented to the outpatient clinic with his father, who stated that the patient h...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. MRI"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022667,
      "question_number": "3",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A young female presents with a right arm focal clonic seizure lasting for 1 hour, triggered by stres...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Stop AEDs",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8245931283905967,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5218372644171086,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022668,
      "question_number": "186",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A bus driver has a seizure and requests that you do not inform his employer about the seizure. What ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Tell him you have to inform his employer",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5459057071960298,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7731909845788849,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022669,
      "question_number": "28",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A patient with refractory epilepsy is scheduled for EMU admission after a 1-year wait. The chairman ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Call the chairman and discuss the case priority",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6625194401244168,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.32822222222222225,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022670,
      "question_number": "228",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A patient with a traumatic brain injury (TBI) wakes up and exhibits apathy. Which lobe of the brain ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Frontal lobe",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7615894039735099,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7699196326061998,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022671,
      "question_number": "158",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A patient with epilepsy, a trucker, asked you, his physician, not to disclose this information to hi...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Ask him to tell his employer",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6203473945409429,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.588905342294111,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022672,
      "question_number": "194",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A patient with generalized tonic-clonic seizures believes his condition is caused by the devil and t...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "B. Send him to the ethical committee",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6962233169129721,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.49404417717127325,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022673,
      "question_number": "113",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A 50-year-old male patient presents with confusion and delirium without fever, which has since resol...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. EEG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8811700182815356,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7146255590446284,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022674,
      "question_number": "109",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "Q109. A patient on pregabalin, suspected of drug abuse, is evaluated. What should you do?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Refer to psychiatry",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6064981949458483,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7454133635334088,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022675,
      "question_number": "124",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Parkinson's disease who is experiencing hallucinations while on pramipexole, what ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Stop pramipexole",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.750733137829912,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.486475152023485,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022676,
      "question_number": "190",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson\u2019s disease (PD) on multiple agents developed hallucinations. What is the rec...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Stop amantadine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6863905325443787,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5845968297725707,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022677,
      "question_number": "9",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A female presents with abnormal movements and a greenish corneal ring (Kayser-Fleischer rings). What...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Depression (but mood disturbance more common)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022678,
      "question_number": "223",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A patient on pramipexol for Parkinson's Disease (PD) develops hallucinations. What is the recommende...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Stop pramipexol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6051873198847262,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5667435306174737,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022679,
      "question_number": "44",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "Q44. What is the management of functional tremor?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. Psychotherapy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5251396648044693,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7365616311399444,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022680,
      "question_number": "152",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "In Balint syndrome, which one of these clinical pictures is one of the presentations?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Simultagnosia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6775510204081633,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6217290799815072,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022681,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson's disease has developed dementia after several years and is now agitated. H...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Quetiapine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8736616702355461,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2999205358156431,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022682,
      "question_number": "27",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "Q27. Which of the following findings is in favor of a diagnosis of functional tremor?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022683,
      "question_number": "239",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A newly diagnosed Huntington's disease patient states that he does not want to inform his employer. ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022684,
      "question_number": "32",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A patient diagnosed with ALS, his son asks you not to tell his father about the diagnosis. What shou...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022685,
      "question_number": "105",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A patient with Parkinson's Disease on treatment presents with visual hallucinations and agitation. W...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Pimavanserin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.808641975308642,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.48310066127847173,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022686,
      "question_number": "82",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Wernicke's aphasia, which of the following symptoms is most commonly observed?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022687,
      "question_number": "182",
      "subspecialty": "Neuropsychiatry",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a right occipital lesion and visual field defect. What condition could be as...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Visual anosognosia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025086,
      "question_number": "476",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "Q476. A patient with resected breast cancer who received radiotherapy developed Horner\u2019s syndrome an...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Radiation-induced syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025087,
      "question_number": "457",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "Q457. An HIV patient presents with a seizure. What is the likely culprit medication?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Efavirenz",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7363636363636363,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6587711069418386,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025088,
      "question_number": "236",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with a history of tingling sensation, numbness, and paresthesia, indicating smal...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Arsenic"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025089,
      "question_number": "529",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A 52-year-old female with dyslipidemia on statin had pneumonia and was admitted to the hospital. Aft...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Concomitant use of erythromycin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025090,
      "question_number": "102",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A tuberculosis (TB) patient started on treatment and then had a seizure. What medication is causing ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Isoniazid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.779783393501805,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7990348155808342,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025091,
      "question_number": "192",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "Q192. What is the most common side effect of lithium?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Tremors",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6219512195121951,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6998902305159166,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025092,
      "question_number": "540",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "What medication causes sensory ataxia?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pyridoxine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5481481481481482,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6404860056411369,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025093,
      "question_number": "320",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "Flumazenil",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025094,
      "question_number": "226",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "What is the recommended treatment for severe arsenic poisoning?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Chelating agents",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6048780487804878,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5788798631893972,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025095,
      "question_number": "396",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "Naloxone",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025096,
      "question_number": "241",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "What is the medication that causes neuropathy and myopathy?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Chloroquine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6744186046511628,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5891529113005624,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025097,
      "question_number": "214",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "Q214. A patient on anti-TB agents developed seizures. Which of the following agents can cause it?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. INH"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025098,
      "question_number": "113",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A young patient with a history of liver transplant on cyclosporine presents with severe lower limb t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Decrease cyclosporine dose",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7547169811320755,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4603561844352281,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025099,
      "question_number": "377",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "What medication can cause a positive Romberg sign and a scenario suggestive of sensory neuronopathy?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pyridoxine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7644787644787645,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.769819378948305,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025100,
      "question_number": "172",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A patient receiving intrathecal methotrexate presents with clinical and biological findings typical ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Folinic acid (leucovorin)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025101,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A patient with newly diagnosed pulmonary tuberculosis is started on standard four\u2010drug therapy. Two ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Isoniazid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8917431192660551,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7787182587666264,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025102,
      "question_number": "115",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following agents can cause sensory ataxia, vibration, and proprioception loss?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pyridoxine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7857142857142857,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7495183044315993,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025103,
      "question_number": "129",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "Q129. A patient with HIV on HAART developed seizures. What is the most likely cause?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Efavirenz",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7363636363636363,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.43752629364745477,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025104,
      "question_number": "53",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A young patient with a history of alcohol abuse presents with hallucinations, nystagmus, and ataxic ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Wernicke encephalopathy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025105,
      "question_number": "11",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A pregnant lady with hyperemesis gravidarum presents with paresthesia in the lower limbs, nystagmus,...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Vitamin B1"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025106,
      "question_number": "100",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "High-dose pyridoxine toxicity may cause which of the following symptoms?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Sensory ataxia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6484018264840182,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7741446513642269,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025107,
      "question_number": "50",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "What medication causes sensory ataxia?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pyridoxine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5481481481481482,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7990519373454246,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025108,
      "question_number": "50",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A patient who was arrested by police is encephalopathic and has a halitosis odor. What should you ad...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thiamine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8014981273408239,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6906728538283062,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025109,
      "question_number": "74",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A 53-year-old male presents with abdominal pain, vomiting, diarrhea, and gait difficulty. He is foun...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Arsenic",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9027777777777778,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.40150005859603893,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025110,
      "question_number": "1",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "In Wernicke's encephalopathy, what type of memory is typically impaired?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Episodic memory",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6278026905829597,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6722539932952081,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025111,
      "question_number": "62",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A patient on long-term use of colchicine developed myopathy and neuropathy. What is the likely cause...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Colchicine-induced myopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6743515850144092,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4545837901661466,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025112,
      "question_number": "60",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario as above (Wernicke encephalopathy presentation), what is the recommended treatm...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thiamine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7326007326007326,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7659041576223076,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025113,
      "question_number": "64",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "In the same patient with colchicine toxicity (implicitly referring to Q62), what is the expected mus...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "B. Autophagic vacuoles",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7395498392282959,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5999231852515683,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025114,
      "question_number": "5",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "An 85-year-old female treated for herpetic neuralgia became lethargic and confused 5 days after trea...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Drug-induced encephalopathy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025115,
      "question_number": "76",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A tuberculosis (TB) patient started on treatment and then had a seizure. What medication is causing ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Isoniazid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.779783393501805,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7996892902223517,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025116,
      "question_number": "4",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "Intoxication with which of the following agents would cause sensory ataxia with proprioception and v...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Pyridoxine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7985865724381626,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7769935913036424,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025117,
      "question_number": "2",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A post-bariatric surgery patient presents with nystagmus and ataxia, with findings suggestive of Wer...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Vitamin B1 deficiency",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.745679012345679,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7953660797034291,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025118,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "Q41. What is the most common side effect of lithium?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Tremor"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025119,
      "question_number": "359",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A case presents of a man with an ataxic gait and confusion, accompanied by a peculiar smell from his...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Administration of intravenous thiamine before glucose administration"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025120,
      "question_number": "45",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "Mees lines are associated with which type of poisoning?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Arsenic",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6708074534161491,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5183444047010731,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025121,
      "question_number": "56",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A patient on anti-TB medication plus pyridoxine presents with painful neuropathy. Sensory exam and r...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pyridoxine toxicity",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7310704960835509,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.791449898213074,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025122,
      "question_number": "74",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A patient developed cognitive impairment and ataxia. MRI showed high signals in the mammillary bodie...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thiamine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8411214953271028,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7620937732572562,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025123,
      "question_number": "17",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "Q17. What is the case scenario associated with Strachan Syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Vitamin B12 deficiency"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025124,
      "question_number": "203",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A patient was on Valproic acid and is discovered to be drowsy. What do you need to check?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Ammonia level",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6932270916334662,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6879963171826448,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100025125,
      "question_number": "78",
      "subspecialty": "Neurotoxicology",
      "question_text": "A patient on pregabalin (suspected to be abusing the drug); what will you do?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. Refer to psychiatry",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5572519083969466,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7962207429675757,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023276,
      "question_number": "87",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A patient in a nursing home informs you that he has been physically abused. What should you do?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023277,
      "question_number": "89",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A patient refuses admission and refuses to sign a Leave Against Medical Advice (LAMA). What is the a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. No need to sign",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7015384615384616,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4850318815519291,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023278,
      "question_number": "88",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "An intern wants to perform a procedure that he knows about but has never done before, and the superv...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023279,
      "question_number": "86",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q86. What is the definition of euthanasia?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023280,
      "question_number": "101",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "In a scenario involving a female patient with hematologic metastasis, what is the most likely skin-r...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Skin melanoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7033639143730887,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6449787835926449,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023281,
      "question_number": "65",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "To act in the best interest of the patient is an example of which ethical principle?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Beneficence",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7312775330396476,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5387067976023466,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023282,
      "question_number": "98",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A group of doctors conducted research, and after finishing, the chairman\u2019s friend asked to add the c...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023283,
      "question_number": "91",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A patient diagnosed with a serious disease has no family members. How should you break the bad news?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023284,
      "question_number": "90",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Which enzyme is the rate-limiting step in catecholamine synthesis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023285,
      "question_number": "95",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "EEG showed diffuse slowing in:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023286,
      "question_number": "9",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "In regards to patient safety and preventing medical errors, which research methodology is the best?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023287,
      "question_number": "99",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A pharmacy company that conducted a clinical trial for a new antiepileptic drug (AED) asks you to gi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Disclose this in the presentation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7343173431734318,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7281489594742607,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023288,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "You have a language barrier with an ER staff member. What is the best way to communicate?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023289,
      "question_number": "61",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "What is the definition of informed consent?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023290,
      "question_number": "180",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Topiramate",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023291,
      "question_number": "195",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is the most sensitive test?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023292,
      "question_number": "1",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "What is the definition of euthanasia?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023293,
      "question_number": "70",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A nurse got a needle stick in her finger after blood extraction from a patient. She refuses to repor...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Report the incident.",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7399577167019028,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5740458015267176,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023294,
      "question_number": "133",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario, what is the most appropriate treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023295,
      "question_number": "10",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "According to resource allocation, when building a children's hospital, which statement regarding the...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023296,
      "question_number": "348",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Felbamate",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023297,
      "question_number": "394",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Medical therapy",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023298,
      "question_number": "160",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A pharmaceutical company conducting a clinical trial for a new AED offers to sponsor your presentati...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Disclose this in the presentation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7228915662650602,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7710590702551555,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023299,
      "question_number": "347",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "MTL",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023300,
      "question_number": "257",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Carbamazepine",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023301,
      "question_number": "360",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Thiamine",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023302,
      "question_number": "495",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Ethosuximide",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023303,
      "question_number": "353",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "What is the mechanism?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023304,
      "question_number": "262",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Taking one medication",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023305,
      "question_number": "503",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q503. CK level",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023306,
      "question_number": "88",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "The same patient is asking what treatment you will give. What will you choose?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023307,
      "question_number": "313",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "3.",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023308,
      "question_number": "269",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q269. MRI/MRV",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023309,
      "question_number": "485",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "In the case of the patient mentioned above, what is the next step in management?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023310,
      "question_number": "533",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "The same patient is asking about the treatment options. What is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. IVIG",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7238095238095238,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7549571603427172,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023311,
      "question_number": "203",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario, what is the most important and useful way for investigation?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023312,
      "question_number": "478",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "In a scenario with a different presentation, what is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. CVT"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023313,
      "question_number": "270",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "tPA",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023314,
      "question_number": "433",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is associated with apoptosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023315,
      "question_number": "225",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Same scenario as above. What should be done next?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023316,
      "question_number": "333",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario, if the patient came to the emergency room, what is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. IV diazepam",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.702928870292887,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.06668539852018357,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023317,
      "question_number": "230",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with hyperreflexia and headache, and brain MRI reveals multiple diffuse enhancing...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Chest X-ray"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023318,
      "question_number": "356",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Endarterectomy",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023319,
      "question_number": "434",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "After all stroke workups are completed except for CTA, what is the next step?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023320,
      "question_number": "506",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "What EEG finding is associated with non-convulsive status epilepticus (NCSE)?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023321,
      "question_number": "522",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A patient diagnosed with ALS, his son asks you not to tell his father about the diagnosis. What shou...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023322,
      "question_number": "311",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q311. What is the mechanism of the patient's condition?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023323,
      "question_number": "55",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A female patient with weight gain presents with carpal tunnel syndrome on the left side and had dela...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Thyroid Function Tests (TFT)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7184466019417476,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.736,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023324,
      "question_number": "156",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q156. (Source: Part I 2018mcqs.txt) AMAN scenario.",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023325,
      "question_number": "260",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Ipsilateral nose wiping",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023326,
      "question_number": "44",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q44. The same patient is asking about the associated antibody. Which antibody is most likely present...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-GM1",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7808764940239044,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.735969387755102,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023327,
      "question_number": "276",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Which of the following statements about glucose is correct?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023328,
      "question_number": "159",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q159. Levodopa",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023329,
      "question_number": "494",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q494. Chronic Progressive External Ophthalmoplegia (CPEO plus) is best classified as which of the fo...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023330,
      "question_number": "305",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q305. (Source: Part II 2022mcqs.txt) Figure of 4 left limb extension Which of the following neurolog...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023331,
      "question_number": "31",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q31. In a patient with Progressive Supranuclear Palsy (PSP), what is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023332,
      "question_number": "40",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario, what is the next step in management?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023333,
      "question_number": "24",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient with poor oral intake has a one-week history of ongoing infection. What is the mo...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Systemic"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023334,
      "question_number": "304",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q304. Dorsolateral",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023335,
      "question_number": "52",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q52. What is the recommendation for NSAID use in the 3rd trimester of pregnancy?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023336,
      "question_number": "64",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A nurse with multiple sclerosis comes for a follow-up. She is about to get married to a doctor\u2019s fri...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023337,
      "question_number": "228",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "In the management of spasticity and weakness due to baclofen, which of the following should be tried...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Baclofen pump"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023338,
      "question_number": "58",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q58. A group of doctors completed research, and the chairman\u2019s friend asked to add the chairman\u2019s na...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023339,
      "question_number": "324",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "In a comatose patient with fever and retinal redness/orange with vascular changes, what is the cause...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023340,
      "question_number": "236",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A patient with impaired decision-making capacity wishes to discharge home because he feels better. W...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023341,
      "question_number": "122",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A 76-year-old gentleman with Parkinson\u2019s disease has been maintained on his medications with good mo...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Asymmetrical atrophy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.79,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7079783113865221,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023342,
      "question_number": "6",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Hemianesthesia is best described as:",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023343,
      "question_number": "348",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Lamictal",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023344,
      "question_number": "191",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Difficulty in the pronunciation of words is referred to as:",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023345,
      "question_number": "36",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A drug company is providing a new drug similar to an already existing one with the same usages and s...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Refuse and report them to Nezaha",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7648183556405354,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5637342908438061,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023346,
      "question_number": "188",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with dysarthria and dysphagia. What do you expect to find on this patient?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023347,
      "question_number": "358",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q358. A patient presents with hyperreflexia and headache, and an MRI shows diffuse lesions. What is ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "C. Chest X-ray of fibroblasts",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7447447447447447,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7941325240263025,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023348,
      "question_number": "114",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "After receiving methylprednisolone, how long should a woman wait before nursing to minimize risks?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. 3 to 4 hours",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7804878048780488,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4790852511217253,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023349,
      "question_number": "3",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q3. Mental retardation",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023350,
      "question_number": "365",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A 19-year-old female patient came with encephalopathy; MRI showed high signal intensity in the basal...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Lumbar puncture"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023351,
      "question_number": "23",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A young male presents with progressive external ophthalmoplegia. What is the likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023352,
      "question_number": "28",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "A case scenario presents a patient with a CT brain scan showing multiple brain calcifications. What ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023353,
      "question_number": "73",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q73. A nurse got a needle stick in her finger after blood extraction from a patient. She refuses to ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Report the incident.",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7432150313152401,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.44178383128295257,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023354,
      "question_number": "105",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q105. Propranolol",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023355,
      "question_number": "261",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q261. Valproate is primarily used in the treatment of which of the following conditions?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023356,
      "question_number": "69",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q69. (Source: Part 2 2020 copymcqs.txt) Aspirin (ASA) is commonly used in neurology for which of the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023357,
      "question_number": "264",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Propranolol",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023358,
      "question_number": "165",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario as above, what is the next step in management?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023359,
      "question_number": "83",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Q83. Weakness is a common neurological symptom. Which of the following is the most likely cause of a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Stroke",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7484662576687117,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6412011030538249,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023360,
      "question_number": "306",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Carbamazepine",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023361,
      "question_number": "80",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Dual antiplatelet therapy (DAPT) is primarily used in which of the following clinical scenarios?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023362,
      "question_number": "78",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Anomia is best described as which of the following?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023363,
      "question_number": "263",
      "subspecialty": "Other Unclassified",
      "question_text": "Keppra",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022630,
      "question_number": "16",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "A case of a child with a rash on the face, contralateral hemiparesis, and radiographic findings of g...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Sturge-Weber syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022631,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "In neonatal mild hypoxic ischemic encephalopathy, what is the most common presentation?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Hypotonia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022632,
      "question_number": "17",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "A case of a child with caf\u00e9 au lait spots, axillary freckling, and Lisch nodules is indicative of:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Neurofibromatosis type 1 (NF1)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6129032258064516,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.708221977676466,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022633,
      "question_number": "119",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is the first-line treatment for migraine in children?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Acetaminophen",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6666666666666666,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6801699716713882,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022634,
      "question_number": "206",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "When should brain imaging be performed in pediatric patients with headaches?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Occipital headache"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022635,
      "question_number": "62",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "An infant presented with choreoathetosis and hearing loss. Brain MRI reported globus pallidus hyperi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Kernicterus"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022636,
      "question_number": "19",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "In a patient with tic disorder and ADHD, which medication is commonly used?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Guanfacine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022637,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "In a case of Sturge-Weber syndrome (hint: port wine stain on the face), what associated condition is...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Glaucoma"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022638,
      "question_number": "6",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "A neonate developed seizures within 24 hours of birth and has high bilirubin. What would be the most...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Globus Pallidus"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022639,
      "question_number": "52",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "A pregnant woman at 10 weeks is concerned about the side effects of steroids. Which of the following...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Cleft palate"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022640,
      "question_number": "79",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q79. A patient with facial weakness and seizures presents with what other condition?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Sturge-Weber disease"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022641,
      "question_number": "118",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "A 10-year-old boy has a headache that is preceded by red circular colors for a few seconds. What is ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Migraine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7146974063400576,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5470604471432514,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022642,
      "question_number": "197",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "In a young child presenting with seizures, hypotonia, and a cherry red spot, which enzyme is affecte...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Hexosaminidase A",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6877192982456141,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7538840937114674,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022643,
      "question_number": "213",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "A baby presents with diplopia, dysarthria, ataxia followed by headache. What is the most likely diag...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Migraine with brainstem aura",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6181818181818182,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.11480945489628558,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022644,
      "question_number": "47",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is the indication for brain imaging in a pediatric patient with migraine?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Occipital headache"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022645,
      "question_number": "1",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "A 7-year-old boy presents with visual hallucinations in the form of colorful and circular objects mo...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Carbamazepine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8781362007168458,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7398502735387273,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022646,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "A scenario of a child with head trauma followed by loss of consciousness after 1 hour is suggestive ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Epidural hematoma",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7283950617283951,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6308548968227973,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022647,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Pediatric Neurology",
      "question_text": "In a case of Sturge-Weber syndrome (hint: port wine stain on the face), what associated condition is...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Glaucoma"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024042,
      "question_number": "71",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "What treatment is indicated for a young female with excessive daytime sleepiness, hyperphagia, and n...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "C. Topiramate",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8364611260053619,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.44593756460616085,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024043,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "Restless Legs Syndrome (RLS) is most commonly associated with which of the following?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pregnancy is a risk factor",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5942028985507246,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4255262099477142,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024044,
      "question_number": "70",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q70. A 65-year-old male presents with disturbed nocturnal sleep. His wife states that he has been sh...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Clonazepam",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8232445520581114,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6018064009424701,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024045,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "A case scenario of a diabetic patient with symptoms suggestive of Restless Legs Syndrome (RLS). What...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Check Ferritin and iron",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5967365967365967,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3913978494623656,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024046,
      "question_number": "30",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old male presents with poor sleeping and recent mood changes, early awakening as reported ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Pharmacotherapy and hypnotic measures have good effects.",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.62,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5898499840408554,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024047,
      "question_number": "65",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "Excessive daytime sleep and an increase in eating habits can be treated with which of the following?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Modafinil",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7644787644787645,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7909081116018528,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024048,
      "question_number": "76",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "Pregnancy is a risk factor for which of the following?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024049,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q35. A patient is impulsive and a drug seeker with a scenario of Restless Legs Syndrome (RLS). What ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Gabapentin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7774294670846394,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.44334635715927373,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024050,
      "question_number": "77",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q77. Excessive daytime sleep and an increase in eating habits may indicate which condition?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "C. Serum oxybate",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7091633466135459,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6168952618453866,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024051,
      "question_number": "74",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "Excessive daytime sleep and increasing eating habits may be treated with which of the following?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "B. Methylphenidate (According to UpToDate)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6934306569343066,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5760193782801777,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024052,
      "question_number": "51",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "Pregnancy is a risk factor for which of the following?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024053,
      "question_number": "74",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with recurrent episodes of excessive daytime sleepiness (hypersomnolence) and inc...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Modafinil",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8897338403041825,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7610756006171479,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024054,
      "question_number": "76",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following is a primary sleep-related movement disorder commonly exacerbated during preg...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Restless Legs Syndrome (RLS)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6976744186046512,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5147639646417153,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024055,
      "question_number": "67",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q67. A patient came with symptoms of restlessness during nighttime, improving when she rubs her feet...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Check iron stores/level"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024056,
      "question_number": "68",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient with a history of visual hallucinations and inability to move from the bed, along with fre...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Narcolepsy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8105726872246696,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3698889151500827,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024057,
      "question_number": "29",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "A 43-year-old man presents with complaints of unrefreshing sleep, excessive daytime sleepiness, and ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Polysomnogram"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024058,
      "question_number": "17",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient has difficulty sleeping and is lying in bed looking at the clock. What is the next best tr...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "C. Zolpidem",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.73224043715847,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.783369131635471,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024059,
      "question_number": "51",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "Which of the following conditions, among primary sleep-related movement disorders, is known to be ex...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024060,
      "question_number": "73",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "A child presents with a history of falling and loss of tone usually after laughing. What is the most...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Cataplexy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7733333333333333,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6058310578701664,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024061,
      "question_number": "36",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q36. With destruction of the anterior hypothalamic nucleus, you will find:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Insomnia and hyperthermia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024062,
      "question_number": "30",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q30. Focuses on the management principles of insomnia, potentially secondary to depression.",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024063,
      "question_number": "75",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "Pregnancy is a risk factor for which of the following conditions?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Restless legs syndrome (RLS)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024064,
      "question_number": "31",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old male presents with poor sleeping and recent mood changes, with early awakening as repo...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Increased cortisol levels in the night",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6445916114790287,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6871591472483887,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024065,
      "question_number": "32",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old male is experiencing poor sleep and recent mood changes, with early awakening as repor...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Pharmacotherapy and hypnotic measures have good effects."
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024066,
      "question_number": "72",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient is sleeping and exhibits aggressive movements in the legs while sleeping, and he used to w...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Parasomnia"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024067,
      "question_number": "31",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "Tests knowledge of potential biological/neurophysiological correlates of insomnia/depression.",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Decreased slow-wave sleep (SWS)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024068,
      "question_number": "289",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient with narcolepsy is treated with which of the following medications?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Modafinil"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024069,
      "question_number": "362",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient is sleeping all day and binge eating with increased weight. What medication would you cons...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Methylphenidate",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7773584905660378,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7734171725932351,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024070,
      "question_number": "33",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old male with poor sleeping and recent mood changes, early awakening reported by his wife....",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "A. Diffuse low glucose uptake in PET scan",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.6065573770491803,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.34285714285714286,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024071,
      "question_number": "127",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "A woman presents with her husband, who complains of her uncomfortable sensations in the legs at nigh...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Pregnancy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024072,
      "question_number": "124",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "Pregnancy is a risk factor for which of the following conditions?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Restless legs syndrome (RLS)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5663716814159292,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6354188759278897,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024073,
      "question_number": "124",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "Q124. Pregnancy is a risk factor for which of the following conditions?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Restless legs syndrome (RLS)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5541125541125541,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.08107284364523011,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024074,
      "question_number": "258",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "What is the sleep disorder associated with Parkinson's disease?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. REM sleep behavior disorder",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.5486725663716814,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.260272648167843,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100024075,
      "question_number": "51",
      "subspecialty": "Sleep Neurology",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with excessive daytime sleepiness and increased eating habits. What is the first-...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "B. Methylphenidate",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7847222222222222,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7799419809365935,
      "match_method": "question_number"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022892,
      "question_number": "68",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q68. In a case scenario of a patient with acute onset weakness and loss of pain and temperature sens...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Spinal cord infarction",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7595505617977528,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6703253002465601,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022893,
      "question_number": "48",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A CT brain scan shows right PICA territory infarction. What finding would you expect on examination?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022894,
      "question_number": "273",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 73-year-old female patient presented with decreased level of consciousness showing hemorrhage with...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Anticoagulation use",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7209876543209877,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7587637009973338,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022895,
      "question_number": "124",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of a patient with left eye amaurosis fugax and transient dysarthria, what is your...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022896,
      "question_number": "62",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In the same case scenario [likely related to Q68, spinal cord infarction], what investigation should...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. MRI",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7730496453900709,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.696828604058684,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022897,
      "question_number": "269",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A similar case presents with left frontal focal hyperintensity mainly subcortical, with cortical dif...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Cerebral venous thrombosis (CVT)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022898,
      "question_number": "95",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with an inability to read his own handwriting, while his comprehension for spoke...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Posterior cerebral artery (PCA)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7176470588235294,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.674504041146216,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022899,
      "question_number": "279",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "For the same patient (referring to Q273, intracerebral hemorrhage with a fluid level on CT), what is...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Surgery",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7554179566563467,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6696222734527398,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022900,
      "question_number": "15",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient two weeks postpartum presents with a headache and left-sided weakness. MRI shows a right c...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Cerebral venous thrombosis (CVT)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7404426559356136,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.614826498422713,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022901,
      "question_number": "170",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with a transient ischemic attack (TIA) is found to have atrial flutter, but the echocardio...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Factor X inhibitor",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7397959183673469,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6985708913125235,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022902,
      "question_number": "251",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An acute ischemic stroke (AIS) patient within the therapeutic window with a platelet count of 45,000...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Platelet count 45,000",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8043875685557587,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2734904746528899,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022903,
      "question_number": "66",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with Horner\u2019s syndrome (ptosis, miosis) presents with a thunderclap headache. A CT brain a...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Internal Carotid Artery (ICA) dissection",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7185185185185186,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5698343504795118,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022904,
      "question_number": "168",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with subarachnoid hemorrhage. Which artery is most likely affected?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022905,
      "question_number": "157",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An 83-year-old man presents with a 3-hour history of acute onset hemiparesis and aphasia consistent ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. tPA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022906,
      "question_number": "24",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q24. A patient underwent carotid endarterectomy due to severe symptomatic stenosis and the next day ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Hyperperfusion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7885714285714286,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7134300852338171,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022907,
      "question_number": "45",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a patient post motor vehicle accident (MVA) presenting with symptoms of lateral medullary syndrom...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Vertebral artery thrombosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7320954907161804,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.49496950011883073,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022908,
      "question_number": "40",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q40. Which of the following is a common neurologic deficit associated with AICA (Anterior Inferior C...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Unilateral hearing loss",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7739938080495357,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5218378936499742,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022909,
      "question_number": "122",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a case of subacute stroke with a CT brain showing no abnormalities, a normal transthoracic echoca...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Prolonged cardiac monitoring",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8017057569296375,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4119420989143546,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022910,
      "question_number": "9",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q9. A patient presented with hemianopia and alexia without agraphia. What is the likely location of ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "C. Angular",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7248322147651006,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5303731695795938,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022911,
      "question_number": "239",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a patient with CADASIL, what is the role of aspirin in secondary prevention?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022912,
      "question_number": "49",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A case scenario of a post-RTA patient presents with brain stem symptoms and findings. What is the mo...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022913,
      "question_number": "74",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A postpartum woman presents with a sudden, severe (\u201cthunderclap\u201d) headache and focal weakness two we...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. RCVS"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022914,
      "question_number": "272",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A young lady with SLE nephritis on dialysis presents with seizures and confusion. MRI shows venous t...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022915,
      "question_number": "99",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of superior cerebellar artery (SCA) infarction, what additional finding would you expe...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022916,
      "question_number": "85",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with Sickle Cell Anemia presents with symptoms of infarction and is found to have severe i...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022917,
      "question_number": "144",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A young female postpartum presents with headache associated with new onset generalized tonic-clonic ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CT venogram",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8407643312101911,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7830172847793254,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022918,
      "question_number": "131",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with an acute stroke has a CT image with no established stroke ASPECT score of 8. After be...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Send him for a CT scan"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022919,
      "question_number": "278",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with a stroke and fibromuscular dysplasia is being evaluated. What is the next step in man...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022920,
      "question_number": "68",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An MRI shows dissection. What is the recommended management?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022921,
      "question_number": "20",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A brain CT shows right SCA territory infarction at the level of the midbrain. Which artery is affect...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. SCA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8178137651821862,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7928176795580111,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022922,
      "question_number": "181",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A male with progressive myelopathy has an attached image clearly showing slow voiding and long cord ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Dural arteriovenous fistula (DAVF)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022923,
      "question_number": "296",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q296. What are the effects caused by SCA? [Referring to Superior Cerebellar Artery infarction]",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022924,
      "question_number": "172",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What can you see with reversible cerebral vasoconstriction syndrome (RCVS)?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022925,
      "question_number": "132",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a patient with a hemorrhagic stroke, what is the recommended blood pressure target?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. 140/90",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7850467289719626,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.35696329813976874,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022926,
      "question_number": "37",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q37. A case scenario about an acute ischemic stroke occurred in the morning, and the patient present...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. No management",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8445378151260504,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6156159919789447,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022927,
      "question_number": "252",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Patient had mild trauma as he cannot see the left side of the road. Presented with visual deficit an...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Vertebral Dissection",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.843010752688172,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.715150451794017,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022928,
      "question_number": "227",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A female patient taking oral contraceptive pills (OCP) had a cerebral venous thrombosis (CVT), and t...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. 3\u20136 months",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8676470588235294,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7588468369995901,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022929,
      "question_number": "149",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of acute ischemic stroke, the patient was started on tPA. Thirty minutes later, he dev...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Brain CT",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8370927318295739,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.560958904109589,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022930,
      "question_number": "64",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with transient lower extremity weakness that worsens upon coughing or during Vals...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Dural arteriovenous fistula (AVF)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7450110864745011,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.47404031051919376,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022931,
      "question_number": "286",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with multiple hemorrhages in the brain was on aspirin; his lips showed petechiae (mucocuta...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022932,
      "question_number": "161",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a young female with a small PFO and atrial fibrillation who developed a stroke, what is the recom...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "B. Warfarin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.782312925170068,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4928131416837782,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022933,
      "question_number": "25",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Locked-in syndrome is associated with infarction of which part of the brain?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022934,
      "question_number": "290",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What is the first cellular change in stroke?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022935,
      "question_number": "31",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a case of posterior reversible encephalopathy syndrome (PRES) with MRI findings, what is the unde...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Autoregulation failure"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022936,
      "question_number": "271",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q271. Which of the following is the correct mechanism of action of these medications?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022937,
      "question_number": "175",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient starts seeing animals and then has decreased level of consciousness and decerebrate postur...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CTA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8786407766990292,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6190649666059502,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022938,
      "question_number": "123",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with polycystic kidney disease presents with a history suggestive of subarachnoid hemorrha...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022939,
      "question_number": "79",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a scenario about CADASIL, which of the following is the correct answer? [Question context missing...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CADASIL",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7283582089552239,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7634926091440357,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022940,
      "question_number": "77",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a scenario about Wernicke's aphasia, which artery is typically affected?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022941,
      "question_number": "86",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q86. Exchange transfusion [Likely the answer to Q85 regarding Sickle Cell/MCA stenosis management]",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022942,
      "question_number": "116",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with acute-onset right face, arm, and leg weakness accompanied by mild articulat...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Internal capsule",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8388625592417062,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7587168758716876,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022943,
      "question_number": "281",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with Horner's syndrome and a left deviated uvula. What other finding would you ex...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022944,
      "question_number": "280",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Another patient came with a stroke; CT showed watershed infarction; what is the next step?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. CTA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022945,
      "question_number": "162",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Which imaging technique is used to assess watershed infarction?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. MRI",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7607361963190185,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7227057945784631,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022946,
      "question_number": "250",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old male patient with a traumatic brain injury 5 days ago, intubated, and with respiratory...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Nimodipine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8710801393728222,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.689592554761094,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022947,
      "question_number": "182",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with an acute ischemic stroke treated with tPA develops tongue angioedema and remains hemo...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Steroid with antihistamine"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022948,
      "question_number": "100",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a patient with an anterior communicating artery (A.Com) aneurysm, which of the following factors ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Size of the aneurysm",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7219251336898396,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2484175325450854,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022949,
      "question_number": "75",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Stenting",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022950,
      "question_number": "129",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a sudden, severe \u201cthunderclap\u201d headache. On examination, the right pupil is ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Posterior communicating artery",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7509727626459144,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7922751729438893,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022951,
      "question_number": "154",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A middle-aged male presents with right hemiplegia and is found to have atrial fibrillation. What is ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Warfarin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022952,
      "question_number": "90",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with sickle cell anemia is concerned about his risk of stroke due to a family history. Wha...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Transcranial Doppler",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8068459657701712,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.28378947368421054,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022953,
      "question_number": "246",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In the case of a 60-year-old male patient with a 3.5-hour history of sudden left-sided flaccid weakn...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Platelet count of 45,000",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8783068783068783,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6018974420559625,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022954,
      "question_number": "105",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q105. A 35-year-old patient with Moyamoya syndrome presents with a history of an ischemic stroke in ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Revascularization surgery"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022955,
      "question_number": "142",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 54-year-old male, a known smoker, is admitted with stroke with right-sided weakness and facial asy...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. ICA endarterectomy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8505747126436781,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5111589136864748,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022956,
      "question_number": "87",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with a large left internal carotid artery (ICA) territory infarction, as shown in the CT i...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Dabigatran",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8329621380846325,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.634874408445577,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022957,
      "question_number": "92",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A woman presented with acute left-sided weakness and dysarthria. A right intracerebral hemorrhage (I...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Labetalol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7284768211920529,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.23280516951403027,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022958,
      "question_number": "152",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A female patient with end\u2010stage renal disease (ESRD) on regular hemodialysis complains of recurrent ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. CT angiography"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022959,
      "question_number": "284",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with subarachnoid hemorrhage (SAH) has hyponatremia; what will you do?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022960,
      "question_number": "203",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 60-year-old male presents with chronic fluctuating paraparesis. Which of the following is the most...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. DAVF",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7864406779661017,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7355907016240314,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022961,
      "question_number": "176",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An 82-year-old female with a stroke has an NIHSS score of 20, blood pressure of 180/100, and present...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Thrombolysis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8622950819672132,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.49287843656840014,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022962,
      "question_number": "73",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Hemianopia refers to loss of half the visual field in both eyes on the same side, often due to lesio...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Posterior cerebral artery (PCA) stroke"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022963,
      "question_number": "242",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q242. What is the management for a patient with a history of ischemic stroke who is contraindicated ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022964,
      "question_number": "235",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q235. In the scenario of a 65-year-old male with a history of diabetes and hypertension who presents...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. High",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8967136150234741,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6915887850467289,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022965,
      "question_number": "108",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with weakness, and an MRI of the brain showed ischemic infarction in the superio...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022966,
      "question_number": "138",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old female patient with hypertension and esophageal symptoms (suggesting systemic sclerosi...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Intracerebral hemorrhage",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7987897125567323,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7870785583790068,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022967,
      "question_number": "43",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a patient with a hemorrhagic stroke and an INR of 3.1, what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022968,
      "question_number": "57",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with stroke syndrome findings suggestive of lateral pons involvement and has a he...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. AICA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9034090909090909,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4420947630922693,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022969,
      "question_number": "151",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An elderly male presented to the ER with right-sided weakness and aphasia. Examination showed BP 220...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CT brain",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8273244781783681,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7469615945551774,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022970,
      "question_number": "165",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In the context of carotid dissection, which statement is true regarding tongue deviation?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022971,
      "question_number": "285",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 60-year-old patient came to the ER with left-sided weakness, decreased proprioception on the left,...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Right vertebral artery"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022972,
      "question_number": "266",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with left MCA occlusion within 3.5 hours from symptom onset and has a history of ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "C. DAPT",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8693333333333333,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7788187372708758,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022973,
      "question_number": "96",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a scenario of acute stroke with a normal non-contrast CT scan, what is the next step if intraveno...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022974,
      "question_number": "36",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Which neurologic deficit is most commonly associated with SCA (Superior Cerebellar Artery) infarctio...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Ataxia (gait or truncal instability)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7122302158273381,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7276061776061776,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022975,
      "question_number": "26",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a case of lateral pontine syndrome with a hint of hearing loss, which artery is most likely invol...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022976,
      "question_number": "72",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with weakness, hemianesthesia, and tongue deviation. Which artery is most likely ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Anterior spinal artery",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7416267942583732,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6641112363773017,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022977,
      "question_number": "54",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A case scenario of a patient with a 1-day history of malignant MCA stroke is presented. The CT brain...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Hemicraniectomy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8235294117647058,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7806116281880817,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022978,
      "question_number": "229",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with CADASIL is being considered for prophylaxis against stroke. Which of the following is...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Smoking cessation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7758620689655172,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5048948513415519,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022979,
      "question_number": "126",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient experiences symptoms of a transient ischemic attack (TIA) for 10 minutes. Both echocardiog...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Neck CTA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022980,
      "question_number": "39",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with a small left internal capsule infarction and right-sided weakness for 2 days is found...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Aspirin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8614718614718615,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2603978300180832,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022981,
      "question_number": "153",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What is the management for a patient who developed angioedema after starting tPA?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022982,
      "question_number": "295",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a sickle cell patient with multiple previous strokes, what is the most important preventive treat...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Chronic transfusion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7410071942446043,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5604038137969714,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022983,
      "question_number": "202",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A young female presents with a case about cerebral venous thrombosis (CVT). What is a possible risk ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Ulcerative Colitis (UC)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022984,
      "question_number": "240",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q240. Why is tPA contraindicated in patients who have had a stroke within the last 3 months?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022985,
      "question_number": "137",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q137. A 68-year-old man awoke with slurred speech and left-sided weakness. Noncontrast head CT shows...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. IV Labetalol",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8774002954209749,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6111241492607369,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022986,
      "question_number": "191",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 50-year-old developed progressive symptoms starting with sensory loss in the left lower limb, whic...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Dural venous fistula",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8956043956043956,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5188966116420504,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022987,
      "question_number": "220",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q220. A patient with acute stroke on dabigatran for atrial fibrillation underwent thrombectomy and d...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Idarucizumab"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022988,
      "question_number": "238",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A young male patient presents with third nerve palsy. What is the most likely diagnosis based on the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022989,
      "question_number": "4",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A lady on oral contraceptive pills (OCP) presents with seizures and headaches, with a CT scan showin...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. CT venography (CTV)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022990,
      "question_number": "30",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q30. A 74-year-old male presents with a CT brain image showing a large hemorrhage in the cortex. Wha...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. CTA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022991,
      "question_number": "141",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 36-year-old male sustained a motor vehicle accident and presented with acute blurred vision. Exami...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Artery-to-artery embolism"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022992,
      "question_number": "236",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient presents with temporal pain, jaw claudication, and visual symptoms, along with a ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "C. Prednisone",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7790055248618785,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5804155444401693,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022993,
      "question_number": "234",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A young lady with two miscarriages and livedo reticularis is being evaluated. What laboratory test s...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022994,
      "question_number": "136",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 61-year-old female presented with sudden severe headache, worsened with double vision. Examination...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Posterior communicating artery",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7269155206286837,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7582946390882229,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022995,
      "question_number": "226",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What is the first-line treatment for warfarin-related intracerebral hemorrhage (ICH) to achieve rapi...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022996,
      "question_number": "222",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 70-year-old male patient with a patent foramen ovale (PFO), diabetes mellitus (DM), hypertension (...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Aspirin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8402777777777778,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7240265566122376,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022997,
      "question_number": "34",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A brain MRI shows unilateral watershed infarction. What is the likely mechanism?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022998,
      "question_number": "31",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A lady with a two-day history of malignant left middle cerebral artery (MCA) stroke and midline shif...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Craniectomy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7739130434782608,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6680056710775047,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100022999,
      "question_number": "63",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "For patients with intracerebral hemorrhage (ICH) whose INR is elevated because of vitamin K antagoni...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023000,
      "question_number": "244",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q244. An elderly patient presented to the ER with a history of visual disturbances. On examination, ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Splenium of the corpus callosum",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8111888111888111,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5211436397877076,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023001,
      "question_number": "294",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A case of right ICA dissection presented with left-sided weakness. What is the treatment in the acut...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Medical therapy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023002,
      "question_number": "147",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An 82-year-old female with a history of diabetes, hypertension, and dyslipidemia presents with sudde...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. 30 minutes",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8912655971479501,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7320421671978427,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023003,
      "question_number": "171",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q171. What is an expected finding in a patient with a superior cerebellar artery (SCA) infarction?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023004,
      "question_number": "276",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with acute right-sided weakness. Noncontrast CT head demonstrates a left basal ga...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Craniotomy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8148148148148148,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.2136255611301822,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023005,
      "question_number": "42",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A scenario of an 82-year-old lady with ischemic stroke presented within 1 hour and has no contraindi...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. tPA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7943661971830986,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.788508677321306,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023006,
      "question_number": "225",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What is the mechanism of the following antiplatelet agent: Ticagrelor?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023007,
      "question_number": "32",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q32. A patient presents with an intracranial bleed. What is the recommended blood pressure managemen...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. 140/90",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8148148148148148,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.1241943090709008,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023008,
      "question_number": "230",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 64-year-old diabetic patient presents with unilateral weakness that lasted 25 minutes and then ful...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023009,
      "question_number": "118",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with an acute stroke in the left occipital lobe will exhibit which of the following in the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023010,
      "question_number": "28",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A case scenario of a lady in the postpartum period presented with headache and seizure, with a norma...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CTV",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8663101604278075,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4833171363783609,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023011,
      "question_number": "180",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A case of malignant MCA stroke with mass effect and decreased level of consciousness is found unresp...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Decompressive hemicraniectomy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7341772151898734,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5783623942082187,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023012,
      "question_number": "98",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q98. An image of diffusion-weighted imaging (DWI) shows a watershed infarction on one side. What sho...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023013,
      "question_number": "167",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In the context of acute ischemic stroke, which visual field defect is commonly observed?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023014,
      "question_number": "274",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with cardioembolic stroke, ECG showed atrial fibrillation, and echocardiogram indicated no...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Factor X inhibitor",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8181818181818182,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7760267430754537,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023015,
      "question_number": "169",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a small right thalamic hemorrhage and normal blood pressure. What is the nex...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023016,
      "question_number": "52",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a case of intracerebral hemorrhage (ICH), what is the target blood pressure (BP) for treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. 140/90",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8034934497816594,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.022358346094946403,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023017,
      "question_number": "207",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient was playing tennis and was brought to the emergency room after a car accident. Initially, ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Reversible cerebral vasoconstriction syndrome (RCVS)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023018,
      "question_number": "224",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with acute stroke is on warfarin and has a CT scan showing intracerebral hemorrhage (ICH) ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Vitamin K",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.83399209486166,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.768056968463886,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023019,
      "question_number": "283",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A stroke patient has livedo reticularis. What is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023020,
      "question_number": "61",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient came with left side weakness; CT showed right semiovale hypodensity; what is the next step...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CTA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7424242424242424,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.06092801387684302,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023021,
      "question_number": "119",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with an acute stroke has a brain MRI that shows a dorsal cerebellar infarction (superior c...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "B. Ipsilateral Horner\u2019s syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7198067632850241,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7913112303227509,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023022,
      "question_number": "59",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of an acute ischemic stroke patient, what is a contraindication for administering...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023023,
      "question_number": "53",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A case scenario of a patient with a history of diabetes mellitus and cardiac risk factors on aspirin...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Medical management",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8126410835214447,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6536181635163852,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023024,
      "question_number": "115",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient on warfarin developed acute focal weakness. A noncontrast CT brain scan shows an intracere...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Coagulopathy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7751937984496124,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6145963793692361,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023025,
      "question_number": "288",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A stroke patient with an NIHSS score of 3. What is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023026,
      "question_number": "70",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q70. A patient diagnosed with acute ischemic stroke underwent workup, and her vessel imaging showed ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Embolism",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9083333333333333,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.1069588835815304,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023027,
      "question_number": "219",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a case about a young patient with malignant middle cerebral artery (MCA) stroke, what is the next...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023028,
      "question_number": "173",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a picture showing a fluid level hemorrhage. What is the mechanism of this he...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023029,
      "question_number": "71",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q71. A man who developed acute vertigo and dysphagia along with left side ataxia on examination had ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Right ptosis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6136097903188089,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023030,
      "question_number": "23",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a case of stroke with intracranial stenosis, what is the recommended management?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. DAPT",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7605633802816901,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5953917050691244,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023031,
      "question_number": "146",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q146. What clinical features are seen in a patient with superior cerebellar artery infarction?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Impaired finger-nose test"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023032,
      "question_number": "150",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A lady in her 30s was presented to the ER with a history of headache and neck pain that started afte...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Aspirin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023033,
      "question_number": "22",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A brain MRI shows unilateral watershed infarction. What should be ordered?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CTA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7236180904522613,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.501737317581654,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023034,
      "question_number": "282",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "The same patient is now asking what treatment you will give. What will you prescribe?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023035,
      "question_number": "97",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q97. What are the CSF findings in RCVS?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023036,
      "question_number": "204",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A stroke patient presented within the treatment window with a normal brain CT and CTA. The NIHSS sco...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023037,
      "question_number": "140",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Foville Syndrome is characterized by lesions involving the dorsal pontine tegmentum in the caudal re...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Supportive care and rehabilitation"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023038,
      "question_number": "56",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 50-year-old patient, a heavy smoker and hypertensive on medication, presents with a history of lef...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. CTA neck",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8444444444444444,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7853587722936541,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023039,
      "question_number": "228",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A case scenario of a patient who came with a left PICA territory infarction is presented. What is th...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023040,
      "question_number": "91",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q91. A common question scenario about progressive symptoms of a spinal fistula with attached MRI for...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. DAVF"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023041,
      "question_number": "158",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 50-year-old patient presents with transient right-sided weakness. The diagnosis is TIA, with right...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. Angio & stenting"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023042,
      "question_number": "231",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a patient presenting with high blood pressure and headache, what is the most likely diagnosis bas...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. PRES",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8373702422145328,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6145041288529147,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023043,
      "question_number": "65",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a CT brain showing a unilateral occipital stroke. Which artery is most likel...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. PCA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8685258964143426,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.47311616954474095,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023044,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 22-year-old female, medically free and on combined oral contraceptives, presents with headaches. A...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023045,
      "question_number": "81",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A female who develops transverse sinus thrombosis: what is the most accurate statement to describe t...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023046,
      "question_number": "127",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q127. (Source: Part I 2018mcqs.txt) Based on the MRI findings, what is your diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023047,
      "question_number": "27",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with tongue deviation to the left side and ptosis in his left upper eyelid. What ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023048,
      "question_number": "233",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A picture of an MRA shows a floating thrombus. What is the next step in management?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023049,
      "question_number": "133",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 62-year-old male presented with acute onset nausea and vomiting. He is diabetic and hypertensive. ...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Posterior inferior cerebellar artery"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023050,
      "question_number": "277",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient came with left side weakness; CT showed right semiovale hypodensity; what is the next step...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CTA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7424242424242424,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7207168764668231,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023051,
      "question_number": "110",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with 6 hours of right-sided weakness affecting the arm, leg, and face, along with...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. DAPT",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8612836438923396,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5719814241486069,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023052,
      "question_number": "94",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a scenario for giant cell arteritis (GCA), what is the most likely mechanism or artery involved?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023053,
      "question_number": "128",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a case of an acute stroke, the patient exhibits left gaze preference and cannot look to the right...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023054,
      "question_number": "88",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q88. A scenario of lateral medullary syndrome shows PICA involvement. What is the significance of th...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023055,
      "question_number": "248",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q248. A 70-year-old female patient with a history of diabetes mellitus, hypertension, and a previous...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Initiate intravenous thrombolysis with tPA after confirming no contraindications",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7300970873786408,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6701254826254827,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023056,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario of alexia without agraphia, what artery is involved?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023057,
      "question_number": "55",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A woman after a successful vaginal delivery complains of severe headache and hemiparesis. Her exam s...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CTV",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8531073446327684,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.793841668944156,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023058,
      "question_number": "101",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q101. Which factors increase the risk for aneurysm formation?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023059,
      "question_number": "148",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q148. In a long case scenario, a patient admitted to the stroke unit is diabetic, hypertensive, and ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Vascular",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8599605522682445,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.46516347237880495,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023060,
      "question_number": "60",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario, a patient initially has a high NIH Stroke Scale Score (NIHSS) that drops to 6 bu...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Give t-PA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7581967213114754,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6097026054917098,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023061,
      "question_number": "121",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 50-year-old male patient with a history of diabetes mellitus, hypertension, and smoking presents w...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Lenticulostriate arteries",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8033826638477801,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7787508420748724,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023062,
      "question_number": "160",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q160. (Source: Part II 2019mcqs.txt) Acute paraparesis after major repair of the aorta can be devast...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. T4",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9169054441260746,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7461447212336892,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023063,
      "question_number": "61",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a 1-day history of ischemic stroke and a high blood pressure (SBP 190). The ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023064,
      "question_number": "291",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a case of acute ischemic stroke presenting within the intravenous thrombolysis window with an NIH...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. TPA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8119891008174387,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5200549793827315,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023065,
      "question_number": "218",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a case scenario about Lateral Medullary Syndrome, what is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023066,
      "question_number": "125",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q125. A 70-something female with diabetes mellitus and hypertension, fully independent, presents wit...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. IV tPA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8418156808803301,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7772664026543936,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023067,
      "question_number": "185",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Which of the following best describes the evidence for the use of decompressive craniectomy in the m...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023068,
      "question_number": "155",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient was not able to read his handwriting. Which artery is most likely involved in this conditi...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "B. MCA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8632478632478633,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3068057625434675,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023069,
      "question_number": "44",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q44. A brain CT shows a large right subdural hematoma. What is the mechanism of this condition?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023070,
      "question_number": "237",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q237. (Source: Promotion 2021mcqs.txt) An 80-year-old man with a history of diabetes and hypertensio...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. IV tPA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8492201039861352,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7550482879719052,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023071,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a patient with acute stroke who was treated with tPA and subsequently vomited, leading to letharg...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Send him for a CT scan"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023072,
      "question_number": "47",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q47. A patient came with a CT brain scan attached. Which artery is most likely involved in the case ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023073,
      "question_number": "120",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with stroke is receiving physiotherapy and speech therapy. What is the type of prevention ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Tertiary",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8111888111888111,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6447736454988087,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023074,
      "question_number": "93",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q93. In the management of a transient ischemic attack (TIA), what is the recommended treatment?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023075,
      "question_number": "139",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 59-year-old male with a history of diabetes, hypertension, and dyslipidemia presented with sudden ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Neck CT angiography"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023076,
      "question_number": "232",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient had an embolic stroke. What is the next step in management?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. ECHO",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7450980392156863,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6787192700853256,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023077,
      "question_number": "76",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q76. (Source: Part 2 2020 copymcqs.txt) What is the site of the lesion in Weber syndrome?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Base of midbrain",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.75,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7965128641292791,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023078,
      "question_number": "67",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q67. What is the recommendation for patients with ICH presenting with systolic blood pressure (SBP) ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023079,
      "question_number": "275",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with an Acom aneurysm, what is the most important risk factor for rupture?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Size",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7008547008547008,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.14497905293893615,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023080,
      "question_number": "293",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a case of livedo reticularis and strokes in the MCA territory, what is the diagnosis to rule out ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023081,
      "question_number": "84",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a scenario regarding cerebral venous thrombosis (CVT), what will confirm the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CTV",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7818181818181819,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6695325094035465,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023082,
      "question_number": "221",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q221. A patient with acute ischemic stroke on dabigatran for atrial fibrillation underwent mechanica...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Idarucizumab"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023083,
      "question_number": "159",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An 82-year-old patient, medically free, presents with acute right-sided weakness and global aphasia ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. IV thrombolytic",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8483754512635379,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.13111587982832618,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023084,
      "question_number": "223",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with perimesencephalic subarachnoid hemorrhage (SAH) has undergone two normal angiograms. ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023085,
      "question_number": "184",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q184. A stroke patient presented within the treatment window with a glucose level of 300, platelet c...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Platelet count",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8280254777070064,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5803151783245784,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023086,
      "question_number": "134",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Scenario of a patient with symptomatic ICA stenosis. He underwent carotid endarterectomy, and a few ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Hyperperfusion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8058727569331158,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6106065045414591,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023087,
      "question_number": "102",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Which factors increase the risk for aneurysm rupture?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023088,
      "question_number": "243",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "This is a 24-year-old female patient with a known case of aneurysm, presenting with a history of rig...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Right PCOM",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9118541033434651,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7241150232513999,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023089,
      "question_number": "130",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 42-year-old female was found unconscious. A noncontrast CT scan of the head demonstrates hyperdens...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Aneurysmal hemorrhage",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.853448275862069,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7862969004893964,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023090,
      "question_number": "89",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A man has right-sided weakness and dysphasia. On stroke workup, he was found to have severe stenosis...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. Stenting",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8082191780821918,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5598657999580625,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023091,
      "question_number": "19",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q19. In patients with large acute MCA stroke and a history of atrial fibrillation, what is the recom...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Decompressive craniectomy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7586206896551724,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7403862023436211,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023092,
      "question_number": "204",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Post aortic surgery, a patient is awake with flaccid paraparesis and a sensory level at which of the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. T4",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8861788617886179,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.652232746955345,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023093,
      "question_number": "104",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q104. A stroke patient with an NIHSS score of 3 is being evaluated. What is the recommended treatmen...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. Aspirin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023094,
      "question_number": "245",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 62-year-old male patient with a history of diabetes mellitus for 12 years presented to the ER with...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. High risk 18%",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8819444444444444,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7873405457774907,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023095,
      "question_number": "143",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 65-year-old male with multiple cardiovascular risk factors and atrial fibrillation presents with a...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Craniotomy/decompression",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8669950738916257,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6109785202863962,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023096,
      "question_number": "101",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A female patient in her 30s presented to the ER with a history of progressive headache that started ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Anticoagulant",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8754716981132076,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7894488930758361,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023097,
      "question_number": "17",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 70-year-old male presents with an MRI showing changes. Which of the following is a potential cause...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Small Vessel Disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7631578947368421,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6701757516281559,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023098,
      "question_number": "177",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What is a common cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) finding in reversible cerebral vasoconstriction syndrome ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023099,
      "question_number": "7",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with infrequent headaches that are well controlled and has a family history of he...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Observation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8232558139534883,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.3956644858900498,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023100,
      "question_number": "77",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q77. A patient post-RTA has an image attached. Where is the localization of the lesion?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023101,
      "question_number": "52",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient has had a stroke and presents with slurred speech. You refer him to a speech therapist and...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Tertiary prevention"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023102,
      "question_number": "76",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A female patient came with ischemic stroke, a history of two previous abortions, and elevated prothr...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-phospholipid syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023103,
      "question_number": "63",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with a history of mild head trauma presents with left Horner\u2019s syndrome and tongue deviati...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Internal carotid",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8152492668621701,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7941846207742161,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023104,
      "question_number": "45",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A case presents typical of Fabry disease with a picture of angiokeratoma and two strokes. What is th...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Fabry disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7878787878787878,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6339949358817283,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023105,
      "question_number": "74",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 66-year-old male patient presented with dysarthria and right-sided weakness for 10 hours. A CT bra...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Aspirin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8640595903165735,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5155532891381948,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023106,
      "question_number": "43",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 60-year-old male has sudden cognitive decline and repetitive questioning. His memory for recent ev...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Brain CT"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023107,
      "question_number": "73",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with acute limb weakness and dysarthria. A CT brain was performed and was normal...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. ACE inhibitor",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.895152198421646,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6561464415338488,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023108,
      "question_number": "54",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with ataxia and vomiting. A CT scan shows hypodensity in the whole right cerebell...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. SCA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9050279329608939,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7748068924539513,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023109,
      "question_number": "75",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A female patient with end-stage renal disease (ESRD) on regular hemodialysis complained of recurrent...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. CT angiography"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023110,
      "question_number": "117",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 60-year-old female patient presents with left side weakness. Carotid Doppler shows right carotid s...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Left endarterectomy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7973273942093542,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6557267247153382,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023111,
      "question_number": "40",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 52-year-old male presents with cognitive decline and unsteady gait. A brain MRI shows extensive su...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. Vascular dementia",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7951219512195122,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7165306998711893,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023112,
      "question_number": "112",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a patient with acute ischemic stroke presenting within the IV tPA treatment window, which of the ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Glucose Level",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8486352357320099,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5438674360112443,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023113,
      "question_number": "244",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q244. A patient presents with symptoms of vertigo and ataxia over 1 day. A CT scan shows left cerebe...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Consult neurosurgery.",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8094218415417559,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5461748393344484,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023114,
      "question_number": "245",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with asymptomatic extracranial internal carotid artery (ICA) 60% stenosis, what is the bes...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023115,
      "question_number": "97",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 75-year-old female with diabetes mellitus and hypertension presents with acute right-sided weaknes...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Maximize medical management",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7890909090909091,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.24562268803945747,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023116,
      "question_number": "232",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with medial medullary syndrome: which artery is affected?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023117,
      "question_number": "47",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In the case of a cerebral venous thrombosis (CVT) after birth, what should be done?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023118,
      "question_number": "43",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a pregnant female patient with positive antiphospholipid antibodies who had a stroke and was foun...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Heparin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8687350835322196,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7428636936833658,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023119,
      "question_number": "239",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q239. A patient presents with recurrent thunderclap headache. A CTA shows a \"string of pearls\" appea...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Reversible cerebral vasoconstriction syndrome (RCVS)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7040358744394619,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6665155978548228,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023120,
      "question_number": "125",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A hypertensive and diabetic patient who underwent surgery for a bone fracture developed a stroke. In...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Physical stress",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8447937131630648,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6985539488320356,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023121,
      "question_number": "238",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with acute stroke received tPA and then developed intracerebral hemorrhage. What should be...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Cryoprecipitate",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7167235494880546,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7446524064171123,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023122,
      "question_number": "81",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with a past medical history of stroke underwent a full cardiac workup that was negative. H...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. C-ANCA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8007968127490039,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6538957134266815,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023123,
      "question_number": "316",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a patient with a stroke, what is the most appropriate management option?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023124,
      "question_number": "287",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a patient with sickle cell disease, what intervention is known to decrease the risk of future str...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Chronic transfusions",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7545787545787546,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4952019902855112,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023125,
      "question_number": "80",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "After 5 hours of labor, a patient on SSRIs presents with depression. What is the likely CT finding a...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023126,
      "question_number": "207",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What is the mechanism of stroke in arterial dissection?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023127,
      "question_number": "314",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Admission to stroke unit",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023128,
      "question_number": "211",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a case of acute ischemic stroke, the blood pressure is 193/103 mmHg. What should be done next?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023129,
      "question_number": "93",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A stroke patient presents with livedo reticularis. What is the diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023130,
      "question_number": "370",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A clear picture suggests perimesencephalic SAH. What is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023131,
      "question_number": "312",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with an aneurysm rupture of the posterior communicating artery (Pcom). What will ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Clipping",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.71280276816609,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6685878962536023,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023132,
      "question_number": "212",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In the ECST trial, what was the estimated 3-year stroke or death rate for patients who underwent car...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "D. 15.7%"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023133,
      "question_number": "355",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 60-year-old male patient with diabetes and hypertension came with a history of transient ischemic ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Dual antiplatelet therapy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023134,
      "question_number": "170",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 36-year-old female is referred to a neurology clinic with complaints of forgetfulness. She has chr...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. CADASIL",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9145569620253164,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.273258077072791,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023135,
      "question_number": "315",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with sickle cell disease comes with a stroke workup done and is found to have multiple ste...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Chronic transfusion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8418891170431212,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.37163416898792945,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023136,
      "question_number": "271",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An 82-year-old male patient came within 3 hours and has no contraindication for tPA. A CT scan shows...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. tPA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023137,
      "question_number": "273",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Angioplasty",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023138,
      "question_number": "488",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Which one is correct about antithrombotic medications?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023139,
      "question_number": "329",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A left ICA deep borderzone infarction is shown on DWI. What test would reveal the etiology?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023140,
      "question_number": "208",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Based on the following imaging, which territory is involved?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023141,
      "question_number": "446",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q446. A young female with right ICA dissection shows a crescent shape on MRA. What is the treatment?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023142,
      "question_number": "190",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 63-year-old male has acute bilateral lower limb weakness, lower back pain, and urinary incontinenc...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Spinal cord infarction (Anterior Spinal Artery Syndrome)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023143,
      "question_number": "406",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with a minor stroke (NIHSS 3) presents with decreased sensation on the left side and mild ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Dual antiplatelet therapy (DAPT)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023144,
      "question_number": "9",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with an intracranial bleed is being assessed for blood pressure management. What is the re...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. 140/90",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8482758620689655,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7997994233421085,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023145,
      "question_number": "286",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with end-stage renal disease (ESRD) presents with a right superficial borderzone infarctio...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Brain CT angiography (no neck CTA)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7110091743119266,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5035959725107879,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023146,
      "question_number": "266",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q266. What is the artery involved in a case of unconsciousness with CT brain findings?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "B. PCA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023147,
      "question_number": "210",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An 82-year-old woman presents with an acute ischemic stroke (onset 2 hours ago) and shows partial im...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Give IV tPA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7741935483870968,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7945863698246176,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023148,
      "question_number": "434",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "After all stroke workups are completed except for CTA, what is the next step?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023149,
      "question_number": "356",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Endarterectomy",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023150,
      "question_number": "479",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A male patient developed weakness and ptosis. A CTA image is attached. What is the most likely diagn...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. ICA dissection",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.75,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.41977710949938085,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023151,
      "question_number": "500",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A young male with internal carotid artery (ICA) occlusion is presented in a vessel image after a mot...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Dissection",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8603104212860311,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6821608040201005,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023152,
      "question_number": "191",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What is the direction of gaze deviation in a patient with hemispheric stroke?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023153,
      "question_number": "508",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 70-year-old female with diabetes and hypertension, who had an ischemic stroke 2 months ago, presen...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. IV thrombolysis and mechanical thrombectomy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7504244482173175,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7592805882874103,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023154,
      "question_number": "330",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old female presents with a sudden, severe headache, neck stiffness, and photophobia. A hea...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Endovascular coiling",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8637770897832817,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7696715049656226,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023155,
      "question_number": "311",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What is the mechanism of the patient's condition?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023156,
      "question_number": "317",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q317. Stent",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023157,
      "question_number": "107",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 60-year-old patient comes to the ER with left-sided weakness, decreased proprioception on the left...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Right vertebral artery",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7468671679197995,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5785843324026934,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023158,
      "question_number": "257",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q257. A 70-year-old male presents with a history of progressive lower limb weakness for months, asso...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Spinal dural fistula"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023159,
      "question_number": "284",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q284. A young patient presents with left hemiparesis and confusion. Imaging shows multiple FLAIR DWI...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Lactate pyruvate level"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023160,
      "question_number": "391",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What is the mechanism of injury in a patient who presented unconscious with a brain CT showing:",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023161,
      "question_number": "267",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What is the mechanism of the patient's condition?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023162,
      "question_number": "391",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q391. Requires identification and classification of the type of intracranial hemorrhage based on CT ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023163,
      "question_number": "369",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with severe stenosis of the intracranial MCA is being evaluated. What is the next step in ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023164,
      "question_number": "194",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What is the direction of gaze deviation in a patient with pontine stroke?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023165,
      "question_number": "171",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An elderly female presents with sudden onset persistent left gaze preference that cannot be overcome...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023166,
      "question_number": "310",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What is the mechanism of injury in a patient who presented unconscious with a brain CT showing a dee...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. Traumatic hemorrhage",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7847082494969819,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7688616810059563,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023167,
      "question_number": "169",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q169. A 45-year-old lady has sudden onset headache following neck manipulation, with right-sided wea...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Internal carotid artery dissection"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023168,
      "question_number": "88",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient developed an embolic stroke, and his routine workup is unremarkable. What should be done n...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023169,
      "question_number": "209",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q209. In a case of intracerebral hemorrhage (ICH) with midline shift greater than 10 mm and clinical...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Decompressive craniectomy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7531806615776081,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4757073170731707,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023170,
      "question_number": "94",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient has recurrent headaches and transient ischemic attacks (TIAs). Cerebral angiography shows ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. RCVS",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.794044665012407,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7750996737948532,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023171,
      "question_number": "89",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient has a right pontine stroke, his NIHSS was 8 and he was on aspirin prior to stroke onset. W...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Add clopidogrel to aspirin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023172,
      "question_number": "128",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Based on the following brain CT findings, what is the most likely diagnosis?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023173,
      "question_number": "70",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A female who just had an uneventful vaginal delivery one week ago presents with seizure and severe h...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. CT venogram",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.84375,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5413644486492168,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023174,
      "question_number": "69",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 70-year-old male came with an acute stroke and was given tPA in the ER. After 6 hours, he was asse...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Nicardipine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8755186721991701,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.11361998558731684,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023175,
      "question_number": "393",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q393. (Source: Part II 2022mcqs.txt) A patient suddenly explained to his wife that he is seeing anim...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. CTA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023176,
      "question_number": "68",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with a history of acute subarachnoid hemorrhage (SAH) and CT angiography showing a posteri...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Endovascular coiling",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7515400410677618,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.45315837656393043,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023177,
      "question_number": "127",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q127. The ACAS trial showed a reduction in the 5-year incidence of ipsilateral stroke or periprocedu...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "C. 70% to 99%",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8531073446327684,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.34502923976608185,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023178,
      "question_number": "96",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A young female developed severe headache and photophobia post-partum. What is the most appropriate n...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Brain CT Venography",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7289156626506024,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7090909090909091,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023179,
      "question_number": "95",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a patient with transient ischemic attack (TIA) and severe internal carotid artery (ICA) stenosis ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Carotid endarterectomy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7457627118644068,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6949006050129646,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023180,
      "question_number": "126",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In patients with blood pressure of 220/120 mmHg who did not receive IV alteplase or mechanical throm...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Lower blood pressure by 15% during the first 24 hours",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7018739352640545,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6720523570917272,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023181,
      "question_number": "124",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A picture of a spine MRI for a patient with progressive myelopathy is presented. What is the likely ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023182,
      "question_number": "125",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In patients with sickle cell disease and a history of ischemic stroke or TIA, what is the recommende...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023183,
      "question_number": "216",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A pregnant lady had a headache, and her CT showed an intracranial hemorrhage (ICH). What is the trea...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023184,
      "question_number": "176",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 62-year-old male patient with a history of diabetes mellitus presents to the ER with a left-sided ...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. High risk (18%)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8592870544090057,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.05381471389645776,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023185,
      "question_number": "87",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient developed ischemic stroke, and his echocardiogram showed a valvular hypokinesia lesion. Ho...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Warfarin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8360128617363344,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5590643274853802,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023186,
      "question_number": "209",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An MRI shows dissection. What is the recommended management?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023187,
      "question_number": "72",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with hypertension and diabetes mellitus, with a history of CABG, presents with bilateral l...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Treat his vascular risk factors",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.808,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.24478623566214808,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023188,
      "question_number": "86",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a scenario with a picture of an arteriovenous malformation (AVM), which of the following is a ris...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Previous history of bleeding"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023189,
      "question_number": "213",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with hypertension and diabetes mellitus, with a history of CABG, presents with bilateral l...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Treat his vascular risk factors",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.808,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.03766342809163968,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023190,
      "question_number": "57",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with right\u2010sided weakness; a noncontrast CT scan shows a left basal ganglia intra...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "A. Craniotomy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7614678899082569,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023191,
      "question_number": "55",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q55. A patient with an anterior communicating artery aneurysm, what is the most important risk facto...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Size",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7602739726027398,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6457891453524641,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023192,
      "question_number": "226",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An elderly man with diabetes mellitus, hypertension, and a history of coronary artery bypass graftin...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Vascular parkinsonism",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8212824010914052,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5341074020319303,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023193,
      "question_number": "46",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Another patient presented with acute stroke; noncontrast CT showed watershed infarction; what is the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. CTA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023194,
      "question_number": "103",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An elderly man with diabetes mellitus, hypertension, and a history of coronary artery bypass graftin...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Vascular parkinsonism"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023195,
      "question_number": "56",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with multiple hemorrhages in the brain was on aspirin; his lips showed petechiae. What sho...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023196,
      "question_number": "137",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with Parkinsonism restricted to the lower limbs with slowing and no tremor, respo...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Vascular Parkinson's disease",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7030878859857482,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7911565225050647,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023197,
      "question_number": "38",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with stroke and fibromuscular dysplasia is being evaluated. What is the next step in manag...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023198,
      "question_number": "20",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with left side weakness, and an MRI shows a right lacunar stroke. A CTA reveals s...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Dual Antiplatelet Therapy (DAPT)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8018867924528302,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.08500520136721652,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023199,
      "question_number": "20",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presented with acute limb weakness and dysarthria. A CT brain was performed and was normal...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Stop t-PA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023200,
      "question_number": "23",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 60-year-old male presented to the ER with a 2-day history of unilateral weakness and dysarthria. O...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Observation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8340080971659919,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5050429585356743,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023201,
      "question_number": "24",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A female patient presented with an ischemic stroke, a history of two previous abortions, and elevate...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Anti-phospholipid syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7146401985111662,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7476801830430914,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023202,
      "question_number": "214",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q214. An elderly patient with a history of diabetes mellitus, hypertension, and end-stage renal dise...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "A. CTA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9174917491749175,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.614828528607952,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023203,
      "question_number": "17",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old healthy woman presented with a 10-day history of severe headache, blurred vision, and ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. CT venogram",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8944881889763779,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6464319695528068,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023204,
      "question_number": "105",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A woman being investigated for stroke was found to have a high titer of anti-beta II glycoprotein an...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Warfarin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9327846364883402,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5956327282294133,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023205,
      "question_number": "55",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient who underwent carotid stenting or endarterectomy presents with altered level of consciousn...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Hyperperfusion syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7835051546391752,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7458937198067633,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023206,
      "question_number": "49",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What is the mainstay of treatment for patients with elevated INR due to vitamin K antagonists (VKAs)...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. PCC",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8067796610169492,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.43933348979112885,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023207,
      "question_number": "22",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An elderly male in his 60s with hypertension and diabetes mellitus presented with sudden onset right...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Mechanical thrombectomy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8339869281045752,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5052896197758459,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023208,
      "question_number": "190",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Which vitamin is known to decrease the risk of stroke in patients with homocysteinemia?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. B6",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8229665071770335,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7221563981042654,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023209,
      "question_number": "289",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Which of the following statements about spinal dural arteriovenous fistula is true?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023210,
      "question_number": "21",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 70-year-old male, known case of hypertension, went to sleep and then woke up in the morning with l...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Hypertensive hemorrhage",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.809437386569873,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7886035313001605,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023211,
      "question_number": "332",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q332. What is the diagnosis for a 40-year-old female, medically free, with a previous history of two...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Cerebral vasculitis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7739602169981917,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6075092774503383,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023212,
      "question_number": "193",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q193. A 75-year-old female with diabetes mellitus and hypertension presents with right-sided weaknes...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Maximize her medical treatment",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8473609129814551,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.27150105185001855,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023213,
      "question_number": "41",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A young female patient with subarachnoid hemorrhage (SAH) and a symptomatic posterior communicating ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "B. Coiling",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8564705882352941,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.722018636791959,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023214,
      "question_number": "352",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 50-year-old male presents with progressive lower limb weakness and a sensory level up to T10. Ther...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Dural arteriovenous fistula (AVF)"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023215,
      "question_number": "137",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An elderly patient with confusion, seizure, and weakness was brought to the emergency department. MR...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023216,
      "question_number": "187",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What is the first-line treatment for Reversible Cerebral Vasoconstriction Syndrome (RCVS)?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Nimodipine",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7665198237885462,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.601481203712384,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023217,
      "question_number": "215",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Homonymous hemianopia is most commonly associated with which artery?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023218,
      "question_number": "370",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with systemic lupus erythematosus and known antiphospholipid syndrome presents two days af...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Warfarin",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8451882845188284,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.748898678414097,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023219,
      "question_number": "194",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a patient with subarachnoid hemorrhage (SAH) and normal CTA and attached CT, what is the recommen...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Reassurance",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7449664429530202,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.46733086190917517,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023220,
      "question_number": "328",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What is the diagnosis for a 40-year-old female, medically free, with a previous history of two misca...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Cerebral vasculitis",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7697974217311234,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5091066782307025,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023221,
      "question_number": "192",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "MRI diffusion-weighted imaging shows multiple acute infarctions confined to one cerebral hemisphere....",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CTA",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.84375,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6395750988142292,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023222,
      "question_number": "295",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In the context of intracerebral hemorrhage (ICH), which statement is correct?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023223,
      "question_number": "56",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q56. A patient with SLE and antiphospholipid syndrome presented with a stroke 2 days ago. What shoul...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Warfarin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023224,
      "question_number": "333",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 30-year-old female presents with an 18-month history of back pain, progressive lower-limb weakness...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Dural venous fistula",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8827433628318584,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5197497432066486,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023225,
      "question_number": "370",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Which cranial nerve is primarily responsible for the sense of smell?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023226,
      "question_number": "152",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 45-year-old patient with a history of migraine 15 years ago developed a TIA. His father has a hist...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. NOTCH3 gene testing",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8109161793372319,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5675803850896329,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023227,
      "question_number": "104",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Based on the following brain MRI, what is the most likely mechanism of injury?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023228,
      "question_number": "95",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q95. The risk of stroke increases with which of the following conditions?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023229,
      "question_number": "50",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A girl with a history of migraine headaches, stroke, and dementia, along with a family history of si...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. CADASIL",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8436724565756824,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5001492982979994,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023230,
      "question_number": "128",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with recurrent epistaxis and telangiectasia over the skin, mucous membranes, retina, and g...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Annual MRI of the brain",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8104089219330854,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.42136498516320475,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023231,
      "question_number": "143",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A male patient with renal impairment, stroke, and angiokeratoma is being evaluated for enzyme supple...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Alpha-galactosidase A",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7387862796833773,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5235612205484743,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023232,
      "question_number": "249",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A young female with a history of stroke and recurrent abortions is evaluated. Which of the following...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "C. Antiphospholipid syndrome"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023233,
      "question_number": "67",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In the same scenario as the previous question, but with a CT angiogram not attached, what is the bes...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. IV tPA followed by mechanical thrombectomy",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7913043478260869,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6587278536160325,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023234,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 4-year-old sickle cell disease patient had a stroke with significant MCA stenosis. What will deter...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Transcranial Doppler",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7125748502994012,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7489092495636999,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023235,
      "question_number": "89",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What is a new recommendation for adults with acute ischemic stroke who have known sickle cell diseas...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023236,
      "question_number": "87",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 20-year-old male with a history of learning difficulty presented to the clinic with his father due...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. MELAS",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.9009708737864077,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7598000526177322,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023237,
      "question_number": "90",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "What was the aggregate risk reduction of stroke at 10 years for patients with 70% to 99% ICA stenosi...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "new_answer": "D. From 22.2% to 15.7%",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.744920993227991,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6576761247167979,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023238,
      "question_number": "187",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a case of malignant MCA infarction presented after 24 hours with midline shift, what is the most ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023239,
      "question_number": "25",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with sickle cell disease developed an ischemic stroke. What is the recommended secondary p...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Chronic blood transfusion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7289719626168224,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.21561456511369056,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023240,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient developed an ischemic stroke, and his echocardiogram showed an intracardiac thrombus as pa...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Warfarin"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023241,
      "question_number": "8",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q8. A patient presents with a skin rash (Angiokeratomas) and a family history of stroke. What is the...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Alpha-galactosidase A"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023242,
      "question_number": "159",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A case scenario of a patient with CADASIL presents with stroke, dementia, and migraine. What is the ...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023243,
      "question_number": "27",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with cardioembolic stroke, ECG showed atrial fibrillation, and echocardiogram indicated no...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Factor X inhibitor",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8181818181818182,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.05460526315789474,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023244,
      "question_number": "106",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a patient presenting with headache, what is the most likely diagnosis based on the MRI findings?",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. RCVS",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8049792531120332,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7221837088388214,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023245,
      "question_number": "27",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "According to the NASCET trial, what was the reduction in stroke rate at 18 months for patients with ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. From 26% to 9%",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8305084745762712,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.4309336046807428,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023246,
      "question_number": "20",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a patient with ischemic stroke, imaging shows bilateral anterior and posterior circulation stroke...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Prolonged cardiac monitoring"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023247,
      "question_number": "28",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q28. A patient presented with a chronic headache and no other neurological symptoms, found to have a...",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023248,
      "question_number": "107",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a headache and recurrent thunderclap headaches, with normal MRI and MRV. Wha...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. RCVS",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7760252365930599,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5482480794453813,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023249,
      "question_number": "30",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 4-year-old sickle cell disease patient had a stroke with significant MCA stenosis. What will deter...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Transcranial Doppler",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7125748502994012,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.06390296886314265,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023250,
      "question_number": "71",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient had head trauma and developed spontaneous perimesencephalic subarachnoid hemorrhage (SAH) ...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Send him home with follow-up in the clinic",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7891156462585034,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.32941783916354717,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023251,
      "question_number": "35",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient who underwent revascularization for severe external carotid stenosis is found confused one...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Hyperperfusion",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8253968253968254,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6803236710027656,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023252,
      "question_number": "15",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Q15. A 30-year-old male presents to the emergency room with a coital headache (very severe). The hea...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. CT scan of the head"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023253,
      "question_number": "39",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An 82-year-old female with good functional status, although she has mild osteoporosis in her knees r...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Blood pressure management",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.8862115127175368,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.48405386250885896,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023254,
      "question_number": "25",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 73-year-old female patient presented with decreased level of consciousness showing hemorrhage with...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Anticoagulation use",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7209876543209877,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.02465176871430003,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023255,
      "question_number": "71",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A young patient presented with acute severe headache associated with nausea and vomiting. He was rec...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. Reversible cerebral vasoconstriction syndrome",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7560321715817694,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.725487163625116,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023256,
      "question_number": "91",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a scenario about cavernous sinus thrombosis, what imaging study is recommended?",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. MRI with MRV",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7476635514018691,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.6869723033220232,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023257,
      "question_number": "83",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "An IV drug user presented with an acute stroke within 2 hours. A noncontrast head CT (showing no hem...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Antibiotics"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023258,
      "question_number": "49",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with a history of vertigo and nausea. Diffusion-weighted imaging (DWI) showed abn...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "B. Left uvula deviation",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7584541062801933,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5872176838058626,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023259,
      "question_number": "45",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient presents with third nerve palsy, tremor, and hearing loss. Which artery is likely involved...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. AICA"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023260,
      "question_number": "18",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with visual defect, what is the artery involved?",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023261,
      "question_number": "33",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A middle-aged patient presented with sudden severe headache associated with blurred vision. On exami...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "status": "answer_fixed",
      "new_answer": "A. Pituitary apoplexy"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023262,
      "question_number": "407",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A patient with a left middle cerebral artery (MCA) aneurysm underwent clipping and subsequently expe...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Optic nerve",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.865625,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.5326547921967769,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023263,
      "question_number": "93",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a scenario resembling cavernous sinus thrombosis but without proptosis, what is the likely diagno...",
      "old_answer": "C",
      "new_answer": "C. CVT",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7058823529411765,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7538381018841591,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023264,
      "question_number": "6",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "In a patient with Moyamoya disease presenting with right\u2010sided weakness and CTA showing severe steno...",
      "old_answer": "B",
      "new_answer": "B. Aspirin and Plavix",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.774818401937046,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.7222619899785254,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023265,
      "question_number": "190",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "A 63-year-old male has acute bilateral lower limb weakness, lower back pain, and urinary incontinenc...",
      "old_answer": "A",
      "new_answer": "A. Spinal cord infarction (Anterior Spinal Artery Syndrome)",
      "answer_updated": true,
      "status": "fixed",
      "similarity": 0.7495145631067961,
      "explanation_similarity": 0.025017512258581006,
      "match_method": "cross_subspecialty"
    },
    {
      "mcq_id": 100023266,
      "question_number": "90",
      "subspecialty": "Vascular Neurology Stroke",
      "question_text": "Based on the following visual field defect in picture B, which artery is involved?",
      "old_answer": "D",
      "status": "no_match",
      "similarity": 0
    }
  ]
}